<text xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0 UNTtite%20(1.3).xsd" xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="TEI">
<body>
<pb n="415" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="241" />
<div1 type="article">
<head type="main">JOINT RESOLUTIONS.</head>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER I.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution to authorize officers elect to act under existing laws until further legislation.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Section 1. Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the sheriffs, clerks, justices of the peace and constables, elected and qualified according to law, under the Constitution of the State of Texas, enter upon the discharge of their duties, respectively, under the laws now existing; which laws for said purpose are hereby continued in full force until further legislation on the subject.</p>
<p>Sec. 2. That this resolution take effect and be in full force from and after its passage.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 23, 1870</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER II.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution asking the Congress of the United States to prevent the Republic of Mexico from harboring bands of Indians, who devastate the south-western frontier of the State of Texas.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, during the last five years certain bands of Indians, known as Kickapoos and Lipans, residing in the States of Coahuila and Tamaulipas, Republic of Mexico, have been making constant raids into the settlements upon the south-western frontier of this State, killing scores of our citizens and driving off large quantities of live stock into Mexico, thereby retarding the settlement and de<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />velopment of many counties in this State and tending to the depopu<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" /><pb n="416" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="242" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>lation and destruction of the scattered settlements on our south-western frontier; and</p>
<p>Whereas, these Indians have resided, and are still residing in and con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tiguous to cities and villages of the Mexican States named; and</p>
<p>Whereas, It is notorious that these Indians have been Constantly aided and encouraged by the citizens of Mexico in their murderous forays upon our soil, armed bands of said Indians, with known hostile intents con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />stantly crossing the Rio Grande from Mexico to this State with the full knowledge and consent of the Mexican authorities, and returning from such expeditions laden with booty captured from our unfortunate citi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />zens, without opposition or interference on the part of the Mexican au<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />thorities; and</p>
<p>Whereas, there can be no relief for the people upon the south-western frontier of this State so long as the Republic of Mexico Continues to pro<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tect and furnish a safe asylum to these savage bands of thieves and mur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />derers; therefore,</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the gov<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ernment of the United States is earnestly requested to at once take measures to compel the Republic of Mexico to fulfill its duties as a friendly power, by no longer permitting its soil to be used as an asylum for the bands of thieving and murderous Indians who, for the last five years, have devastated the south-western frontier of this State, with the full knowledge of the Mexican authorities and the aid of the Mexican people.</p>
<p>Be it further resolved, That copies of this preamble and resolution be forwarded to the President of the United States. President of the Senate and Speaker of the House of Representatives of the United States, and to each one of the senators and representatives from this State in the Congress of the United States.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 24, 1870</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER III.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution asking the Government of the United States to improve the bars at Galveston. Pass Cavallo, Aransas Pass, Sabine Pass and Brazos Santiago.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, The interest of commerce and the prosperity of the State of Texas would be greatly advanced by the improvement of the bars at Galveston, Pass Cavallo, Aransas Pass, Sabine Pass and<pb n="417" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="243" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>Brazos Santiago, so that sea-going vessels of average tonnage could cross said bars regularly, and without danger or impediment; and</p>
<p>whereas, the ports to be reached by crossing said bars are the natural outlets and shipping points, not only for the products of the great State of Texas, but also for a large portion of northern Mexico, and probably will be such, in the near future, for several of the States and Territories lying to the north of Texas; and</p>
<p>Whereas, the General Government expends millions of dollars annually for bar, harbor and river improvements, and such improvements are be<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />lieved to be proper subjects for the action of the General Government; therefore</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />gress of the United States is earnestly petitioned to enact such measures, and make such appropriations as may be necessary to improve the bars at Galveston, Pass Cavallo, Aransas Pass, Sabine Pass and Brazos San<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tiago, so that sea-going vessels of average tonnage may be able to cross such bars regularly and without danger or impediment.</p>
<p>Be it further resolved, That a copy of this preamble and resolution be transmitted to the President of the Senate and Speaker of the House of Representatives of the United States, and to each one of the senators and representatives from this State in the Congress of the United States, and that such senators are hereby instructed and such representatives re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />quested to use their utmost endeavors to secure the legislation indicated in this resolution.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 24, 1870</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER IV.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That we in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />struct our Senators, and request our Representatives in Congress to urge the immediate passage of such measures by the Congress of the United States as will protect our frontier from Indian depredations; to the end that the Legislature of this State may, by proper legislation, assist in the same.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 27, 1870</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="418" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="244" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER V.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint. Resolution Requiring the Late Assessors and Collectors to Com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />plete the Assessment of Taxes in their Respective Counties, and Make Return Thereof to the Comptroller of Public Accounts, on or before the first day of August, 1870.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, the late assessors and collectors of this State are required by General Orders No. 74, Headquarters Fifth Military District, of date April 16, 1870, &#8220;to complete the assessment of taxes in their respective counties, and return their rolls to the Comptroller of Public Accounts on or before the first day of June, 1870;&#8221; and</p>
<p>Whereas, up to this date returns have been received at the Comp<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />troller&#8217;s office from only four counties, viz: Atascosa, Gillespie, Jack<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />son and Mason; and</p>
<p>Whereas, In the opinion of the Comptroller of Public Accounts, the time in which assessors shall be required to return their rolls for 1870, should be extended at least sixty days; therefore,</p>
<p>Be it resolved, That assessors and collectors shall complete the assess<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ment of taxes in their respective counties, and return their rolls to the Comptroller of Public Accounts on or before the first day of August, 1870; and that every assessor and collector failing or refusing so to com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />plete his assessment and make return thereof, as herein required, and within the time herein specified, shall be subject to a penalty of five hundred dollars, to be recovered upon his official bond; and his final settlement with the Comptroller of Public Accounts shall be suspended; provided, that in counties where there are no assessors and collectors of taxes, it shall be the duty of the justices of the peace of their respective beats or precincts to assess the taxes in accordance with existing laws; and the sheriffs of said counties shall collect the taxes, in accordance with existing laws.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>June 15, 1870</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="419" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="245" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER VI.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution in Relation to Salaries of Provisional District Judges.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, By General Orders No. 74 of the commander of the Fifth Military District, dated at Austin, Texas, April 16, 1870, declaring that the State of Texas had resumed her practical relations to the National Government, and that all authority conferred upon said commander by the Reconstruction Laws was remitted thereby to the civil authorities, it was directed that &#8220;All civil officers will continue in the discharge of their present duties until relieved by qualified successors,&#8221; etc.; and further, that &#8220;The Supreme and District Courts of the State will con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tinue in the discharge of their respective duties until the new courts shall be inaugurated;&#8221; and</p>
<p>Whereas, the several persons acting as judges of the District Courts of said State, in order to prevent the courts of justice from being closed, continued in the discharge of their respective duties as such judges; and</p>
<p>Whereas, there has been some doubt expressed as to the right of the Comptroller and Treasurer of the State to audit and pay the salaries of said judges for service rendered after the passage of the act re-districting the State, and the Comptroller refuses to audit claims for such salaries; therefore</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Comptroller of Public Accounts and the Treasurer of the State of Texas be directed to audit and pay the salaries of such judges as con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tinued in the official discharge of their duties, down to the time when the judges of the present districts, including the counties of the former districts of the respective military appointees, shall have been or may be nominated, confirmed and qualified; provided, that no such judge, who has been appointed judge of any district within the State, shall draw salary as such military appointee after he has qualified as judge of any of the present districts of the State; and provided further, that the unpaid balance of salaries due said provisional district judges be paid out of the unexpended balance of the appropriation already made by the commanding general of the Fifth Military District for payment of the seventeen district judges; provided, that no salary shall be audited or paid to any such provisional judge, unless satisfactory evidence be pro<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />duced to the Comptroller that such judge actually continued in the discharge of his official duties during the time for which he claims such salary.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>August 15, 1870</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="420" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="246" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER VII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution to defray the contingent expenses of the Twelfth Leg<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />islature.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas. That the sum of thirty thousand dollars, or so much thereof as may be necessary, be and the same is hereby appropriated, out of any money in the treasury not otherwise appropriated, to defray the contingent expenses of the Twelfth Legislature.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>August 15, 1870</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER VIII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint resolution authorizing the Governor to invite proposals for the location of two penitentiaries, and to report the result to the next session of the Legislature.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Gov<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ernor be, and he is hereby authorized and required, to invite proposals, by proclamation, for the location of two penitentiaries in this State, one east of the Trinity and one west of the Colorado rivers, and report the result to the next session of the Legislature.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>August 15, 1870</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="421" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="247" />
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">INDEX.</head>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">A.</head>
<p>Abstract of Titled and Patented Lands.</p>
<p>Page.</p>
<p>to be made out annually by Commissioner of General Land Office, and sent by Comptroller to each, district clerk................................................. 207</p>
<p>Accounts.</p>
<p>(See administrators, executors, guardians, justices of the peace, and sheriffs.)</p>
<p>Acts.</p>
<p>and parts of, repealed.................................... 5, 16, 18, 31, 33, 45, 49, 59, 66, 70, 75, 77, 84, 127, 128, 139, 183, 196, 233, 234.</p>
<p>Adjutant General.</p>
<p>one to be appointed, with rank of colonel................. 13</p>
<p>duties of........................................ 13</p>
<p>to be quartermaster and commissary general........................... 13</p>
<p>duties of as such............................................ 13</p>
<p>to be chief of State Police................................. 19</p>
<p>duties of as such....................................... 19</p>
<p>Administration of Estates.</p>
<p>definition of.............................................. 143</p>
<p>effected how........................................... 144</p>
<p>commencement of, where deceased left a will...................150-154</p>
<p>commencement of, where deceased did not leave a will. 155-156</p>
<p>closing of.................................... 183</p>
<p>general mode of................................................ 160-161</p>
<p>object of.................................... 144</p>
<p>parties to the...................................... 146-148</p>
<pb n="422" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="248" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Administration of Estates&#8212;continued.</p>
<p>place of commencing................................... 148-149</p>
<p>temporary labors of.................................. 149</p>
<p>time of commencing and continuance of.................. 146</p>
<p>Administrators.</p>
<p>accounts of.................................. 176-177</p>
<p>application of, wishing to resign......................... 177-178</p>
<p>bond or oath of......................................... 157</p>
<p>claims of, against estates, how exhibited................. 167</p>
<p>death, resignation or removal of........................... 177-180</p>
<p>duties of, in collection of an estate............................ 158-165</p>
<p>Ad valorem tax.</p>
<p>when, on what, and at what rate to be levied............... 199</p>
<p>Agent.</p>
<p>Governor appointed, to dispose of State bonds........... 46</p>
<p>responsible for taxes, on property rendered by him............. 213</p>
<p>special, to be appointed, for the purchase of means of transportation etc................................ 8</p>
<p>Aide-de-camp.</p>
<p>each brigadier general of militia entitled to one................. 14</p>
<p>Aides-de-camp.</p>
<p>each major general of militia entitled, to two............... 14</p>
<p>Governor entitled to three&#8212;of whom one to act as private secretary, if required................................. 14</p>
<p>Aldermen.</p>
<p>board of, for each city and town, to be appointed by Gov<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ernor.................................. 17</p>
<p>Alsbury, Juana Navaro.</p>
<p>pension o................................................ 123</p>
<p>Alterations.</p>
<p>not to be made in property books, when certified........... 222</p>
<p>Ammunition.</p>
<p>Governor to contract for full supplies of.................... 6</p>
<p>Anderson.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<pb n="423" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="249" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Anderson, W. H.</p>
<p>pension, of.......................... 123</p>
<p>Angelina.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Answers.</p>
<p>to justices of the peace (assessing,) to be under oath......... 216</p>
<p>Appeals.</p>
<p>from District Courts in matters of probate.........197-198</p>
<p>in cases of misdemeanor, from justices of the peace......... 107</p>
<p>(see Board of Appeals and Revision.)</p>
<p>Appraisement.</p>
<p>of an estate......................................... 159-160</p>
<p>Appraisers.</p>
<p>of property, may be chosen by justice of the peace, and per<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />son rendering property.................................... 214</p>
<p>disagreeing, may choose third appraiser..................... 214</p>
<p>Appropriations.</p>
<p>for covering deficiency in cost of making lists of registered voters....................................... 47</p>
<p>for defraying expense of ranging companies................... 64</p>
<p>for defraying expense of registration................... 31</p>
<p>for defraying expense of next general election............ 139</p>
<p>for mileage and per diem pay of members, etc., of Twelfth Legislature..................................1, 11</p>
<p>for payment of fees of justices of the peace and peace offi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cers, etc...................................................... 125</p>
<p>Appropriations.</p>
<p>for pensions, veterans of Revolution................. 119</p>
<p>for printing and contingent expenses, Twelfth Legisla<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ture................................................1, 23, 86, 246</p>
<p>for printing State bonds....................... 46</p>
<p>for procuring blank forms for assessment, etc............... 233</p>
<p>for provisional officers............................. 32</p>
<p>for quarantine.......................................... 5</p>
<p>for re-covering Treasury building........................... 46</p>
<p>for repairs, etc., of public buildings.......................... 140</p>
<p>for safe and furniture for Treasurer&#8217;s office................. 62</p>
<pb n="424" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="250" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>For salary of Judge of Criminal Court of Galveston and Harris counties......................................... 112</p>
<p>for support of State Government............................. 119-123</p>
<p>Aransas Pass........................................ 242-243</p>
<p>Archer County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Arms.</p>
<p>Governor to contract for 1500 stand of breech-loading.... 6</p>
<p>right to Dear, prohibited, where, and when................</p>
<p>Arrest,</p>
<p>(see warrant of arrest.)</p>
<p>Assessment Rolls.</p>
<p>when and by whom to be made, contents of, etc....219, 220</p>
<p>to serve as guide to Comptroller, in his settlement with sheriffs.................................................... 219</p>
<p>to be admitted as evidence in any proceeding for judgment against sheriff, on account of taxes.................. 220</p>
<p>Assessors</p>
<p>(see justices of the peace.)</p>
<p>Assets</p>
<p>of decedent, liable for payment of taxes due by estate.... 217</p>
<p>Atascosa County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Attorney.</p>
<p>(see county attorney, district attorney.)</p>
<p>Austin County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">B.</head>
<p>Bail.</p>
<p>what, and how given.................................... 106</p>
<pb n="425" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="251" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Bail Bond.</p>
<p>how taken, when justice of the peace has not jurisdiction.. 106</p>
<p>may be taken by justice of the peace having jurisdiction, or</p>
<p>officer, etc., when................................. 106</p>
<p>requisites of........................................... 106</p>
<p>Bandera County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Barnett, Thomas</p>
<p>pension of.............................................. 103</p>
<p>Bastrop County.</p>
<p>Baylor County.</p>
<p>Bee County.</p>
<p>Bell County,</p>
<p>Bexar Comity.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Bill of Review..................................... 198</p>
<p>Blanco County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Board of Appeals and Revision.</p>
<p>accounts of members of, on whom drawn ............................. 30</p>
<p>any member of, may procure certified copy of district clerk&#8217;s list of voters, in cases specified.................... 27</p>
<p>compensation of members of.......................... 29</p>
<p>duties of..................................... 26</p>
<p>each member of, to take oath of office...................... 25</p>
<p>empowered to administer oaths.................... 26</p>
<p>penalty on any member of, refusing to produce list of regis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tered voters, received from registrar................. 27</p>
<p>penalty for resisting, etc................................ 29</p>
<p>penalty for disturbing, by intimidation, etc.................. 31</p>
<p>provisions for cases of vacancy in................................ 30</p>
<p>registrar to attend sessions of........................ 27</p>
<p>shall, after election, deliver to registrar, list of voters used by them........................................... 28</p>
<p>term of office, and service............................. 25</p>
<p>time and place of meeting of............................. 26</p>
<p>to be also, &#8220;judges of election.&#8221;....................... 25</p>
<pb n="426" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="252" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Board of Appeals and Revision,</p>
<p>to be appointed in each organized county.................. 25</p>
<p>to be appointed, when................................. 25</p>
<p>to be free from arrest.............................. 30</p>
<p>(see judges of election.)</p>
<p>Bond.</p>
<p>of an executor or administrator...................... 157</p>
<p>of justices of the peace (as assessors)...................... 204</p>
<p>of justices of the pease (as assessors)................... 204</p>
<p>of justices of the peace (as assessors,) to be filed with dis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />trict clerk.................................. 204</p>
<p>of sheriff................................ 224</p>
<p>Bondage.</p>
<p>issue of, persons formerly living in, declared legitimate... 128</p>
<p>persons formerly in, and now living as man and wife, con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sidered legally married.................................. 128</p>
<p>Bonds.</p>
<p>State, to be issued and sold for payment of expense of ranging companies................................. 45</p>
<p>State Treasurer to invest sinking fund of, in U. S. interest<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />bearing bonds, etc...................................... 46</p>
<p>tax to be levied to pay interest, and sinking fund of.... 45, 46</p>
<p>when payable; when redeemable...................... 45</p>
<p>Bosque County.</p>
<p>Bowie County.</p>
<p>Brazoria County.</p>
<p>Brazos County.</p>
<p>Brown County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Buildings.</p>
<p>new, not to be assessed till fit for use, etc.................... 209</p>
<p>old, increased in value, how to be assessed................... 209</p>
<p>public, appropriation for repairs of................... 140</p>
<p>public, Police Courts authorized, to levy special tax for re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />pairs and completion of......................... 47</p>
<p>Burleson County.</p>
<p>Burnet County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
</div3>
<pb n="427" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="253" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">C.</head>
<p>Caldwell County.</p>
<p>Callahan County.</p>
<p>Calhoun County.</p>
<p>Cameron County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Canal Companies.</p>
<p>to report gross earnings quarterly...................... 216</p>
<p>Capitation Tax.</p>
<p>an annual, to be levied............................. 199</p>
<p>part of &#8220;available school fund&#8221;....................... 118</p>
<p>proceeds of, for benefit of public schools................ 118</p>
<p>Census.</p>
<p>scholastic, to be taken annually............................... 116</p>
<p>one copy of, to be transmitted to State Treasurer, and one filed with district clerk........................... 116</p>
<p>Certified Copies of Written Documents.</p>
<p>from heads of departments, received in evidence, when... 62</p>
<p>Chambers County.</p>
<p>Cherokee County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Chief Clerk.</p>
<p>House of Representatives, to cause &#8220;House journal&#8221; to be delivered to State Printer, when adopted........... 72</p>
<p>to place on the roll of the &#8220;House,&#8221; the names of represen<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tatives elect, as furnished by the Secretary of State.... 136</p>
<p>Claims.</p>
<p>for money against estates.............................. 166, 169</p>
<p>for money against estates of minors...................... 191</p>
<p>for money against estates of persons of unsound mind and habitual drunkards....................................... 194</p>
<p>classification of, and the order in which they shall be paid.................................... 170, 171</p>
<p>other than for money, and of other controversies......173, 174</p>
<p>payment of, against estates......................171, 173</p>
<pb n="428" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="254" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Claim Docket.</p>
<p>Nature and contents of....................... 169</p>
<p>Clay County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Clerks of the District Courts.</p>
<p>(see district clerks)</p>
<p>Code of Criminal Procedure.</p>
<p>articles three hundred and seventy-nine and three hun<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dred and eighty of the, amended.................... 67</p>
<p>Cold Springs.</p>
<p>town of, made county site of San Jacinto county.......... 79</p>
<p>Cole, David.</p>
<p>pension of.......................... 123</p>
<p>Coleman County.</p>
<p>Collin County.</p>
<p>Colorado County.</p>
<p>Comal County.</p>
<p>Comanche County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Commissioner of General Land Office.</p>
<p>to issue patents on certain settler&#8217;s claims in Hood county........................................................34, 35</p>
<p>to issue patents for all claims confirmed under chapter eighty-three, General Laws of 1870................... 203</p>
<p>to make abstract, annually, of all titled and patented lands 207</p>
<p>one thousand copies of annual report of, to be printed.... 71</p>
<p>Comptroller of Public Accounts.</p>
<p>authorized to invest in &#8220;five-twenty&#8221; United States bonds, the moneys of the school fund, now in the State Treas<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ury, and to deposit bonds and coupons in the State Treasury...................................... 68</p>
<p>authorized to retain moneys due to State Lunatic Asylum 9</p>
<p>fee of, for certificate of payment of taxes..................... 230</p>
<p>drafts drawn by, on sheriff, to be paid by sheriff, if in funds 231</p>
<pb n="429" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="255" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Comptroller of Public Accounts.</p>
<p>instructions of, binding on all justices of the peace, clerks and sheriffs............................................. 221</p>
<p>may appeal from decision of District Court and advise supersedeas, etc., when.................................. 223</p>
<p>may order sale of property bid in for State, at tax sale... 229</p>
<p>to allow sheriff credit for amount of State taxes due by in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />solvents.................................. 230</p>
<p>to furnish clerks of courts with necessary blank forms and books..................................... 221</p>
<p>to furnish each justice of the peace printed forms for land register, etc., and all necessary blank forms andb ooks, for purposes of assessment, and to issue him instructions by printed circular......................................206, 221</p>
<p>to furnish sheriffs with all necessary blanks and books for collection...................................... 221</p>
<p>prohibited from settling with sheriff without marginal duplicates.......................................... 227</p>
<p>to make index of chapter eighty-four, General Laws of 1870................................................. 233</p>
<p>to publish notice concerning defaulting sheriffs......... 231</p>
<p>to receive tax on any part of a lot, if furnished with partic<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ular specifications.................................................229-230</p>
<p>to receive taxes from non-residents........................... 230</p>
<p>to report misconduct of justices of the peace.................. 206</p>
<p>to send annually to district clerks, abstract of titled and patented lands....................................... 207</p>
<p>to transmit to sheriffs lists of taxes paid to himself....... 230</p>
<p>Concho county.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Constitutional Convention.</p>
<p>ordinance of, legalized................................ 10</p>
<p>Cook County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Cooper, Dillard.</p>
<p>pension of............................................. 123</p>
<p>Cooper.</p>
<p>named county site of county of Delta......................... 43</p>
<pb n="430" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="256" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Coryell County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>County Attorney.</p>
<p>authorized to administer oaths............................... 112</p>
<p>duties of................................. 111</p>
<p>fees of.......................................... 111-112</p>
<p>to assist district attorney when............................. 112</p>
<p>County Courts.</p>
<p>how composed.................................. 108</p>
<p>may appoint agents to contract for erection and repairs of county buildings................................... 111</p>
<p>may appoint commissioner to sell real estate or connty.... 110</p>
<p>may appoint county attorney......................... 111</p>
<p>powers of................................ 108-109</p>
<p>terms of&#8212;regular and special......................... 110</p>
<p>to be &#8220;ex officio&#8221; boards of school directors&#8212;duties of, as such board...................................114-115</p>
<p>to have like powers as District Courts, to punish for con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tempt....................................... 109</p>
<p>to provide books, etc., for offices of clerks of the District Court, County Court, and for justices of the peace.... 111</p>
<p>to provide manual labor poor houses............................ 111</p>
<p>to take measures for prosecuting and defending suits by and against county................................. 110</p>
<p>to require district clerk to transcribe records of county when defaced, worn, etc............................ 111</p>
<p>County Judges.</p>
<p>certain official acts of, validated......................... 77</p>
<p>County Surveyor.</p>
<p>to survey land sold for taxes, when ordered by sheriff.... 229</p>
<p>County Surveyors.</p>
<p>official acts of&#8212;appointed county judges, legalized, but subject to proviso................................ 112</p>
<p>County Tax.</p>
<p>must be levied at regular term of County Court.......... 110</p>
<p>see taxes (county.)</p>
<pb n="431" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="257" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Criminal District Court</p>
<p>of Galveston and Harris counties created................ 37</p>
<p>duties and powers of............................ 37, 38</p>
<p>attorney of..................................... 38</p>
<p>clerk of...................................... 39</p>
<p>feees and salaries of attorney and clerk of.................. 38, 39</p>
<p>judge of..................................... 38</p>
<p>&#8220;nolle prosequi,&#8221; not to be entered, in any case in, till when................................................ 39</p>
<p>practice of...................................... 38</p>
<p>salary of judge of.................................... 112</p>
<p>seal of...................................... 38</p>
<p>sheriffs of Galveston and Harris comities, to attend on... 39</p>
<p>Counties.</p>
<p>Anderson, act apportioning causes on docket of, repealed. 84</p>
<p>in Tenth Judicial District..................... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...................... 53</p>
<p>Angelina, act apportioning causes on docket of, repealed. 84</p>
<p>in Third Judicial District.............................. 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................. 51</p>
<p>Archer, attached to Twelfth Judicial District, and Mon<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tague county, for judicial purposes......................22, 53</p>
<p>Atascosa, in Seventeenth Judicial District............... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Counts of.................. 55</p>
<p>Austin, in Twenty-first Judicial District.................. 22</p>
<p>times of bolding District Courts of............... 56</p>
<p>Bandera, in Twenty-fourth Judicial District........... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...................... 56</p>
<p>Bastrop, in Twenty-seventh Judicial District............. 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................. 57</p>
<p>Baylor, attached to Twelfth Judicial District, and Mon<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tague county, for indicial purpose.....................22, 53</p>
<p>Bee, in Seventeenth Judicial District.............................. 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of............... 55</p>
<p>Bell, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District........................ 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................... 59</p>
<p>Bexar, concerning the levy of taxes for.......................... 65</p>
<p>in Twenty-third Judicial District....................... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of.................... 56</p>
<p>Blanco, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District..................... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of.......................... 57</p>
<p>Bosque, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District..................... 23</p>
<p>times of bolding District Courts of.................. 59</p>
<pb n="432" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="258" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Bowie, in Eighth Judicial District........................ 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of........................... 52</p>
<p>Brazoria, in Eighteenth Judicial District....................... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of........................... 55</p>
<p>Brazos, election provided for, to determine change in boundary of................................ 50</p>
<p>in Twenty-eighth Judicial District...................... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of.................... 57</p>
<p>Brown, in Thirty-second Judicial District........................ 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...................... 58</p>
<p>Burleson, county site provided for, if boundary of be changed...................................... 50</p>
<p>election provided for, to determine change in bound<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ary of....................................... 50</p>
<p>in Twenty-eighth Judicial District............... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of.........................</p>
<p>Burnet, in Thirty-second Judicial District........................ 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of....................... 58</p>
<p>Caldwell, in Twenty-second Judicial District................ 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................... 56</p>
<p>Callahan, attached to Thirteenth Judicial District, and Palo Pinto county, for judicial purposes...................22, 54</p>
<p>Calhoun, in Sixteenth Judicial District......................... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of.............. 54</p>
<p>Cameron, boundaries of, marked and established........ 40</p>
<p>in Fifteenth Judicial District......................... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...................... 54</p>
<p>Chambers, in First Judicial District....................... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...................... 51</p>
<p>Cherokee, act, apportioning causes on docket of, repealed. 84</p>
<p>in Fourth Judicial District.................... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of 52</p>
<p>Clay, attached to Twelfth Judicial District and Montague county for judicial purposes.............................22, 53</p>
<p>Coleman, attached to Thirty-second Judicial District and Brown county, for judicial purposes............................23, 58</p>
<p>Collin, in Eleventh Judicial District...................... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of 53</p>
<p>Colorado, in Twenty-first Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 56</p>
<p>Comal, in Twenty-third Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 56</p>
<pb n="433" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="259" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Comanche, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District...... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 59</p>
<p>Concho, attached to Thirty-second Judicial District and San Saba county, for judicial purposes..... 23, 58</p>
<p>Cook, in Twelfth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 53</p>
<p>Coryell, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 59</p>
<p>Dallas, in Fourteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 54</p>
<p>Davis, in Seventh Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 52</p>
<p>Delta, created, and boundaries of defined..... 42</p>
<p>attached to eighth judicial, and tenth senatorial dis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />trict..... 43</p>
<p>county seat of..... 43</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 126</p>
<p>Denton, in Twelfth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 53</p>
<p>De Witt, in Twenty-second Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 56</p>
<p>Dimmitt, attached to Twenty-fourth Judicial District, and Maverick county, for judicial purposes..... 22, 57</p>
<p>Duval, attached to Sixteenth Judicial District, and to Nueces county...... 22, 55</p>
<p>boundaries of, defined..... 40</p>
<p>Eastland, attached to Thirteenth Judicial District, and Palo Pinto county, for judicial purposes..... 22, 54</p>
<p>Edwards, attached to Twenty-sixth Judicial District, and Kerr county, for judicial purposes...... 57</p>
<p>Ellis, in Fourteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 54</p>
<p>El Paso, in Twenty-fifth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 57</p>
<p>Encinal, attached to Ffteenth Judicial District, and Webb county, for judicial purposes.......22, 54</p>
<p>boundaries of, defined..... 40</p>
<p>Erath, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 59</p>
<p>Falls, in Thirty-third Judicial District...... 23</p>
<p>special tax, as voted, to be collected in..... 10</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 58</p>
<p>Fannin, in Eleventh Judicial District...... 21</p>
<pb n="434" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="260" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 53</p>
<p>Fort Bend, in Twenty-first Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 56</p>
<p>Freestone, in Thirty-first Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 58</p>
<p>Frio, attached to Medina county, for judicial purposes.... 57</p>
<p>Galveston, Criminal District Court of, established....37, 38, 39</p>
<p>in Eighteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding Criminal District Courts of..... 38</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 55</p>
<p>Gillespie, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 57</p>
<p>Goliad, acts of Police Court of, legalized...... 37</p>
<p>In Seventeenth Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 55</p>
<p>Gonzales, in Twenty-second Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 56</p>
<p>Grayson, in Twelfth Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 53</p>
<p>Grimes, in Thirtieth Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 58</p>
<p>Guadalupe, in Twenty-second Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 56</p>
<p>Hamilton, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District...... 23</p>
<p>qualification, etc., of officers of, legalized...... 49</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 59</p>
<p>Hardeman, attached to Twelfth Judicial District, and to Montague county for judicial purposes...... 22, 53</p>
<p>Hardin, in first Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 51</p>
<p>Harris, Criminal District Court of, established...... 37, 38, 39</p>
<p>in Nineteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding Criminal District Courts of...... 38</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 55</p>
<p>Harrison, in Sixth Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 52</p>
<p>Haskell, attached to Thirteenth Judicial District, and Jack county for judicial purposes..... 22, 54</p>
<p>Hays, in Twenty-seventh Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 57</p>
<p>Henderson, in tenth Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 53</p>
<p>Hidalgo, boundaries of, defined..... 40</p>
<pb n="435" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="261" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>attached to Cameron county, for judicial purposes... 54</p>
<p>in Fifteenth Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 54</p>
<p>Hill, election authorized for location of county seat of.... 63</p>
<p>in Thirty-fifth Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 59</p>
<p>Hood, in Thirteenth Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>settler&#8217;s claims in, determined..... 35</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 54</p>
<p>Hopkins, county seat of, established..... 18</p>
<p>in Eleventh Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 53</p>
<p>Houston, in Third Judicial District...... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 51</p>
<p>Hunt, in Eleventh Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 53</p>
<p>Jack, in Thirteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 52</p>
<p>Jackson, in Twentieth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 55</p>
<p>Jasper in Second Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 51</p>
<p>Jefferson, in First Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 51</p>
<p>Johnson, in thirteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 54</p>
<p>Jones, attached to Thirteenth Judicial District and Palo Pinto county for judicial purposes...... 22, 54</p>
<p>Karnes, in Seventeenth Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 55</p>
<p>Kaufman, in Tenth Judicial District...... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 53</p>
<p>Kendall, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 57</p>
<p>Kerr, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 57</p>
<p>Kimball, attached to Twenty-sixth Judicial District and Gillespie county, for judicial purposes..... 58</p>
<p>Kinney, attached to Twenty-fourth Judicial District, and Uvalde county, for judicial purposes...... 22, 57</p>
<p>Knox, attached to Twelfth Judicial District, and Mon<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tague, county, for judicial purposes...... 22, 53</p>
<p>Lamar, in Eighth Judicial District..... 21</p>
<pb n="436" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="262" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 52</p>
<p>Lampasas, in Thirty-second Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 58</p>
<p>La Salle, attached to Fifteenth Judicial District, and Webb county, for judicial purposes...... 22, 54</p>
<p>Lavaca, in Twentieth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>special term of District Court of, authorized...... 60, 61</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 55</p>
<p>Leon, in Thirty-first Judicial District...... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 58</p>
<p>Llano, in Thirty-second Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 58</p>
<p>Liberty, in First Judicial District...... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 51</p>
<p>Limestone, in Thirty-fifth Judicial District...... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 59</p>
<p>Live Oak, in Seventeenth Judicial District....... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 55</p>
<p>Madison, in Thirtieth Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 58</p>
<p>Marion, in Seventh Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 52</p>
<p>Mason, in Thirty-second Judicial District...... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 58</p>
<p>Matagorda, in Twentieth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 55</p>
<p>Maverick, in Twenty-fourth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 56</p>
<p>McCulloch, attached to Thirty-second Judicial District, and San Saba county, for Judicial purposes...... 23, 58</p>
<p>McLennan, in Thirty-third Judicial District..... 23</p>
<p>special tax, as voted, to be collected in..... 10</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 59</p>
<p>McMullen, attached to Seventeenth Judicial District, and Live Oak county, for judicial purposes..... 22, 55</p>
<p>Medina, in Twenty-fourth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 56</p>
<p>Menard, attached to Thirty-second Judicial District, and Mason county, for judicial purposes..... 23, 58</p>
<p>Montague, in Twelfth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 53</p>
<p>Montgomery, in Nineteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 55</p>
<pb n="437" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="263" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Nacogdoches, in Fourth Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 52</p>
<p>Newton, in Second Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 51</p>
<p>Nueces, boundaries of, defined..... 40</p>
<p>in Sixteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 55</p>
<p>Orange, in First Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 51</p>
<p>Palo Pinto, in Thirteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 54</p>
<p>Panola, act apportioning causes on docket of, repealed... 84</p>
<p>in Fifth Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 52</p>
<p>Parker, in Thirteenth Judicial District..... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 54</p>
<p>Polk, in Second Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 51</p>
<p>Presidio, organized....... 32, 33</p>
<p>county seat of, to be determined by election...... 33</p>
<p>in Twenty-fifth Judicial District......... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of........ 57</p>
<p>Rains, created, and boundaries of defined......... 2</p>
<p>in Ninth Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 52</p>
<p>portions of, to belong to counties from whence taken, till when...... 3</p>
<p>Red River, in Eighth Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 52</p>
<p>Refugio, in Sixteenth Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 54</p>
<p>Robertson, county seat of, removed and located..... 31</p>
<p>in Thirty-first Judicial District........... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 58</p>
<p>Runnels, attached to Thirty-second Judicial District, and Brown county, for judicial purposes.......23, 58</p>
<p>Rusk, in Sixth Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>special tax, for building jail in, legalized...... 36</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 52</p>
<p>Sabine, in Fifth Judicial District...... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of...... 52</p>
<p>San Augustine, in Fourth Judicial District..... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of..... 52</p>
<pb n="438" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="264" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>San Jacinto, created, and boundaries defined...... 79</p>
<p>made part of Thirtieth Judicial District........ 126</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of....... 125</p>
<p>San Patricio, in Sixteenth Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of......... 54</p>
<p>San Saba, in Thirty<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />second Judicial District........ 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of....... 58</p>
<p>Shackleford, attached for judicial purposes to Thirteenth Judicial District...... 22</p>
<p>attached for judicial purposes to Palo Pinto county.. 54</p>
<p>Shelby, in Fifth Judicial District........ 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of......... 52</p>
<p>Smith, act apportioning causes on docket of, repealed.... 84</p>
<p>in Ninth Judicial District........... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of........ 53</p>
<p>Starr, boundaries of, defined.......... 40</p>
<p>in Fifteenth Judicial District....... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of......... 54</p>
<p>Stevens, attached to Thirteenth Judicial District, and Palo Pinto county, for judicial purposes........ 22, 54</p>
<p>Tarrant, in Fourteenth Judicial District........ 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of......... 54</p>
<p>Taylor, attached to Thirteenth Judicial District, and Palo Pinto county, for judicial purposes..........22, 54</p>
<p>Throckmorton, attached to Thirteenth Judicial District, and Jack county, for judicial purposes...... 22, 54</p>
<p>Titus, in Seventh Judicial District......... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of............ 52</p>
<p>Travis, in Twenty-seventh Judicial District.......... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of.......... 57</p>
<p>Trinity, in Third Judicial District................... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of.............. 51</p>
<p>Tyler, in Second Judicial District................... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of............. 51</p>
<p>Upshur, in Ninth Judicial District................. 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................ 52</p>
<p>Uvalde, in Twenty-fourth Judicial District........... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of............... 56</p>
<p>Van Zandt, in Tenth Judicial District.............. 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................. 53</p>
<p>Victoria, in Sixteenth Judicial District................... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of............... 54</p>
<p>Walker, in Thirtieth Judicial District.................. 23</p>
<pb n="439" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="265" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................. 58</p>
<p>Washington, in Twenty-ninth Judicial District......... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of.............. 57</p>
<p>Webb, boundaries of, defined.................... 40</p>
<p>in Fifteenth Judicial District................ 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of............. 54</p>
<p>Wharton, in Twentieth Judicial District.............. 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................ 55</p>
<p>Wichita, attached to Twelfth Judicial District, and Mon<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tague county, for judicial purposes................22, 53</p>
<p>Wilbarger, attached to Twelfth Judicial District, and Mon<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tague county, for judicial purposes...............22, 53</p>
<p>Williamson, in Thirty-second Judicial District.......... 23</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of............... 58</p>
<p>Wilson, in Twenty-third Judicial District............. 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of............... 56</p>
<p>Wise, in Twelfth Judicial District................... 22</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................. 53</p>
<p>Wood, in Ninth Judicial District................... 21</p>
<p>times of holding District Courts of................. 52</p>
<p>Young, attached to Thirteenth Judicial District, and Jack county, for judicial purposes...............22, 54</p>
<p>Zavalla, attached to Twenty-fourth Judicial District, and Maverick county, for judicial purposes............22, 57</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">D.</head>
<p>Dallas County.</p>
<p>Davis County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Davis, Rolla M.</p>
<p>pension of.................................... 123</p>
<p>Day, John.</p>
<p>pension of.......................... 123</p>
<p>Deed of Trust.</p>
<p>on goods or chattels not to prevent their being dis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />trained or sold for taxes.................... 230</p>
<p>Denton County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<pb n="440" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="266" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Deputy Sheriff.</p>
<p>bond of, to be available to heirs or representatives of sheriff................................... 226</p>
<p>duties of deceased or removed sheriff to devolve on...... 226</p>
<p>liable to be sued on bond, for default, malfeasance, etc... 231</p>
<p>one or more may be appointed by sheriff................ 225</p>
<p>or sheriff to call once on every person taxed, and leave written demand for taxes if person not to be found.... 226</p>
<p>penalty on, for extortion.......................... 227</p>
<p>to continue in office, if not disapproved by Comptroller.. 226</p>
<p>to give bond payable to sheriff..................... 225</p>
<p>to have same authority, within his own limits, as sheriff.. 225</p>
<p>to notify Comptroller of death or removal of sheriff..... 226</p>
<p>to remain at county seat in the absence of sheriff....... 225</p>
<p>to take and subscribe oath....................... 226</p>
<p>DeWitt County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>District Clerks.</p>
<p>appropriation for costs due to........................ 120</p>
<p>appropriation for fees due to, in 1869, and previous years. 123</p>
<p>claims allowed by executors and administrators to be filed with................................... 167</p>
<p>bonds of justices of the peace and sheriffs to be recorded in office of..........................204, 224</p>
<p>compensation and mode of payment of, under chapter eighty-four, General Laws of 1870................. 222</p>
<p>copy of citation to be delivered to, when suit is brought against a county.......................... 91</p>
<p>duties of, on receipt of commission from justice of the peace................................ 95-6</p>
<p>duties of, under chapter eighty-three, General Laws of 1870.......................................202-3</p>
<p>duty of, when aware that there is a minor in his county without guardian............................. 187</p>
<p>empowered to approve official bonds in certain cases...... 36</p>
<p>empowered to take acknowledgment of deeds, etc........ 49</p>
<p>executors or administrators wishing to resign, to file appli<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cation with..................................... 177</p>
<pb n="441" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="267" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>in future elections for, election to be returned to people, in case of an equality of votes................. 136</p>
<p>judge&#8217;s order, appointing another day for sale of prop<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />erty, when made in vacation, to be filed with.......... 167</p>
<p>papers to be copied by, in the record, or in docket........ 196</p>
<p>penalties on......................66, 133, 207, 219, 231</p>
<p>to annex certificate to land and personal property books.. 218</p>
<p>to approve bond securing debts against an estate, prior to removal of property......................... 189</p>
<p>to be legal custodians of all papers and records of late County Courts........................... 48</p>
<p>to be recorders of deeds and ex-officio clerks of County Courts for their respective counties............. 66</p>
<p>to compare and examine copies 0f land and personal prop<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />erty, books, etc...................... 218</p>
<p>to file bonds of justices of the peace................ 204</p>
<p>to forward to Comptroller certificates of delivery of books, etc., to sheriff............................ 220</p>
<p>to forward sheriff&#8217;s bonds to Comptroller................. 224</p>
<p>to furnish copy of list of lands alienated, etc., to justice of the peace................................ 207</p>
<p>to issue all writs, etc., necessary, to complete unfinished business of late County Courts..................... 48</p>
<p>to issue certificate to justice of the peace for fees and com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />missions..................................... 221</p>
<p>to Keep in one wrapper, all papers belonging to same suit, and not to permit any to be removed without taking re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ceipt....................................... 66</p>
<p>to keep cross indexes of all books and records, etc........ 66</p>
<p>to make list of all decrees, etc., for partition, and of lands devised during the year......................... 207</p>
<p>to make list of all deeds for partition, etc................ 206</p>
<p>to make out and forward assessment rolls to Comptroller. 219</p>
<p>to notify justices of the peace, when estate of decedent passes by will to other lineal descendants, etc........... 207</p>
<p>to perform all the duties now required of them by existing laws................................... 66</p>
<p>to preserve copies of official journal of the State............. 71</p>
<p>to retain one copy of land, and one of personal property books, and deliver one copy of each, and other data, to sheriff..................................... 219</p>
<pb n="442" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="268" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>to retain one copy of the list of registered voters received from registrar, and forward the other to Secretary of State...................................... 31</p>
<p>to settle accounts annually with district judge........... 222</p>
<p>to transfer to District Court docket undetermined causes on docket of late County Courts..................... 48</p>
<p>vacancies in office of, how filled........................ 17</p>
<p>District Clerk</p>
<p>of Presidio county, election of, provided for............ 33</p>
<p>of Travis county, certified account of amounts due by de<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />faulting sheriffs, to be filed with................. 231</p>
<p>judgment entered by, against defaulting sheriffs, to have same effect as if rendered by court................... 231</p>
<p>to enter up judgment, with interest, and ten per cent. pen<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />alty, against defaulting sheriffs................. 231</p>
<p>District Court.</p>
<p>all proceeedings relating to guardianship of minors, etc., transferred to................................. 196</p>
<p>appeals from, in matters of probate...................197, 198</p>
<p>appeals from justices&#8217; courts to....................98, 99</p>
<p>costs in, in matters of probate....................... 197</p>
<p>guardians appointed by........................... 184</p>
<p>jurisdiction of, in matters of probate.................... 141</p>
<p>may grant relief to any one aggrieved by entry on land book, or book of personal property................... 222</p>
<p>proceedings of, in cases under chapter eighty-four, section eighty-two, General Laws of 1870.................... 223</p>
<p>proceedings of, prior to March 30, 1870, legalized....... 9</p>
<p>records of, in matters of probate........................ 196</p>
<p>suit for specific performance of contract entered into by deceased, for conveyance of real property, must be brought in............................ 173</p>
<p>terms of, (see counties.)</p>
<p>to charge grand juries to inquire into all violations of reve<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />nue laws by justice of the peace.................. 223</p>
<p>two kinds of special proceedings in, in matters of probate. 142</p>
<p>unsettled proceedings in late County Courts, in relation to settlement of estates of decedents, to be transferred to 184</p>
<pb n="443" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="269" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>writs and process which were made returnable to former terms of, to be made returnable to next ensuing terms of, such writs and process legalized................ 80</p>
<p>of Lavaca county, special term of.................... 61</p>
<p>District Judge.</p>
<p>accounts of district clerks, under chapter eighty-four, General Laws of 1870, to be presented to, and settled by 222</p>
<p>bond of sheriff, as security for performance of duties in respect to county taxes, to be approved by............. 225</p>
<p>empowered to approve official bonds in certain cases..... 36</p>
<p>may remove justice of the peace and order new election when........................................ 205</p>
<p>may remove sheriff, and order new election, when.......... 225</p>
<p>may require new bond of justice of the peace............ 205</p>
<p>proceedings of, holding over under appointments made before March 30, 1870, legalized...................... 9</p>
<p>to approve bond of justice of the peace.................... 204</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">E.</head>
<p>Edwards County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Election.</p>
<p>general, what, and when held....................128-9</p>
<p>special, what, and when held......................... 128</p>
<p>for State, district and county officers, to be held when and where................................................ 129</p>
<p>first general................................. 129</p>
<p>to be returned, in future, to the people, in case of equality of votes........................................ 129</p>
<p>judges of, (see judges of election.)</p>
<p>Elections.</p>
<p>to fill vacancies, how conducted......................... 137</p>
<p>Ellis County.</p>
<p>El Paso County.</p>
<p>Erath County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<pb n="444" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="270" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Estate.</p>
<p>of a deceased person, claims against, for money................166-9</p>
<p>claims against, other than for money................... 173</p>
<p>classification of claims against......................171-3</p>
<p>collection of the....................... 158</p>
<p>commencement and continuance of administration of the. 146</p>
<p>distribution of the............................180-1</p>
<p>general mode of administering...........................161-2</p>
<p>land, to be chargeable to the, for taxes, till property charged to heir, devisee or grantee.................... 217</p>
<p>personal property, to be chargeable to the, for taxes, till disposed of................................ 217</p>
<p>payment of claims against............................171-3</p>
<p>payment of residue of..................................181-3</p>
<p>sales of, for payment of debts.....................174-6</p>
<p>settlement and distribution of.....................143-6</p>
<p>to be listed for taxes, by whom..................... 213</p>
<p>who entitled to administer the.....................146-8</p>
<p>where there are directions in a will as to the administra<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion of....................................... 164</p>
<p>of a minor, claims for money against...................... 191</p>
<p>of a minor, to be listed for taxes, by whom................. 213</p>
<p>of an idiot or lunatic, to be listed for taxes, by whom.... 213</p>
<p>of a person of unsound mind, and of a habitual drunkard.194-6</p>
<p>Evidence.</p>
<p>of payment of taxes required before titles to land shall be given or deeds recorded........................... 231</p>
<p>rules of, in justices&#8217; courts.......................... 96</p>
<p>Execution, stay of.</p>
<p>justice of the peace may grant......................... 99</p>
<p>not to prevent taking out writ of certiorari............... 99</p>
<p>Execution.</p>
<p>when to be issued by justice of the peace, on judgment for money................................ 99</p>
<p>Executions.</p>
<p>issued by justice of the peace, when returnable........... 99</p>
<p>on judgments rendered by the late County Courts, when returnable................................... 48</p>
<pb n="445" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="271" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Executor.</p>
<p>account required from, and payment of claims by......171-3</p>
<p>accounts of......................................176-7</p>
<p>death, resignation or removal of......................177, 180</p>
<p>duties of, as to estate............................161-2</p>
<p>duty of, desiring to settle title to an estate.............. 174</p>
<p>duty of, requiring possession of real, or recovery of per<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sonal property, belonging to an estate..................... 174</p>
<p>duty of, with respect to claims for money against an es<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tate........................................166-8</p>
<p>duty of, with respect to sale of real property, for payment of debts, etc...............................174-6</p>
<p>entitled to demand letters testamentary, after administra<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion granted, when.............................. 147</p>
<p>miscellaneous provisions concerning duties and liabilities of............................................165-6</p>
<p>oath of.................................. 154</p>
<p>personal property, passes to, to be disposed of......161, 164</p>
<p>power of, before grant of letters testamentary.......... 161</p>
<p>real property passes to possession of, to be preserved, hired or rented................................ 161</p>
<p>to enter into bond, unless testator direct otherwise...... 154</p>
<p>under twenty-one years of age at the time of proving the will, entitled to demand letters testamentary, when of age.......................................... 147</p>
<p>when, and how to be discharged.................... 183</p>
<p>when named in will, and afterwards renouncing, not to be appointed administrator of same estate............ 146</p>
<p>Exemptions.</p>
<p>from ad valorem tax, personal property............. 212</p>
<p>from ad valorem tax, real property.............. 210</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">F.</head>
<p>Falls County.</p>
<p>Fannin County.</p>
<p>Fayette County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Fees.</p>
<p>to justices of the peace for services rendered in connection with assessment..............................214, 220</p>
<pb n="446" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="272" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Field, Joseph E.</p>
<p>pension of............................... 123</p>
<p>Forced Sale for Debts.</p>
<p>what property exempt from............................ 127</p>
<p>Fort Bend County.</p>
<p>Freestone County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Frontier.</p>
<p>northern and western, Governor authorized to raise twenty companies of Texas Rangers for protection of the..... 5</p>
<p>(see Governor.)</p>
<p>Frontier Counties.</p>
<p>to be divided into districts........................ 7</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">G.</head>
<p>Galveston Bar......................................243, 244</p>
<p>Galveston County.</p>
<p>(see counties&#8212;&#8220;Criminal District Court.&#8221;)</p>
<p>Geological Survey of the State.</p>
<p>appropriation for, how to be expended................. 82</p>
<p>appropriation not to exceed $20,000 in any one year.... 82</p>
<p>Geologist, State.</p>
<p>duties of................................81, 82, 83</p>
<p>each assistant of, to be allowed twenty copies of his reports 83</p>
<p>in case of death, etc., Governor may appoint successor.... 83</p>
<p>may be removed, for what....................... 83</p>
<p>salary of.............................. 82</p>
<p>salaries of assistants of............................. 82</p>
<p>to appoint one chemist and one mineralogist as his as<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sistants.................................. 81</p>
<p>to be allowed fifty copies of his own reports............... 83</p>
<p>to be appointed by Governor, by and with advice and con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sent of Senate................................ 81</p>
<p>to enter into bond...................... 81</p>
<p>to present report at each regular session of Legislature... 82</p>
<pb n="447" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="273" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>to superintend publication of his own reports.......... 83</p>
<p>Gillespie County.</p>
<p>Goliad County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Governor (of this State.)</p>
<p>Under Chapter 3.</p>
<p>to order an election for county officers of Rains county... 3</p>
<p>Under Chapter 4.</p>
<p>empowered to issue his proclamation declaring quarantine 3</p>
<p>to appoint a health officer wherever there shall be no town or city corporations on the coast................... 4</p>
<p>Under Chapter 5.</p>
<p>to raise twenty companies of Texas Rangers.............. 5</p>
<p>to appoint Captains........................... 6</p>
<p>to contract for 1500 stand of arms................... 6</p>
<p>special order from, required to discharge an enlisted man. 7</p>
<p>to divide frontier counties into convenient districts...... 7</p>
<p>to designate the ranking officer of each district.............. 7</p>
<p>to nominate commanding officer, in case of campaign against Indians........................... 8</p>
<p>to appoint a paymaster............................ 8</p>
<p>to appoint special agents for the purchase of means of transportation and supplies.................... 8</p>
<p>to disband said companies, when................... 8</p>
<p>Under Chapter 10.</p>
<p>to appoint and commission all general, field, and staff offi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cers of State Guards and Reserve Militia............ 13</p>
<p>to appoint one Adjutant General with rank of Colonel... 13</p>
<p>to appoint a paymaster.......................... 14</p>
<p>to organize the staff departments.................... 14</p>
<p>may designate a uniform........................ 14</p>
<pb n="448" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="274" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>to direct Adjutant General to provide books as a guide to the military forces, and furnish same to the commis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sioned officers............................. 14</p>
<p>to direct the officer to whom payments for commutation are to be made........................... 15</p>
<p>to prescribe all necessary regulations for collecting tax (commutation)............................ 15</p>
<p>may divide State into military divisions.................. 15</p>
<p>empowered to order the military force of this State into active service, when.......................... 16</p>
<p>to declare counties under martial law, when............... 16</p>
<p>laws being suspended, to provide for the trial of offenders 16</p>
<p>Under Chapter 11.</p>
<p>to appoint for each judicial district one District Attorney. 17</p>
<p>to appoint for each county one county treasurer, one county surveyor, hide and cattle inspectors, and (where required) weighers of cotton...................... 17</p>
<p>to appoint in each county where vacancies exist, one sheriff, and one district clerk.................... 17</p>
<p>to appoint for each city, or incorporated town, a mayor, board of aldermen, or officers of like character........</p>
<p>to appoint for Houston and Galveston cities, each, a city recorder.............................. 17</p>
<p>in case of vacancy in any of the offices mentioned in this act, to fill such vacancy by appointment............17, 18</p>
<p>Under Chapter 13.</p>
<p>to appoint a chief of State Police, when there is no Adju<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tant General............................... 19</p>
<p>approval of, required, for removal of any of the members of the State Police.......................... 19</p>
<p>approval of, required, to all needful rules, etc., for govern<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ment of State Police............................ 19</p>
<p>certain officers of counties, cities and towns, subject to supervisory control of....................... 19</p>
<p>to approve rules for the government of these officers.... 20</p>
<p>to approve uniform for State Police.................. 20</p>
<pb n="449" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="275" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Chief of State Police and his subordinates may be detailed by, separately or together..................... 20</p>
<p>to assume command of all or any part of the municipal police of any city or town, etc.................. 20</p>
<p>Under Chapter 16.</p>
<p>to appoint a registrar for each organized county........24-5</p>
<p>to appoint a board of appeals and revision.................. 25</p>
<p>to have supervisory control over all registration......... 31</p>
<p>Under Chapter 26.</p>
<p>to appoint a judge of the Criminal Court, and district at<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />torney for Galveston and Harris counties............. 38</p>
<p>to appoint a clerk of the Criminal Court for each of said counties................................38-9</p>
<p>Under Chapter 27.</p>
<p>to appoint a suitable person as surveyor to superintend running and marking the lines of Cameron, and other counties named............................... 40</p>
<p>Under Chapter 30.</p>
<p>to commission officers for the county of Delta, when elected..................................... 43</p>
<p>Under Chapter 32.</p>
<p>bonds, for expenses of ranging companies, to be issued un<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />der the direction of......................... 45</p>
<p>to direct style and denomination of said bonds.......... 45</p>
<p>made agent of the State to sell said bonds................. 46</p>
<p>to turn over proceeds of sale to State Treasurer........... 46</p>
<p>to order the printing of said bonds................ 46</p>
<p>Under Chapter 47.</p>
<p>to order an election to be held in the county of Hill, and to prescribe rules for the same.................. 63</p>
<pb n="450" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="276" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>to notify the Police Court of Hill county of the result of said election................................ 64</p>
<p>Under Chapter 54.</p>
<p>on breach of State Printer&#8217;s bond, suit to be ordered by the 70</p>
<p>empowered to designate journals to publish county and ju<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />diciary printing............................ 74</p>
<p>Under Chapter 59.</p>
<p>to appoint county officers for San Jacinto county......79, 80</p>
<p>Under Chapter 61.</p>
<p>to appoint State Geologist.................. 81</p>
<p>to procure rooms at the capital of the State for deposit of specimens.................................. 81</p>
<p>to approve vouchers of State Geologist................ 82</p>
<p>to cause State Geologist&#8217;s reports to be printed........... 83</p>
<p>to remove State Geologist for cause................... 83</p>
<p>Under Chapter 63.</p>
<p>to cause railroads, and their franchises, etc., to be sold, for causes specified: to buy in railroads, when............ 85</p>
<p>Under Chapter 65.</p>
<p>to order special election to fill all vacancies in offices of justice of the peace............................ 87</p>
<p>to commission justices of the peace................... 87</p>
<p>Under Chapter 68.</p>
<p>to appoint Superintendent of Public Instruction, by and with advice and consent of Senate................... 113</p>
<p>Under Chapter 78.</p>
<p>to issue writ of election within five days after being offi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cially informed of any vacancy in seat of any senator or representative, provided, etc.................... 131</p>
<pb n="451" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="277" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>to sign certificate of returns of election for representa<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tives in Congress......................... 132</p>
<p>returns of election to be opened in presence of.......... 135</p>
<p>to commission all officers elect, except members of the Leg<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />islature and the Governor.................... 136</p>
<p>in elections for, returns to be made separately and trans<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />mitted, how.............................. 136</p>
<p>to appoint three judges of election, to serve at each city or town election................................ 136</p>
<p>to take all necessary steps to secure a fair election, to have paramount charge of the State, on days of election.... 138</p>
<p>to have supervisory control over all elections, empowered to call out the militia, etc................... 139</p>
<p>Under Chapter 85.</p>
<p>to give notice of sale of Houston Tap and Brazoria Rail<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />way thirty days prior to sale.................. 233</p>
<p>sale to be conducted by, or by his appointee................233-4</p>
<p>to execute and deliver deed of conveyance to purchaser.. 234</p>
<p>to purchase railway, in certain event............... 234</p>
<p>Under Joint Resolution No. 8.</p>
<p>to invite proposals for location of two penitentiaries, and report result to next session of Legislature........... 246</p>
<p>Grayson County.</p>
<p>Grimes County.</p>
<p>Guadalupe County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Guardian.</p>
<p>(of a minor) accounts of................... 192</p>
<p>appointed by District Court.....................141, 184</p>
<p>bond and oath of.....................187-8</p>
<p>compensation of....................... 193</p>
<p>death, resignation, etc., of.............. 188</p>
<p>duties incidental to the right of....................184-5</p>
<p>natural, who...................... 185</p>
<p>not to dispute right of ward to any property that shall have come into his possession as, except, etc.......... 188</p>
<pb n="452" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="278" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>only one bond required, where same person is appointed guardian of person and estate..................... 187</p>
<p>order of appointment of, to specify whether of person or estate, or both........................... 188</p>
<p>parties to proceedings for appointment of, who.......... 186</p>
<p>powers and duties of......................189, 190</p>
<p>proceedings for appointment of, where and how com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />menced......................... 186</p>
<p>requirement of, to give bond, may be negatived by will.. 187</p>
<p>special.......................................... 193 193</p>
<p>term of office............................ 188</p>
<p>where&#8212;and ward reside in another State, course of pro<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ceedings of, with respect to ward&#8217;s property in this State.............................188-9</p>
<p>who cannot be appointed....................... 186</p>
<p>(see minor.)</p>
<p>(of person of unsound mind, or habitual drunkard,) ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />pointment of........................ 194</p>
<p>same person to be appointed, of person and estate......... 194</p>
<p>term of office of............................ 194</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">H.</head>
<p>Hamilton County.</p>
<p>Hardeman County.</p>
<p>Hardin County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Harris County.</p>
<p>(see counties, Criminal District Court.)</p>
<p>Harrison County.</p>
<p>Hays County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Health Officer.</p>
<p>duties of...................................4, 76</p>
<p>fees collected by, to be reported, and used, how.......... 76</p>
<p>when and by whom appointed....................... 3-4</p>
<p>Henderson County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Hill County.</p>
<p>(see counties, Governor.)</p>
<pb n="453" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="279" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Homestead.</p>
<p>duties of persons occupying public land as a.............. 69</p>
<p>exempt from forced sale for debts, except as specified..127, 229</p>
<p>when sold (in cases of partition) proceeds to be held or dis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />posed of by the court....................... 161</p>
<p>who entitled to, and on what conditions............. 68</p>
<p>Hood County.</p>
<p>Hopkins County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>House of Representatives.</p>
<p>who alone competent to organize the, after general election 136</p>
<p>Houston County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Houston Tap and Brazoria Railway.</p>
<p>Governor authorized to purchase, in case sale should not bring one hundred thousand dollars, coin............. 233</p>
<p>place, and terms of sale of...................234-4</p>
<p>proceeds of sale, how to be disposed of................ 234</p>
<p>thirty days&#8217; notice of sale to be given, by publication, etc.. 233</p>
<p>to be sold within ninety days from August 15, 1870...... 233</p>
<p>Hunt County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">I.</head>
<p>Index.</p>
<p>of &#8220;an act for the assessment and collection of taxes,&#8221; ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />proved August 15, 1870, to be made by Comptroller.... 233</p>
<p>of journals of &#8220;House&#8221; and &#8220;Senate&#8221; to be furnished to Public Printer, etc........................... 72</p>
<p>of plaintiffs and defendants in judgments rendered by jus<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tice of the peace, to be made by district clerk, etc...... 98</p>
<p>of laws and resolutions, to be furnished by Secretary of State, to State Printer......................... 71</p>
<pb n="454" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="280" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Indians, (Kickapoos and Lipans.)</p>
<p>joint resolution concerning................... 241</p>
<p>Inspectors of Hides and Cattle.</p>
<p>to be appointed by Governor.................... 17</p>
<p>office of, not lucrative...................... 17</p>
<p>Instrument Requiring Registration.</p>
<p>(see registration.)</p>
<p>Inventory, for taxation.)</p>
<p>to be entered in inventory book, and dated and signed by person rendering the same.................... 213</p>
<p>to be made and signed by justice of the peace, when..... 214</p>
<p>Inventory Book.</p>
<p>to be signed by appraisers, when................... 214</p>
<p>Inventory, (of an estate.)</p>
<p>concerning the...............................158-159</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">J.</head>
<p>Jack County.</p>
<p>Jasper County.</p>
<p>Jefferson County.</p>
<p>Johnson County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Journals, (manuscript) of &#8220;House&#8221; and &#8220;Senate.&#8221;</p>
<p>to be filed with archives of the Legislature.................... 72</p>
<p>to be furnished to Public Printer from day to day, after adoption.................................. 72</p>
<p>Journals, (printed) of &#8220;House&#8221; and &#8220;Senate.&#8221;</p>
<p>to be delivered within sixty days after last copy furnished Public Printer........................ 72</p>
<p>Judges of Election.</p>
<p>boards of appeal and revision, to be also.............. 25</p>
<p>compensation of, in city or town elections............. 137</p>
<p>duties of, in case of riot, etc., at any place at or near poll, etc............................. 132</p>
<p>empowered to administer oaths to persons offering to vote, and to examine them under oath..............130-131</p>
<pb n="455" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="281" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>may appoint two clerks......................... 130</p>
<p>mayor, and city or town council to appoint three, (if Gov<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ernor fail to do so,) at each city or town election......... 136</p>
<p>one of the, to keep the record; another, to receive the votes 130</p>
<p>one of the, to take vote from the hand of voter himself.. 129</p>
<p>penalty on, for placing any other word or mark.......... 131</p>
<p>penalty on, for receiving a vote from the hand of any per<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />son, other than a voter.................. 129</p>
<p>penalty on, for receiving or depositing ballot of any one, whose name does not appear upon list furnished them.. 129</p>
<p>to be free from arrest during election, etc................ 130</p>
<p>to deliver list of voters used by them, to the registrar, after an election......................128, 130</p>
<p>to deposit ballot of each voter in full view of voter himself 129</p>
<p>to keep a list of the names of the persons voting......... 130</p>
<p>to mark as rejected, and keep separate, the ballot of any one, whose name appears on register, as that of one re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />jected as a voter..........................128-129</p>
<p>to preserve order during an election................ 130</p>
<p>to receive the ballots of all legal voters who shall offer to vote................................ 129</p>
<p>vacancies in office of, how filled................... 30</p>
<p>Judges (of the Supreme Court.)</p>
<p>authorized to proceed in the discharge of their functions, till appointments made..................... 10</p>
<p>proceedings, etc., of, prior to reorganization of courts under present constitution, validated................. 9</p>
<p>to adopt rules for the dispatch of business.................. 79</p>
<p>Jurors.</p>
<p>Challenges of, without and for cause................... 94</p>
<p>Jury fees,</p>
<p>in criminal cases, before justices of the peace............. 61</p>
<p>in trials before a justice of the peace, other than for of<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fenses against the laws of this State, what, and how col<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />lected............................. 94</p>
<pb n="456" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="282" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Justices of the Peace.</p>
<p>any person may confess judgment before a, for an amount within his jurisdiction............................ 96</p>
<p>appeals from a, in actions of forcible entry and detainer.. 89</p>
<p>appeals from a, in cases of misdemeanor............... 107</p>
<p>appeals from a, to District Court.................. 98</p>
<p>application for new trial before a, when to be made..... 96</p>
<p>appropriation to pay fees of, in criminal prosecutions.... 125</p>
<p>challenges in trials before a, without and for cause...... 94</p>
<p>citation, when issued by, in civil cases.............. 91</p>
<p>commissioned by Governor, to act as justices and as nota<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ries public........................ 87</p>
<p>continuance, in cases before a......................91, 96, 97</p>
<p>disqualified from sitting, when interested in a suit...... 100</p>
<p>distress warrant for rent, when issuable by a, and on what conditions.....................103, 104</p>
<p>duty of, before whom complaint is made of an offense com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />mitted in another county..................... 107</p>
<p>duty of, on receiving writ of certiorari................ 99</p>
<p>to demand books and papers of his predecessor........... 90</p>
<p>to keep a docket, its contents.................. 89</p>
<p>to keep a fee book........................... 102</p>
<p>to proceed with unfinished business of his predecessor, on receipt of books and papers.................... 90</p>
<p>to take scholastic census, annually................... 116</p>
<p>to turn over books and papers to his successor............ 89</p>
<p>duty of, where defendant is brought before him under chap. 65, sec. 17, General Laws of 1870............. 106</p>
<p>elected and duly qualified, to enter upon his duties under existing laws............................ 241</p>
<p>election, and term of office of................... 87</p>
<p>evidence of a female, etc., in trials before a, how procured 95</p>
<p>evidence, rules of, in trials before a................ 96</p>
<p>execution issued by a, when returnable................ 99</p>
<p>execution issued by a, where judgment is for money, not returnable before eleventh day after judgment, except in what cases........................... 99</p>
<p>fees of a, when acting as a member of board of school directors............................ 114</p>
<p>fees of jurors in criminal trials before a, what and how collected......................... 61</p>
<pb n="457" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="283" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>fees of jurors in trials before a, other than for offenses against the laws of this State, what and how collected.. 94</p>
<p>fees of jurors, to be taxed by...................... 61</p>
<p>fees of jurors, to be paid over to county treasurer........ 61</p>
<p>fees of witnesses, in trials before a................... 94</p>
<p>final judgment against parties to any bail bond, etc., not to be entered by a, till when.................. 87</p>
<p>free trials before a, when and on what conditions.........99, 100</p>
<p>in case of vacancy in office of, any justice of the peace of the county can hold his court................. 100</p>
<p>Justice of the Peace is Empowered,</p>
<p>to appoint a deputy............... 107</p>
<p>to award writs of restitution................... 89</p>
<p>to charge ten cents for certificate to juror, in what cases.. 61</p>
<p>to discharge all duties of coroner, except such as devolve on constables............................... 104</p>
<p>to enforce liens on personal property, when.............. 87</p>
<p>to grant stay of execution..................... 99</p>
<p>to impose fines on defaulting jurors and witnesses, not ex<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ceeding $25................................ 87</p>
<p>to issue subpoenas, and enforce attendance of witnesses.. 94</p>
<p>to issue writs of attachment, sequestration and garnish<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ment........................... 100</p>
<p>to solemnize matrimony...................... 104</p>
<p>to take acknowledgment of deeds.................. 104</p>
<p>to take depositions in any suit pending in this State..... 104</p>
<p>to take forfeiture of bail bonds, in cases specified, (sub<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ject to proviso as to final judgment).................. 87</p>
<p>Justice of the Peace.</p>
<p>judgment and final orders of a, to be given in open court. 96</p>
<p>judgment may be confessed before a, without issuance of citation................................... 96</p>
<p>judgment rendered by a, to operate as a lien on real estate, when.............................. 98</p>
<p>judgment rendered by a, to be recorded by district clerk, in book used for record of mortgages.............. 98</p>
<p>juries, in trials before a, to be composed of six men...... 94</p>
<pb n="458" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="284" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Justice of the Peace, jurisdiction of.</p>
<p>a justice of the peace has jurisdiction, (where the matter in controversy, value of specific articles, penalty, fine, or forfeiture does not, or the damages claimed do not ex<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ceed one hundred dollars.)</p>
<p>in all actions on behalf of the State, or of any county there<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />of, or of any individual, to recover penalties, fines and forfeitures............................... 87</p>
<p>in all actions in behalf of the State, or any county thereof, for any violation of the revenue law of this State...... 87</p>
<p>in all actions for recovery of money on any account, bill, bond, rents, note, or other instrument of writing...... 87</p>
<p>in all actions for the recovery of specific articles, or the value thereof.......................... 87</p>
<p>in all actions for torts, trespasses, and other injuries to per<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />son or property........................ 87</p>
<p>a justice of the peace has jurisdiction, over all cases of forcible entry in lands, tenements, or other real prop<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />erty..................................... 88</p>
<p>over all other matters that may be cognizable before a jus<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tice of the peace, under the laws of this State........ 88</p>
<p>may be removed for cause..................205, 206</p>
<p>new trials before a, when granted.................... 96</p>
<p>oath to be administered to jurors, in trials before a...... 94</p>
<p>parties to a suit before a, entitled to change of venue, when............................... 91</p>
<p>penalty on any one refusing to deliver up books and papers of a................................89, 90</p>
<p>penalty on juror refusing to attend, when summoned by a.......................................93, 94</p>
<p>person applying to a, for distress warrant for rent, to make oath that it is not sued out for vexatious purposes..103, 104</p>
<p>pleadings before a, oral, except in certain cases........ 93</p>
<p>proceedings before a, in cases of forcible entry and de<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tainer..........................88, 89</p>
<p>proceedings by a, or jury, after suit for recovery of specific articles........................... 97</p>
<p>proceedings by a, where defendant, served with citation, neglects or refuses to appear...................96, 97</p>
<p>process from a.......................91, 92</p>
<p>remedy of landlord before a, where rent is due, or tenant about to remove..................... 103</p>
<pb n="459" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="285" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>stay of execution granted by a, not to prevent taking out writ of certiorari.......................... 99</p>
<p>suits before a, where commenced...................90, 91</p>
<p>terms of court of, when held...................... 100</p>
<p>terms of court of, resident at county seat, when held..... 100</p>
<p>vacancies in office of, how filled..............87, 205, 206</p>
<p>Justice of the Peace as Assessor of Taxes.</p>
<p>answers to questions of, to be under oath............. 216</p>
<p>appraisers may be chosen by, and persons rendering prop<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />erty.......................... 214</p>
<p>certificate of district clerk to be issued to, for fees and com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />missions.............................. 221</p>
<p>commission of, for assessing..................... 221</p>
<p>commission of, to be denied, unless all duties are properly performed........................... 221</p>
<p>compensation of, for making books for former years..221, 222</p>
<p>compensation of, when, and how apportioned............ 222</p>
<p>costs may be awarded against, for erroneous assessment.. 223</p>
<p>differences in settlement between, and district clerk, to be determined by district attorney.................... 218</p>
<p>&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;, dissatisfied with valuation of person rendering, may adopt his own valuation; consequent con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />troversy, if any, to be decided under section thirty<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />nine, (pp. 213, 214)...................... 216</p>
<p>evidence of record required, to entitle&#8212;to transfer to an<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />other, land correctly charged to one person........... 208</p>
<p>fee of, for summons......................... 214</p>
<p>fees of, under sections sixteen, twenty-one and sixty-eight of chapter eighty-four, General Laws of 1870, what, and how paid..........................220, 221</p>
<p>in suit aginst person refusing to render, shall attend as a witness................................ 214</p>
<p>instructions of Comptroller binding on............... 221</p>
<p>list of lands partitioned and devised to be furnished by district clerk to........................ 207</p>
<p>may be removed for cause.......................205, 206</p>
<p>may be required to give new bond.................. 205</p>
<p>may employ assistant at his own expense............... 205</p>
<p>oath to be taken by......................... 204</p>
<p>penalty on, for charging less than lawful tax.......... 219</p>
<pb n="460" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="286" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>penalty on, for failing to administer oath.............. 216</p>
<p>penalty on, for failing to make copies of books.......... 218</p>
<p>penalty on, for failing to perform duties under section fifty-three, (p. 218)............................ 220</p>
<p>penalty on, for failing to report his own property, etc.... 217</p>
<p>penalty on, for making false entry................... 219</p>
<p>penalty on, for refusing to surrender books, etc., to suc<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cessor.................... 205</p>
<p>per centage of, for making out inventory for delinquents, and claim for per centage, how supported............. 214</p>
<p>person absent when&#8212;calls, need not include valuation in his statements, in which case justice of the peace shall value.....................215, 216</p>
<p>shall act under section forty, (p. 214,) if a person desiring forms to be furnished him, or absent, should fail to make out lists and statements..................... 215</p>
<p>shall assess value of any old building omitted, and of new building, if fit for use, and of addition to a building, if it increases value to one hundred dollars or upward...... 209</p>
<p>shall assess value of property for person requiring it, on presentation of forms...................... 215</p>
<p>shall assist, at examination of his books, by district clerk. 218</p>
<p>shall assist persons rendering land, in giving correct de<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />scriptions thereof......................... 213</p>
<p>shall be assessor of taxes in his precinct................. 204</p>
<p>shall call on every person in his precinct, etc............. 205</p>
<p>shall charge interest on tax previously omitted......... 216</p>
<p>shall commence, on first of January, to ascertain persons and property in his district, subject to taxes, on that day 216</p>
<p>shall correct mistakes of former justices (assessors)...... 208</p>
<p>shall endeavor to have full statements in his lists of, what. 216</p>
<p>shall furnish blank forms for rendition of property..... 215</p>
<p>shall furnish district attorney with statements of viola<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tions of revenue laws................. 223</p>
<p>shall give bond, nature of.................... 204</p>
<p>shall include machinery and fixtures in valuation of mills, etc........................................ 209</p>
<p>shall leave proper forms of statements and oaths at resi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dence of person absent when he calls.................. 215</p>
<pb n="461" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="287" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>shall make a book containing names of persons taxed, and subjects of taxation......................216, 217</p>
<p>shall make books of land tax and personal property tax, for former years, if necessary. Proceedings with re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />spect to............................. 217</p>
<p>shall make entry and assessment of land omitted from reg<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ister.......................208, 209</p>
<p>shall make out inventory, in case of refusal of any person to render, and for this purpose shall have right of entry into any building other than the dwelling........... 214</p>
<p>shall make report, on oath, of his own property, enter same, and taxes charged, on his books............ 217</p>
<p>shall make two copies of land and personal property books; oaths to be appended thereto................. 217</p>
<p>shall retain original of each book, and deliver both copies of each to district clerk, etc.................217, 218</p>
<p>shall settle his accounts annually, with District Court.... 221</p>
<p>shall value property at its specie value on the first of Janu<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ary preceding the assessment................ 214</p>
<p>to be furnished by Comptroller with printed forms for land register and property books, etc..............205, 206</p>
<p>when assessing, shall take with him register of preceding year, etc......................... 209</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">K.</head>
<p>Karnes County.</p>
<p>Kaufman County.</p>
<p>Kendall County.</p>
<p>Kerr County.</p>
<p>Kimball County.</p>
<p>Kinney County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">L.</head>
<p>Lamar County.</p>
<p>Lampasas County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Land Certificates.</p>
<p>holders of, required to locate, etc., by January 1, 1875.. 69</p>
<p>may be located for homestead purposes................ 69</p>
<pb n="462" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="288" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Landed Property.</p>
<p>sales of, under decrees of courts, how to be made....... 78</p>
<p>Landlord.</p>
<p>may stipulate as to lien, by contract in writing, put upon record............................................. 104</p>
<p>not to have preference over other creditors, except on crop raised on rented premises................................ 103</p>
<p>remedy of, where rent is due, or tenant about, to remove his person or property...............................102-103</p>
<p>Lands.</p>
<p>claims for, against the State, between Nueces river and Rio Grande, how to be adjudicated..................201, 204</p>
<p>Larbaletrier, Charles.</p>
<p>pension of......................................... 123</p>
<p>Lavaca County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Legislature.</p>
<p>time of annual meetings of the, prescribed................ 35</p>
<p>(present,) to make appropriations necessary to enable Ex<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ecutive to carry out provisions of chapter five, General Laws of 1870.......................................... 8</p>
<p>Leon County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Laws, (of the State.)</p>
<p>how to be printed; quality of paper, etc................... 71-72</p>
<p>when printed, to be delivered at office of Secretary of State 72</p>
<p>Letters of Administration.</p>
<p>application for, by whom and how commenced............ 155</p>
<p>application for, when made by a creditor, how defeated.. 155</p>
<p>application for, when made by a person not interested, how defeated................................... 155</p>
<p>consist of, what................................. 156</p>
<p>evidence required before grant of.......................... 156</p>
<p>one creditor may apply for, in behalf of all................ 155</p>
<pb n="463" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="289" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Letters Testamentary.</p>
<p>consist of, what..................................... 124</p>
<p>evidence required before grant of........................ 153</p>
<p>to whom granted................................. 154</p>
<p>Licenses.</p>
<p>see tax (occupation.)</p>
<p>Liberty County.</p>
<p>Live Oak County.</p>
<p>Limestone County.</p>
<p>Llano County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">M.</head>
<p>McDonald, John.</p>
<p>pension of........................................ 123</p>
<p>McLennan County.</p>
<p>McMullen County.</p>
<p>Madison County.</p>
<p>Marion County.</p>
<p>Mason County.</p>
<p>Matagorda County.</p>
<p>Maverick County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Mayor.</p>
<p>one to be appointed by Governor for each incorporated city and town................................... 17</p>
<p>to be a qualified elector, and to qualify within ten days after notice of appointment.................................. 18</p>
<p>to be returning officer (with registrar) in city or town elec<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion................................................... 137</p>
<p>Medina County.</p>
<p>Menard County.</p>
<p>Milam County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Military Duty.</p>
<p>who subject to.......................................... 11</p>
<p>Military Forces (of this State.)</p>
<p>of whom to consist....................................... 12</p>
<p>GL&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;19</p>
<pb n="464" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="290" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Militia (Reserve).</p>
<p>compensation of, when called into service............. 16</p>
<p>discipline and tactics of................................ 14</p>
<p>expense of maintaining, in counties under martial law.... 16</p>
<p>fines imposed on, now disposed of........................ 15</p>
<p>how governed.................................... 13</p>
<p>may be organized, how.................................</p>
<p>of whom to consist............................... 12</p>
<p>persons may avoid service in, how............................... 15</p>
<p>subject to detail, same as State Guard...................... 15</p>
<p>uniform of, may be designated by Governor.............. 14</p>
<p>Minor.</p>
<p>claims for money against estate of........................ 191</p>
<p>definition of................................... 184</p>
<p>education of.................................... 185, 191</p>
<p>guardianship of......................................... 185-193</p>
<p>special guardian of................................... 193</p>
<p>(see guardian.)</p>
<p>Montague County.</p>
<p>Montgomery County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Morris, Thomas.</p>
<p>pension of................................... 123</p>
<p>Municipal Police (of Cities and Towns).</p>
<p>Governor may assume command of, when................ 20</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">N.</head>
<p>Navarro County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Newspaper.</p>
<p>advertising sales under an order of court, to hold first mortgage on property sold, until paid............... 74</p>
<p>Newton County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Nichols, J. W.</p>
<p>pension of.................................... 123</p>
<pb n="465" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="291" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Nueces County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">O.</head>
<p>Occupation Tax.</p>
<p>on whom to be levied.......................... 199, 200</p>
<p>see tax (occupation.)</p>
<p>Officers Elect.</p>
<p>to enter upon the discharge of their duties, under laws now existing............................................. 241</p>
<p>Officers.</p>
<p>appointed by the Governor, to be qualified electors, and otherwise eligible.................................. 18</p>
<p>Official Journal (of the State).</p>
<p>what.......................................................... 70</p>
<p>Overseers of Roads.</p>
<p>appointment, duties, and pay of............................... 44</p>
<p>bond of....................................................... 45</p>
<p>Palo Pinto County.</p>
<p>Panola County.</p>
<p>Parker County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Pass Cavallo Bar</p>
<p>improvements of........................................243&#8212;244</p>
<p>Peace Officer.</p>
<p>penalty on a, for refusing to execute justice&#8217;s warrant.... 106</p>
<p>Pensions.</p>
<p>to veterans of the revolution which separated Texas from Mexico.......................................... 118</p>
<p>Police.</p>
<p>(see State Police, Municipal Police.)</p>
<pb n="466" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="292" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Presiding Justice of Police Court.</p>
<p>to report annually to Superintendent of Public Instruc<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion, what...................................... 115</p>
<p>compensation of for services under chapter sixty-eight, section four, General Laws of 1870................... 115</p>
<p>Presiding Justices of Counties.</p>
<p>certain powers formerly conferred on chief justices of coun<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ties, transferred to.....................................124&#8212;125</p>
<p>Police Courts</p>
<p>authorized to levy special tax to pay off outstanding in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />debtedness............................................33-34</p>
<p>authorized to levy special tax to repair roads and bridges.. 47</p>
<p>one-half of the amount of taxes authorized, by &#8220;An Act to levy taxes,&#8221; approved August 15, 1870, may be levied by, except, etc......................................... 201</p>
<p>Poll Tax.</p>
<p>(see capitation tax.)</p>
<p>Presidio County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Printer (State).</p>
<p>(see State Printer.)</p>
<p>Printing (Public).</p>
<p>bills and resolutions, how printed, how many copies of, etc. 73</p>
<p>price of rule and figure work.......................... 73</p>
<p>rates of pay for printing and advertising, whether State, judicial or otherwise, under chapter fifty-four General Laws of 1870, (sections six and thirteen)................73-74</p>
<p>rates of pay for, of laws, journals, Governor&#8217;s message, re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ports, bills, resolutions, etc............................. 73</p>
<p>(see appropriations.)</p>
<p>Process.</p>
<p>from a justice of the peace, to be under his hand............ 91</p>
<p>returnable, when......................................... 91</p>
<p>served, how........................................ 91</p>
<p>served, how, in suits against private corporations............. 91</p>
<p>to whom directed...................................... 91</p>
<pb n="467" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="293" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Property.</p>
<p>exempt from forced sale for debts, what......................... 127</p>
<p>valuation of, for assessment of ad valorem tax to be made in specie........................................... 201</p>
<p>Provisional District Judges.</p>
<p>Comptroller directed to audit and pay salaries of, subject to provisos......................................... 245</p>
<p>Provisional Government.</p>
<p>officers of, to be paid in full.................................. 32</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">Q.</head>
<p>Quarantine.</p>
<p>duties of corporate authorities, after declaration of....... 3</p>
<p>duties of corporate authorities, after cessation of........... 75</p>
<p>Governor empowered to declare........................... 3</p>
<p>Quarantine Station.</p>
<p>fees to be collected from vessels arriving at.................. 76</p>
<p>penalty on vessels arriving at, from an infected port, with<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />out clean bill of health............................... 75</p>
<p>Quarantine Vessel.</p>
<p>penalty on person going ashore from a, without permission 76</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">R.</head>
<p>Rains County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Railroad Companies.</p>
<p>indebted to the State for loans from the special school fund, may avoid sale of their road, how............. 85</p>
<p>penalty for non-compliance.............................. 85</p>
<p>payment of principal not to be required of any, not here<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />after in default, except on account of sinking fund.... 86</p>
<p>State lien, already attached, not to attach to any extension of existing road, hereafter constructed................... 86</p>
<pb n="468" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="294" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>to advertise in legal advertising mediums of every judicial district through which they pass, correct schedules of hours of arrival and departure of all regular trains, and all rates of passage and freight.................... 75</p>
<p>Rangers.</p>
<p>(see Texas Rangers.)</p>
<p>Recorder.</p>
<p>for each of the cities of Galveston, and Houston, to be ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />pointed by the Governor................................ 17</p>
<p>other recorders to be elected.................................. 17</p>
<p>Red River County.</p>
<p>Refugio County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Registrar.</p>
<p>books, etc., for, to be furnished by Secretary of State.... 25</p>
<p>duty of, on receipt of writ of election........................ 131</p>
<p>each county to provide rooms, etc., for..................... 25</p>
<p>free from arrest during registration, etc................... 30</p>
<p>in each county, to supervise the holding of all city, town and charter elections..................................... 136</p>
<p>judges of election to deliver list of voters used by them, to 28</p>
<p>list furnished by, to board of appeals, to be alphabetically arranged.................................................. 27</p>
<p>list of persons registered by Secretary of State, to be fur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />nished to................................................. 30</p>
<p>list of registered voters to be furnished to each, by Secre<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tary of State............................................. 25</p>
<p>office hours of....................................... 25</p>
<p>office of, not deemed lucrative............................. 30</p>
<p>one, to be appointed by the Governor for each organized county.............................................. 24</p>
<p>penalty on a, for knowingly entering on register names of persons not entitled to registration..................... 29</p>
<p>penalty on a, for refusing to deliver list to board of appeals penalty on any one resisting or impeding a..................29, 31.</p>
<p>persons not entitled to registration, but who can prove that they will be so on or before next ensuing election, to have their names entered by............................ 25</p>
<pb n="469" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="295" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>powers of........................................................ 25, 26</p>
<p>term of office of................................................ 24</p>
<p>to apply to district clerk for registration books, and to cer<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tify additional names registered by him, to judges of election.............................................. 28</p>
<p>to be appointed at least sixty days prior to each general election............................................... 25</p>
<p>to begin registration when, and continue, how long....... 25</p>
<p>to deposit registry book with district clerk, when........... 27</p>
<p>to give ten days&#8217; notice of time and places of his session... 25</p>
<p>to have powers of judge of District Court................... 28</p>
<p>to issue transfers to registered voters, when.................. 28</p>
<p>to make, duplicate copies of list of registered voters, etc., one for board of appeals and one for Secretary of State. 31</p>
<p>to make two fair copies of list of registered voters, upon conclusion of registration, and deposit them with dis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />trict clerk............................................... 27</p>
<p>to post up copies of &#8220;An Act to provide for the registration of voters.&#8221; approved July 11, 1870, when and where... 31</p>
<p>to receive twenty-five cents for each person registered.... 29</p>
<p>to take oath of office..................................... 25</p>
<p>Registration, (Instruments Requiring.)</p>
<p>that have been acknowledged or proved before and certi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fied by county judge, shall be held to have been duly ac<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />knowledged or proved................................ 77</p>
<p>(instruments requiring,) and which have been registered, etc., shall be held to have been duly registered.......... 77</p>
<p>Registration.</p>
<p>appropriation to defray expenses of next revision of....... 31</p>
<p>books of, to be kept among records of District Court.... 28</p>
<p>(of citizens,) how, when, and where effected.................. 24, 30</p>
<p>(of voters,) under late provisional government, declared valid, but subject to revision......................... 24</p>
<p>Returning Officers.</p>
<p>duties of, in compiling returns after an election............. 135</p>
<p>who, in city or town elections........................... 137</p>
<pb n="470" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="296" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Roads and Bridges.</p>
<p>special tax authorized for improvement of................... 44</p>
<p>Robertson County.</p>
<p>Rusk County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">S.</head>
<p>Sabine County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Sabine Pass.</p>
<p>improvement of bar of.............................. 243-4</p>
<p>San Jacinto County.</p>
<p>San Patricio County.</p>
<p>San Saba County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>School Directors, Board of.</p>
<p>fees or per diem pay of members of....................... 115</p>
<p>may make separation of students or school................... 114</p>
<p>may remove teachers or expel students....................... 114</p>
<p>of whom to consist..................................... 114</p>
<p>shall discharge their duties faithfully............................ 115</p>
<p>shall make rules, regulations and by-laws for government of schools............................................. 115</p>
<p>to appoint school examiners.............................. 114</p>
<p>to appoint school trustees................................. 114</p>
<p>to be subject to the rules, etc., of the Superintendent of Public Instruction..................................... 115</p>
<p>to divide counties into sub-districts.................... 114</p>
<p>to levy an ad valorem tax, for building school houses, when necessary...................................... 114</p>
<p>to locate school houses.................................. 114</p>
<p>to require parents and guardians to send their children and wards to public school, except, etc........................ 114</p>
<p>to settle difficulties arising in public free schools......... 114</p>
<p>School District.</p>
<p>each, county to be a......................................... 114</p>
<p>School Fund.</p>
<p>available, of what to consist................................. 118</p>
<pb n="471" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="297" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>available, to be applied exclusively to what................... 118</p>
<p>permanent, of what to consist............................. 117, 118</p>
<p>permanent, to be converted into United States bonds.... 118</p>
<p>Schools, Free Public.</p>
<p>subjects of education in.................................... 117</p>
<p>to be taught four mouths in the year, or longer, under cer<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tain circumstances...................................... 117</p>
<p>School Trustees.</p>
<p>appointed annually by board of school directors....... 114, 116</p>
<p>duties and powers of...................................... 115, 116</p>
<p>difficulties arising in schools to be reported by, to board of school directors......................................... 114</p>
<p>each board of, to consist of three persons................. 114</p>
<p>may be removed, for cause................................. 116</p>
<p>one board of, at least, to be appointed in each county..... 114</p>
<p>Secretary of State.</p>
<p>actual expenses of, while superintending publication of the laws, (if printed away from seat of government) to be paid out of appropriation for printing.................72, 73</p>
<p>appropriation for salary of............................... 120</p>
<p>certificate of returns of election for representatives in Con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />gress, to be entered on record by, and one copy, sub<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />scribed by, and Governor, to be delivered to person so elected, and another transmitted to House of Represen<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tatives of Congress of United States................ 132</p>
<p>compensation of, for registering......................... 30</p>
<p>may employ clerks to compile election returns, their time, pay, etc................................................ 136</p>
<p>may register qualified voters, till when.................... 30</p>
<p>to cause copies of all laws and resolutions to be furnished to the Public Printer, and to furnish index of the same. 71</p>
<p>to cause copies of State official journal, containing laws, etc., to be sent to the judges and clerks of courts....70, 71</p>
<p>to certify, that the laws published by Public Printer, are true copies of the originals in his office, and the date upon which the Legislature adjourned..................... 72</p>
<p>to furnish list of voters of each county, to county regis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />trar............................................... 25</p>
<pb n="472" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="298" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>to furnish necessary books, etc., to each registrar......... 25</p>
<p>to furnish printed blanks and instructions to all boards of election.............................................. 137</p>
<p>to furnish, registrars with a sufficient number of copies of &#8220;An Act to provide for the registration of voters,&#8221; ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />proved July 11, 1870.................................... 31</p>
<p>to furnish to all boards of election, printed blanks, etc.. 137</p>
<p>to make tabular returns of the votes given for candidates, and publish them in official State journal.............. 135</p>
<p>to send to each member of the Legislature one copy of the general, and one of the special laws, and one of the journals of each &#8220;House&#8221;................................. 71</p>
<p>to superintend, printing of the laws, and read and correct the proof............................................... 72</p>
<p>to transmit to Secretary of the Senate and Clerk of the House of Representatives of the last Legislature, a list of Senators and Representatives elect.................. 136</p>
<p>what reports, and how many, to be printed under the supervision of.................................. 71</p>
<p>Secretary of the Senate.</p>
<p>to cause Senate journal to be furnished to State Printer from day to day, after its adoption................... 72</p>
<p>to furnish index of the same............................ 72</p>
<p>to place list of Senators elect, as received from the Sec<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />retary of State, on roll of the Senate................... 136</p>
<p>Senate.</p>
<p>who alone competent to organize the, after a general elec<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion.................................................... 136</p>
<p>Settlers, (Future.)</p>
<p>may purchase one hundred and sixty acres of land at one dollar per acre..................................... 69</p>
<p>Settlers, (Present.)</p>
<p>may take steps, within twelve months, to appropriate one hundred and sixty acres (in case of the head of a family) and eighty acres (in that of a single man) to a home<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />stead, without pay, except fees........................ 69</p>
<p>Shackleford County.</p>
<p>Shelby County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<pb n="473" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="299" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Sheriff.</p>
<p>authorized to pay district clerks............................... 222</p>
<p>authorized to pay justices of the peace..................... 221</p>
<p>bond of deputy, available to heirs of sheriff.............. 226</p>
<p>(bond of, as collector of county taxes......................... 225</p>
<p>bond of, as collector of State taxes...................... 224</p>
<p>books, and other data, to be delivered by district clerk to. 219</p>
<p>compensation of.......................................... 232&#8212;3</p>
<p>deed of, for land sold for taxes, shall be prima facie evi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dence of compliance with requirements of chapter eighty-four, General Laws of 1870........................ 229</p>
<p>deed of, for land sold for taxes, shall, when recorded, con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fer absolute and complete title, and have force and effect of deed in fee simple..................................... 229</p>
<p>duty of, towards persons engaging in any taxable occupa<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion, without prepayment of tax........................ 232</p>
<p>duty of, if property seized for taxes is not sold at the time first appointed.............................................. 229</p>
<p>failure of, to advertise, or fill his appointment, not to excuse persons for non-payment of taxes............................... 226</p>
<p>fee of, for distraining personal property for taxes........ 228</p>
<p>fee of, for making deed of land sold for taxes............... 229</p>
<p>fees of, for attending justices&#8217; court, to be taxed by jus<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tice......................................................107&#8212;8</p>
<p>instructions of Comptroller binding on.................... 221</p>
<p>judgment against defaulting, to be entered up by district clerk of Travis county................................. 231</p>
<p>list of taxes paid to Comptroller, to be transmitted to..... 230</p>
<p>may appoint deputies...................................... 225</p>
<p>may be removed for cause; consequent vacancy in office of, how filled.............................................224&#8212;5</p>
<p>may be required to give new bond, when..................... 224</p>
<p>not to enter upon his duties until commissioned.............. 225</p>
<p>oath of, as collector................................... 224</p>
<p>one in each county, where vacancies exist, to be appointed by Governor.............................................. 17</p>
<p>or deputy, shall call on every one in his county, demand payment of taxes, and leave written demand on those absent when he calls.............................. 226</p>
<p>order of court to restrain, from collecting taxes erroneously charged................................................. 223</p>
<p>payment of occupation tax to be made to, but not to be re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ceived for a less period than four months................. 232</p>
<pb n="474" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="300" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>penalty on, for extortion.................................. 227</p>
<p>penalty on, for refusing to deliver books, etc., to his suc<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cessor.................................................... 225</p>
<p>personal property, exempt from execution in other cases, may be sold by, for taxes......................... 229</p>
<p>personal property, sold and bid in by, for the State, may be afterwards sold by direction of Comptroller, and shall not be subject to redemption........................... 229</p>
<p>property of, to be bound by statutory lien, for three years from, when.............................................. 224</p>
<p>responsibility of, not impaired by death, removal, etc..... 226</p>
<p>stall administer oath to person paying occupation tax.... 232</p>
<p>shall ascertain from data specified, the lands and city and town lots on which taxes have not been paid, and the personal property not rendered for the current year, and shall describe them, in the manner specified, on a gen<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />eral list, and shall transcribe from this list, on separate lists, the property in each precinct rendered and unrend<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ered, and shall post, in at least three public places in each precinct, copies of the list of property pertaining to such precinct, and shall cite the owners to appear before District Court within twenty days from date of notice, and show cause why it should not be sold for taxes due...........................................227&#8212;8</p>
<p>shall add ten per cent to taxes of persons failing to pay within ten days after times specified in first notice, and notify them through the post office of taxes and penalty owning, and of the intended seizure of their personal property within ten days from date of mailing notice.. 228</p>
<p>shall, if taxes, etc., are not paid at the expiration of the time specified in second notice, seize the personal prop<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />erty, and leave notice at place of distraint, of property seized, and of time and place of sale thereof; time to be not less than ten days from date of service............. 228</p>
<p>shall sell personal property to highest bidder, at expira<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion of time specfied in third notice, subject to proviso for redemption, prior to sale.......................... 228</p>
<p>shall make additional levies and sales till taxes, penalties and costs are satisfied, if personal property first seized proved insufficient.................................... 228</p>
<pb n="475" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="301" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>shall sell the whole of the personal property seized for taxes, if indivisible, and pay surplus to owner, or into treasury to his credit................................ 228</p>
<p>shall bid in personal property for the State, and issue cer<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tificate of purchase therefor, if it cannot be sold for want of bidders............................................... 229</p>
<p>shall be allowed credit by County Court, for amount of county taxes, and by Comptroller, for amount of State taxes, due by insolvents............................ 230</p>
<p>shall be furnished by Comptroller with necessary blanks.. 221</p>
<p>shall be responsible for acts of his deputies................. 225</p>
<p>shall distrain on property about to be removed from county, without prepayment of taxes due.............. 230</p>
<p>shall forward to Comptroller tri-monthly statements of State taxes collected by him........................... 231</p>
<p>shall forward to county treasurer tri-monthly statements of county taxes collected by him....................... 231</p>
<p>shall honor Comptroller&#8217;s drafts, when in funds............. 231</p>
<p>shall issue summons of garnishment to debtors of delin<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />quents taxed, etc.................................. 229</p>
<p>shall keep marginal duplicates of receipts, for settlement with Comptroller....................................... 227</p>
<p>shall make out lists of persons whose taxes are not paid, and who have no property whereon to levy............. 230</p>
<p>shall make out on Comptroller&#8217;s blanks, sign and deliver receipts for taxes............................................. 226</p>
<p>shall order land sold for taxes to be surveyed by county surveyor, and shall issue deed for same to purchaser, upon payment of charges for surveying and fee of three dollars.............................................. 229</p>
<p>shall pay over, annually, to Comptroller, on or before De<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cember first, all moneys collected by him for State taxes. 231</p>
<p>shall pay over, annually, to county treasurer, on or before December first, all moneys collected by him for county taxes............................................... 231</p>
<p>shall post notices of the days when he will be at the county seat, to collect taxes.................................... 226</p>
<p>shall proceed, not later than November first, in each year, to settle his accounts with Comptroller................... 231</p>
<pb n="476" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="302" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>shall receive payment of taxes on any part of a lot, etc., on being furnished with a particular specification there<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />of, or with the name of the owner, in case of an undi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />vided share........................................... 230</p>
<p>shall, with his sureties, be liable to be sued, on their bond, (for malfeasance, etc.,) in District Court of Trayis county.............................................. 231</p>
<p>to collect taxes in accordance with existing laws, in coun<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ties where there are no collectors...................... 244</p>
<p>Smith County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Speaker of the House of Representatives.</p>
<p>further compensation of, fixed......................... 140-141</p>
<p>Stamp, Jno. S.</p>
<p>pension of.......................................... 123</p>
<p>Starr County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>State Guard.</p>
<p>conditions, as to arms and equipments of................... 12</p>
<p>discipline and tactics of................................. 14</p>
<p>expense of maintaining, in counties under martial law.... 16</p>
<p>fines, etc., on, how disposed of............................. 15</p>
<p>how governed, in actual service, etc........................... 13</p>
<p>how organized........................................12-13</p>
<p>of whom to be composed..................................... 12</p>
<p>uniform, horse and equipments of, tree from distresses, sales, etc.......................................... 12</p>
<p>uniform of, may be designated by Governor................... 14</p>
<p>State Police,</p>
<p>composition of.......................................... 19</p>
<p>district judge may call on, to enable him to suppress com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />binations, etc.....................................20-21</p>
<p>entitled to reward, when offered by Governor, but not to rewards from private persons, etc., unless by consent of Governor............................................. 20</p>
<p>may be detailed separately or together........................ 20</p>
<p>may be removed for cause............................ 19</p>
<pb n="477" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="303" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>pay of officers and men................................ 19</p>
<p>rules and regulations for, by whom to be made.............. 19</p>
<p>shall be invested with the authority of peace officers...... 20</p>
<p>shall obey Governors orders................................ 20</p>
<p>shall receive same mileage and other compensation, for transporting prisoners, as sheriffs.................... 19</p>
<p>term of office of.................................. 19</p>
<p>to provide themselves with one horse, and prescribed arms, ammunition and equipments............................. 19</p>
<p>uniform may be prescribed for........................... 20</p>
<p>State Treasurer.</p>
<p>may authorize collection of taxes to pay the whole or a part of the taxes collected for school purposes to county treasurer.............................................. 116</p>
<p>required to invest sinking fund set apart for payment of State bonds issued to defray expenses of ranging com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />panies, in United States interest-bearing bonds, etc.... 46</p>
<p>required to pay accounts of district attorneys appointed by district judges, or Commanding General Fifth Military District, for the time being............................. 41</p>
<p>shall keep a record of the number of children of scholastic age in each county of the State, and a correct account of the school fund due the several counties............... 116</p>
<p>shall report, annually, to the Governor, condition of school fund, and distributions made to the several counties........................................... 116</p>
<p>State Treasury.</p>
<p>distribution of moneys in the, due to counties, provided for................................................. 9</p>
<p>Superintendent of Public Instruction.</p>
<p>duties of............................................. 113-4</p>
<p>may hire clerk, if required................................. 117</p>
<p>office of, to be kept, where.............................. 113</p>
<p>salary of clerk of.................................... 117</p>
<p>salary of, to be paid quarterly............................. 117</p>
<p>term of office, and salary of................................. 113</p>
<p>to be appointed by Governor till next general election.... 113</p>
<p>to be elected, at first general election........................... 113</p>
<p>vacancy in office of, how filled............................. 113</p>
<pb n="478" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="304" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Surveyors (County.)</p>
<p>compensation of, for assisting sheriff in making out gen<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />eral list of lands on which taxes have not been paid... 228</p>
<p>official acts of, appointed by county judges or courts, legal<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ized, subject to proviso.................................. 112</p>
<p>(see county surveyor.)</p>
<p>Tarrant County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<p>Tax (ad valorem.)</p>
<p>(see ad valorem tax.)</p>
<p>Tax,</p>
<p>annual, of two per cent on gross earnings to be levied on every railroad, insurance, or telegraph company...... 199</p>
<p>Tax (Capitation,)</p>
<p>(see capitation tax.)</p>
<p>Tax (Occupation,)</p>
<p>duty of persons wishing to engage in taxable occupations. 232</p>
<p>license not to be granted for a less period than three months........................................... 201</p>
<p>licenses granted before January 1, 1871, to expire on that day, and the pro rata amount for the unexpired time to be credited on the amount as levied by &#8220;An Act to levy taxes,&#8221; approved August 15, 1870.......................... 201</p>
<p>penalty on persons engaging in taxable occupations, with<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />out prepayment of..................................... 232</p>
<p>(see occupation tax.)</p>
<p>special, authorized to be levied by County Courts, to im<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />prove roads and build bridges........................... 44</p>
<p>special, by Police Court of Goliad county, legalized........ 44</p>
<p>Taxes.</p>
<p>equal to one-half the amount authorized by &#8220;An Act to levy taxes,&#8221; approved August 15, 1870, may be levied by Police Courts, except as specified...................... 201</p>
<p>levied for building school houses, to be assessed and col<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />lected as other county taxes............................. 116</p>
<pb n="479" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="305" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>levied for building school houses, to be paid to county treasurer............................................ 116</p>
<p>levied under &#8220;An Act to levy taxes,&#8221; approved August 15, 1870, (pp. 199&#8212;201,) payable in the national currency of the United States.................................. 201</p>
<p>Teachers, Private.</p>
<p>when entitled to share in school fund......................... 116</p>
<p>Texas Bangers.</p>
<p>companies of, how armed................................. 6</p>
<p>companies of, how organized........................ 6</p>
<p>entire force of, to be under orders of Governor............... 8</p>
<p>for what time enrolled.................................. 7</p>
<p>how governed......................................... 7</p>
<p>pay of officers and men of.............................. 6</p>
<p>provisions, forage, etc., for, how furnished................. 7</p>
<p>to be raised, if possible, in frontier counties.................. 6</p>
<p>to furnish what arms, etc................................. 6</p>
<p>Thatcher. J. B.</p>
<p>pension of.................................... 123</p>
<p>Titus County.</p>
<p>Travis County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Treasurer (County).</p>
<p>to collect county taxes on occupations, trades and profes<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sions................................................... 108</p>
<p>Treasurer of the State.</p>
<p>(see State Treasurer.)</p>
<p>Truahart, Thomas M. and Henry M.</p>
<p>patents issued to, confirmed.............................. 42</p>
<p>Tyler County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">U.</head>
<p>Undetermined Causes.</p>
<p>on docket of the late County Courts, to be transferred to District Court docket................................... 48</p>
<pb n="480" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="306" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Unorganized Counties.</p>
<p>residents of, where entitled to register and vote.................. 131</p>
<p>Upshur County.</p>
<p>Uvalde County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>V an Zandt County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Veterans of the Revolution.</p>
<p>(see pensions)</p>
<p>Victoria County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Voter.</p>
<p>may be required to make, what oath and declaration..... 131</p>
<p>may deposit his vote in ballot box with his own hand, or hand it to one of the judges of election, but to no other person, for that purpose................................. 129</p>
<p>penalty for discharging, or threatening to discharge, etc., a 137</p>
<p>Voter&#8217;s Ticket.</p>
<p>to contain, what......................................... 131</p>
<p>Votes.</p>
<p>in case of equality of in future elections for Senators, etc., election to be returned to the people...................... 136</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">W.</head>
<p>Waco Tap Railroad Company.</p>
<p>special tax voted for aid of, authorized to be collected.... 10</p>
<p>Walker County.</p>
<p>(see counties)</p>
<p>Warrant of Arrest.</p>
<p>may be executed, by whom............................... 105</p>
<p>justices of the peace may issue, when..................... 104-105</p>
<p>requisites of.................................... 105</p>
<p>Washington County.</p>
<p>W ebb County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
<pb n="481" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="307" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>W ebb, David F.</p>
<p>pension of....................................... 123</p>
<p>Weighers of Cotton.</p>
<p>to be appointed by Governor where required................ 17</p>
<p>office of, not deemed lucrative............................. 17</p>
<p>Wharton County.</p>
<p>Wichita County.</p>
<p>Wilbarger County.</p>
<p>Williamson County.</p>
<p>Wilson County.</p>
<p>Wise County.</p>
<p>Wood County.</p>
<p>(see counities.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">Y.</head>
<p>Young County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">Z.</head>
<p>Zavalla County.</p>
<p>Zapata County.</p>
<p>(see counties.)</p>
</div3>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">ERRATA IN INDEX.</head>
<p>Page 248, line 3, for &#8220;labors&#8221; read &#8220;letters.&#8221;</p>
<p>Page 255, line 22, for &#8220;furnisned&#8221; read &#8220;furnished.&#8221;</p>
<p>Page 256, line 33, insert &#8220;by&#8221; between the words &#8220;appointed&#8221; and &#8220;county.&#8221;</p>
<pb n="482" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="308" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
</div2>
<div2 type="addendum">
<p>THE STATE OF TEXAS. <lb/>Department of State.</p>
<p>I, James P. Newcomb, Secretary of State of the State of Texas, certify that the Acts, Concurrent Resolution, and Joint Resolutions contained in this volume are, (except as explained in notes to pages one hundred and twenty-three and one hundred and twenty-four, and the word [it] in brackets, on page two hundred and thirty-four,) true copies taken from the originals in the Department of State, with which they have been carefully compared.</p>
<p>And I further certify, that the session of the Twelfth Legislature of said State commenced at the city of Austin on Tuesday, the twenty<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sixth day of April, in the year of our Lord, one thousand, eight hundred and seventy, and adjourned on Monday, the fifteenth day of August, in the year of our Lord, one thousand, eight hundred and seventy.</p>
<p>In testimony whereof, I have hereunto signed my name, and caused the seal of the Department of State to be affixed at the city of <floatingText rend="left"><body><p>[L. S.]</p></body></floatingText>Austin, this twenty-fourth day of September, in the year of our Lord, one thousand eight hundred and seventy.</p>
<closer>
<signed>JAMES P. NEWCOMB, <lb/>Secretary of State.</signed>
</closer>
</div2>
</div1>
</body>
</text>