<text xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0 UNTtite%20(1.3).xsd" xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="TEI">
<body>
<pb n="1043" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="141" />
<div1 type="article">
<head type="main">JOINT RESOLUTIONS.</head>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER I.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution authorizing the Adjutant General of the State to procure a suitable building in this city for the use of his depart<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ment, and to remove the powder and explosive ammunition in the basement of the capitol.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Adjutant General, Colonel Davidson, be and he is hereby au<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />thorized to procure a suitable building, somewhere in this city, for the use of his department, and that the powder and explosive am<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />munition now in the basement of this building be removed forth<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />with, daily, after the adjournment of both houses.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>January 26, 1871</date></dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER II.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution providing for the election of United States Sena<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tor on the second Tuesday after the organization of this Legis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />lature.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, An election for a Senator to represent this State in the Congress of the United States for the term of six years from and after the fourth day of March, 1871, having been had anterior to the declaration by the Congress of the United States that said State was entitled to representation in Congress, and before the act of Congress of April 25, 1866, providing therefor, was recognized by Congress as of effect herein, and at which election Morgan C. Ham<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" /><pb n="1044" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="142" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>ilton was declared to be elected as such Senator, at a provisional ses<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sion of this body held under the reconstruction laws, and before it had organized, provisionally or otherwise, under the Constitution of this State, and while it was sitting solely for the purpose of organiz<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ing in compliance with the reconstruction law of Congress; and</p>
<p>Whereas, Such election is deemed invalid, and in nowise effectual in the law, said Act of Congress of April 25, 1866, being inoperative herein at that time by reason of the subsequent legislation of Con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />gress in the premises, commonly known as the Reconstruction Acts; therefore,</p>
<p>Be it hereby declared and resolved, That this Legislature do proceed in accordance with the act of Congress in the premises, of April 25, 1866, to an election of a Senator to represent this State in the Congress of the United States of America for the full term of six years, commencing on the fourth day of March, A. D. 1871, and that such election be held on the twenty-fourth day of January, 1871, that being the second Tuesday after the organization of this session of the Legislature.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>January 26, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER III.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution asking influence of Texas Congressmen for cor<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />rection of and increased mail facilities.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, Great negligence is manifest in the existing manage<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ment of our mail service, as applied to Texas, and serious derange<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ment continually occurring, caused by want of proper facilities to insure prompt and reliable service; therefore,</p>
<p>Resolved, That our Senators be instructed, and our Representa<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tives in Congress be earnestly requested, to urge upon the Postal Department the great necessity of appointing at once a special mail agent for Texas alone, whose energy and efficiency will guarantee that existing evils will be speedily remedied; and also to urge upon the Department an immediate increase of our mail facilities.</p>
<p>Resolved, That the Secretary of State shall furnish copies of the foregoing to our Senators and Representatives in Congress.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>January 26, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1045" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="143" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER IV.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution instructing our Senators and requesting our Rep<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />resentatives in Congress to secure the establishment of the port of Sabine Pass a port of entry, and recommending to the Honora<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ble Congress of the United States a favorable consideration of the petition of the citizens of Southeastern and Northeastern Texas in relation to this subject, now in the hands of their Rep<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />resentative, G. W. Whitmore, for presentation to the Honorable Congress of the United States of America.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, It appears by the petition of the citizens of Eastern Texas, that the port of Sabine Pass is the only natural outlet and depot for the commerce and supplies of Eastern Texas, and it is the desire and wish of the entire people of Eastern Texas that Sabine Pass should be established a port of entry; therefore,</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That our Senators in Congress are hereby instructed, and our Representa<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tives are requested, to endeavor to secure the establishment of Sa<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />bine Pass a port of entry; and that this Legislature most heartily endorse the petition of the citizens of Eastern Texas to the Con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />gress of the United States upon this subject, and request for the same an early and favorable consideration.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>February 2, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER V.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution in reference to the defense of a certain suit.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, John A. C. Gray, Receiver for the Memphis, El Paso and Pacific Railroad Company, has filed a, bill in the United States Circuit Court for the Western District of Texas, against E. J. Da<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />vis, Governor of Texas, and Jacob Kuechler, Commissioner of the General Land Office, praying that said officers be restrained by in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />junction from issuing patents to certain parties who have: located land certificates within the Memphis, El Paso and Pacific Railroad Reserve, and upon said company&#8217;s lands; and</p>
<pb n="1046" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="144" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<p>Whereas, The Governor and the Commissioner of General Land Office, by the Attorney General of the State, has filed a demurrer to the aforesaid bill, which demurrer after full argument by the counsel for the State and the road has been overruled by said United States Circuit Court and the injunction granted; therefore</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Governor is hereby authorized to instruct the Attorney General of the State to take an appeal at once from the judgment of the Circuit Court in overruling said demurrer and in granting said in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />junction to the Supreme Court of the United States; and that if the Attorney General cannot leave his office to appear in person in the Supreme Court of the United States to represent the State, that the Governor be authorized to select some other attorney to prose<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cute an immediate appeal, and to press an early decision of the case by the Supreme Court of the United States.</p>
<p>Be it resolved, That this resolution shall take effect and be in force from and after its passage.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>February 14, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER VI.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution asking the Congress of the United States to pass a bill for the construction of a railroad from the eastern boundary of Texas to the Pacific Ocean, on or near the thirty-second paral<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />lel of latitude, and to grant the same aid for the construction of this railroad that has been granted to secure the building of the Northern Pacific Railroad.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, It is the opinion of the Legislature of the State of Texas that the early construction of a railroad from the eastern boundary of Texas to the Pacific Ocean, on or near the thirty-second parallel of latitude, is of vital importance to the people of the United States, and especially to the people of Texas; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The Government of the United States has granted lib<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />eral aid to secure the construction of two lines of railway to the Pacific Ocean, neither of which is located in the South; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The Southern States have an equal interest with the other States in the ownership of the public domain, and no lands<pb n="1047" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="145" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>have yet been donated by the General Government to aid in the construction of a Southern Pacific Railroad; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The construction of such a railroad would save to the Treasury of the United States the vast sums of money expended annually for the defense of the frontiers of Texas from the incur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sions of hostile Indians, and would save the lives and property of scores of the citizens of Texas, who perish annually at the hands of these savages, and would also secure the speedy settlement of a large portion of the State of Texas, which is now almost uninhab<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ited; therefore,</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Congress of the United States is earnestly requested to pass a bill for the construction of a railroad from the eastern boundary of Texas to the Pacific Ocean, on or near the thirty-second parallel of latitude, as soon as possible, and to grant the same aid for the con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />struction of this railroad that has been granted to secure the build<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ing of the Northern Pacific Railroad.</p>
<p>Be it further resolved, That our Senators are instructed and our Representatives in Congress are requested to use their utmost en<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />deavors to secure the passage of a bill embracing the objects set forth in this resolution.</p>
<p>Be it further resolved, That copies of this preamble and resolu<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion be forwarded to the President of the United States, to the President of the Senate, and Speaker of the House of Representa<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tives of the Congress of the United States, and to each of the Sen<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ators and Representatives from Texas in the Congress of the United States.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>February 14, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1048" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="146" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER VII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution authorizing the Governor to receive from the Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company, or the present repre<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sentatives thereof, the amount of interest due the special school fund on the first day of November, 1870, under the provisions of an act entitled &#8220;An Act for the relief of railroad companies in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />debted to the State for loans from the special school fund,&#8221; ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />proved August 13, 1870, and permitting said company, or its representatives, to avail itself of the provisions of said act.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, first, That the representatives of the Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company, having paid into the State Treasury the amount of in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />terest due the Special School Fund on the first day of November, A. D. 1870, under the provisions of an act entitled &#8220;An act for the relief of railroad companies indebted to the State, for loans from the Special School Fund,&#8221; approved August 13, 1870, and having also paid the costs of advertising said railroad for sale, the said railroad and the parties interested therein are hereby permitted to avail themselves of the provisions of said law, and the Governor is hereby authorized to suspend the sale thereof, as advertised to take place on the fourteenth day of February, 1871.</p>
<p>Secondly, That this joint resolution take effect from its passage.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>February 14, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER VIII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution making an appropriation of, one thousand and eighty-five dollars to pay for the portrait of Gen. Sam Houston.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, On the 15th day of August, A. D. 1870, a resolution was adopted by the Senate, instructing and requiring the sergeant<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />at-arms to obtain a portrait of Gen. Sam. Houston for the Senate Chamber;</p>
<p>Section 1. Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the sum of one thousand and eighty-five dollars be, and the same is hereby appropriated out of any unappropriated<pb n="1049" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="147" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>moneys in the Treasury, to reimburse Capt. A. Faulkner, sergeant<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />at-arms, amount paid for portrait of Gen. Sam Houston, father of Texas.</p>
<p>Sec. 2. Be it further resolved, That the Comptroller is author<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ized and required to draw his warrant upon the Treasurer for the amount.</p>
<p>Sec. 3. That this resolution take effect and be in force from and after its passage.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Passed <date>February 15, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="addendum">
<p>The foregoing joint resolution, received in the office of Secretary of State March first, one thousand eight hundred and seventy-one, having been presented to the Governor of Texas for his approval, and not having been returned by him to the house in which it origi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />nated within the time prescribed by the Constitution, has become a law without his approval.</p>
<closer>
<signed>JAMES P. NEWCOMB, <lb/>Secretary of State.</signed>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER IX.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution authorizing members of the Legislature to with<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />draw from office of Secretary of State enrolled bills which failed to become laws at the last session of the Legislature.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, Many bills passed at the last session of the Legislature failed to become laws; and</p>
<p>Whereas, Many members desire to reintroduce said bills; there<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fore,</p>
<p>Resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the introducer of any bill which passed both houses of the Legislature at its last session, and which failed to become a law, shall be au<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />thorized to withdraw from the office of the Secretary of State the enrolled copy of said bill on file in said office, and the Secretary of State is hereby directed to deliver to any member of the Senate or the House of Representatives, who may require the same, any en<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />rolled bill now on file in the office of the Secretary of State which may have been introduced by said member, and which failed to become a law.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>February 17, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1050" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="148" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER X.</head>
<p>Joint Resolution authorizing the Engrossing and Enrolling Clerks of this Legislature to occupy the State Library for the perform<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ance of their clerical duties.</p>
<p>Whereas, The Supreme Court of this State at present occupies the rooms set apart for the engrossing and enrolling clerks of this Legislature, under the direction of the President of the Senate and Speaker of the House of Representatives;</p>
<p>Be it resolved, That the engrossing and enrolling clerks of this Legislature be authorized to occupy pro tempore, for the perform<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ance of their clerical duties, the room in which the State Library and geological specimens are contained.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>February 23, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XI.</head>
<p>Joint Resolution making an appropriation, and expressing the wish of the State touching the suit of John A. G. Gray, receiver, etc., versus the Governor and Commissioner of the General Land Of<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fice.</p>
<p>Section 1. Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the sum of twelve hundred dollars, or so much thereof as may be necessary, be and is hereby appropriated, to be drawn on requisition of the Governor, to be used in paying the costs of court and the expenses of counsel in the suit of John A. C. Gray, re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ceiver, etc., versus the Governor and Commissioner of the General Land Office, in which an appeal has been taken to the Supreme Court of the United States.</p>
<p>Sec. 2. That it is the earnest desire of the State of Texas that said court shall advance said suit on its docket, and decide the same at as early a day as practicable.</p>
<p>Sec. 3. That this joint resolution shall be in force and take ef<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fect from its passage.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>March 13, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1051" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="149" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution asking the Congress of the United States to send a joint committee to the frontiers of Texas to inquire into and report upon the number of murders, and extent of the outrages committed in Texas during the last (5) five years, and now being committed in Texas by bands of Indians living within the terri<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tory of the United States, and harbored within the Republic of Mexico.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, By the terms of the joint resolution of the Congress of the United States, of December 29, 1845, admitting Texas into the Union as one of the States thereof, it was declared that the State of Texas was &#8220;admitted into the Union on an equal footing with the original States in all respects whatever,&#8221; and,</p>
<p>Whereas, Section 4 of Article 4 of the Constitution of the United States provides, among other things, that the United States shall protect each of the States &#8220;against invasion;&#8221; and</p>
<p>Whereas, During the last five (5) years the State of Texas has been invaded constantly by bands of Indians living within the boundaries of the United States, and with some of which bands the government of the United States has, at different times, made treaties of peace, and some of which bands have been fed and clothed by the government of the United States; and</p>
<p>Whereas, Said Indians during the last five (5) years have mur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dered several hundreds of the citizens of Texas, have stolen and de<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />stroyed property to the amount of millions of dollars in value, have not only retarded the settlement of the frontier counties of the State, but have almost depopulated several of the counties thereof most exposed to their invasions, and are at present actively engaged in their hellish work of murder, outrage and plunder; and</p>
<p>Whereas, During the last five (5) years bands of Indians known as the &#8220;Kickapoos&#8221; and &#8220;Lipans&#8221; have found a safe asylum within the territory of the Republic of Mexico, contiguous to the western frontier of Texas, from which territory they have made re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />peated invasions each year into the western counties of Texas, mur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dering and carrying into captivity many citizens of Texas, and re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />turning to Mexico laden with property captured from the people of Texas, with the full knowledge of the Mexican authorities, and without any opposition thereto having been offered by the Mexican authorities up to the present time, and it is fully believed that not<pb n="1052" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="150" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>less than one hundred (100) of the citizens of Texas have been mur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dered and carried into captivity by said Indians during the last five (5) years, while the work of murder and plunder was never more actively carried on by said Indians than at the present time; and</p>
<p>Whereas, During the last five (5) years the government of the United States has failed to make good its guarantee to protect the State of Texas &#8220;against invasion,&#8221; and the State of Texas is not allowed to make war upon the savages who are under the protection of the United States and ravage our frontiers and murder our citi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />zens, nor to make war upon the Indians who find a safe asylum in Mexico, from whence they invade our western counties, and the people of Texas are thus placed at the mercy of these savages without the means of retaliation; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The appeals of the people of Texas to the government of the United States for the relief and protection to which they are justly entitled, have been unheeded, and it has been asserted in the Congress of the United States that the statements of Indian outrages in Texas are greatly exaggerated, and in the main have been fabricated by interested parties desiring contracts, etc.; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The Congress of the United States has, at different times, sent committees into different parts of the Union to inquire into and report upon the murder of numbers of its citizens; there<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fore,</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Congress of the United States is hereby earnestly petitioned to send a joint committee from both houses to the frontier of Texas, to in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />quire into and report upon the facts set forth in the preamble to this resolution, to the end that the State of Texas may be protected by the United States against further invasion.</p>
<p>Be it further resolved, That our Senators are hereby instructed to do all in their power to secure the appointment of a joint com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />mittee for the purpose stated in the foregoing resolution.</p>
<p>Be it further resolved, That copies of this preamble and resolu<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion be forwarded as soon as possible to the President of the United States, the President of the Senate and Speaker of the House of Representatives of the Congress of the United States, and to each one of our Senators.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Passed <date>March 15, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1053" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="151" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XIII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution instructing our Senators and requesting our Rep<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />resentatives in Congress to urge upon Congress the passage of a bill for more secure and reliable postal telegraph facilities.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, The increased population and wealth of our State, and of the great States composing the Federal Union, demand an in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />crease of postal facilities; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The monopolies known as the Western Union Tele<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />graph Company, and other telegraph companies chartered by Con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />gress, have exacted such exorbitant rates as to preclude from its benefits much of the commercial interests of the country, to the detriment of all classes of the people of this Union; and</p>
<p>Whereas, An act of Congress passed in 1866, providing that the United States may at any time after the expiration of five years from the date of the passage of this act, for postal, military and other purposes, purchase all the telegraph lines, property and effects of any or all of said companies, at an appraised value to be ascer<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tained by five competent disinterested persons, two of whom shall be selected by the Postmaster General of the United States, two by the company interested, and one by the four so previously selected; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The time for the continuation of the charters of said companies having now expired, and the United States are author<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ized (if in their judgment it be deemed best,) to purchase and take control of the lines, property and effects, of any or all of said com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />panies, as provided by the section heretofore cited; therefore be it</p>
<p>Resolved, That our Senators in Congress be and are hereby in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />structed, and our Representatives requested, to immediately urge upon Congress the necessity of the passage of a bill for postal tele<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />graph facilities, under the control of the United States authorities, relieving us from monopolies and guaranteeing speedy and reliable communication at rates within the reach of all classes, of the inhab<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />itants of this Union.</p>
<p>Resolved, That one copy of this resolution be sent to each of our Senators and Representatives in Congress, and one copy to the Postmaster General, Washington, D. C.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>March 18, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1054" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="152" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XIV.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution respecting our postal service.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, The State of Texas embraces an area of nearly two hundred and seventy-five thousand square miles, and the distance from the eastern to the western boundary is near nine hundred miles, and the great distance between the postoffices, as well as the exposed condition of the mail routes in the interior of the State, subject our mails to great risks; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The increased mail depredations and robberies in this State are such as to greatly impair the efficiency of the postal serv<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ice, and it is believed that in many instances these robberies and depredations are committed by postmasters, and others connected with the postal service; and</p>
<p>Whereas, It is utterly impossible for the postal agent of this State, R. B. Baer, to visit the various portions of the State, correct irregularities, and ferret out depredations and robberies; therefore be it</p>
<p>Resolved, That our Senators in Congress be instructed, and our Representatives requested, to urge upon the Postmaster General the necessity of at least three assistants, to act as detectives under the supervision of the special agent for this State, if consistent with the postal laws of the United States.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>March 18, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XV.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution instructing our Senators and requesting our Rep<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />resentatives in Congress to use their exertions to effect the re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />moval of bands of Comanche and Kiowa Indians to a point at least one hundred and fifty miles from the civilized settlements or organized counties in Texas.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, It has been made manifest to the Legislature of the State of Texas, that large bands of Comanche and Kiowa Indians, well armed with repeating rifles, and mounted, periodically enter the State of Texas from the United States Indian Reservation,<pb n="1055" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="153" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>known as Fort Sill, in the Indian Territory, with the avowed pur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />pose of making war upon the citizens of the State of Texas; and</p>
<p>Whereas, Said bands of Indians do murder and rob our citizens, and capture their children, and return to said reservation with their plunder and captives, and are there harbored and protected; and</p>
<p>Whereas, It is believed that the removal of these Indians from their reservation on the frontier of Texas is absolutely necessary for the protection of the lives and property of the citizens of the frontier counties of the State; therefore,</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That our Senators be instructed, and our Representatives in Congress be re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />quested, to use their exertions to effect the removal of said Indian to a point at least one hundred and fifty miles from the civilized settlements, or organized counties in Texas; and that a copy of this resolution be forwarded to the President of the United States, and to our Senators and Representatives in Congress.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>March 18, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XVI.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution requesting our Representatives and Senators in the Congress of the United States to procure the passage of an act creating and establishing a port of entry at the city of Rockport, on Aransas Bay, in the county of Refugio, in this State.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, The city of Rockport, in the county of Refugio, has become the principal point of shipment on Aransas bay, and is now the most accessible and principal port having outlet for marine pur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />poses through Aransas Pass to the Gulf of Mexico; therefore</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That our Representatives in the Congress of the United States be instructed and our Senators requested to use their influence to procure the passage of a law creating and establishing a port of entry at the city of Rockport, on Aransas Bay, and appointing suitable officers for said port; and that a copy of this resolution be forwarded imme<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />diately after its passage to each of our members in Congress for their information.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>March 22, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1056" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="154" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XVII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution requiring the Comptroller of Public Accounts to re-transfer to the State revenue account, the sum of thirty-live thousand nine hundred and fifty dollars, and five cents heretofore erroneously transferred from said revenue account to the availa<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ble school fund account.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, The Comptroller of Public Accounts did, at the close of the last fiscal year, to-wit: August 31, 1870, erroneously transfer from the State Revenue account to the Available School Fund ac<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />count, the sum of thirty-five thousand nine hundred and fifty dollars and five cents; and</p>
<p>Whereas, Said sum does not properly belong to said school fund; therefore,</p>
<p>Section 1. Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Comptroller of Public Accounts be and he is hereby required to re-transfer said sum of thirty-five thousand nine hundred and fifty dollars and five cents from the Available School Fund account to the State Revenue account.</p>
<p>Sec. 2. That this resolution take effect from and after its passage.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>March 31, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XVIII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution instructing our Senators and requesting our mem<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />bers in Congress to urge the opening of the Indian country north of Texas to settlement.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Be it resolved by the Senate and House of Representatives of the State of Texas, That our Senators in the Congress of the United States be instructed and our Representatives requested to use their united influence to secure by treaty, act of Congress or otherwise, the opening of the Indian country north of Texas to settlement; and to urge the early organization of a State or Territorial Govern<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ment over the Territory now occupied by the Cherokee, Creek, Choc<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />taw, Chickasaw and other friendly Indians.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>April 4, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1057" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="155" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XIX.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution asking the Congress of the United States to pass an act giving a pension to the widow and minor children of Cap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tain William W. Montgomery.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, William W. Montgomery, a citizen of the county of Caldwell, and State of Texas, on the breaking out of the rebellion, was, through fear of violence on account of his loyalty to the Gov<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ernment of the United States, forced to leave his home and take refuse within the Federal lines; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The said William W. Montgomery, afterwards volun<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />teered in the service of the United States, and was appointed Cap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tain of Company.... in the First Regiment of Texas Cavalry; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The said William W. Montgomery afterwards, to-wit: on or about the fifteenth day of March, A. D. 1863, while a Captain in the said First Regiment of Texas Cavalry, then in the service of the United States, and while in the line of duty was, by a band of rebels styling themselves Confederate soldiers, captured and hung; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The said William W. Montgomery left a widow, to-wit: Mary Ann Montgomery, whose maiden name was Mary Ann McKay, who is still alive and a citizen of said Caldwell county, and has remained a widow ever since the death of her said husband William W. Montgomery; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The said William W. Montgomery, at the time of his death, had six children under the age of sixteen years, the dates of whose births are as follows, to-wit: Francis Marion, September 12, 1847, Edward L., December 19. 1851, John Wesley, January 24, 1854, Mary Ann, April 17, 1856, Martha E., August 19, 1858, and Harriet S., March 3, 1861; therefore</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Congress of the United States is earnestly petitioned to enact such measures as may be necessary to enable the said Mary Ann Mont<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />gomery, and her said minor children, to avail themselves of an act of Congress, approved July 14, 1862, and to obtain the pension pro<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />vided for in said act.</p>
<p>Be it further resolved, That a copy of this preamble and reso<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />lution be transmitted to the President of the Senate and Speaker of the House of Representatives of the United States, and to each of the Senators and Representatives from this State in the Congress of<pb n="1058" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="156" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>the United States, and that said Senators are hereby instructed, and said Representatives are earnestly requested, to use their most strenuous exertions to secure the legislation pointed out in this resolution.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>April 25, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XX.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution authorizing the Secretary of State to present one Winchester carbine to each of the persons who overtook and killed four of a band of hostile Indians.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, a hostile hand of savages had penetrated the settlements, killed one of our citizens and stolen a number of horses; and</p>
<p>Whereas, The following persons, to-wit: E. Phelan, J. K. Back<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ers, E. M. Shelby, B. M. Gibson, M. Phillips, J. W. Harrington, D. E. Harrington, Wm. Morrison, J. M. Beams, B. Daniels and W. B. Haynes overtook and gallantly attacked and defeated the said band, killing four of their number and recovered the stolen property,</p>
<p>Be it resolved, That one Winchester carbine belonging to the State be presented by the State to each of the above-named persons, upon his depositing in the geological room of the Capitol his share of the trophies captured, and that the Secretary of State is hereby authorized to make the presentation herein provided for.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>April 12, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XXI.</head>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">Joint Resolution authorizing and requiring the Governor to call a special election to fill certain vacancies.</head>
<p>Whereas, By reason of the expiration of the term of office of our Representatives in the Forty-first Congress, the State of Texas is<pb n="1059" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="157" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>unrepresented in the House of Representatives of the Congress of the United States; and</p>
<p>Whereas, Under the existing laws of this State, no general elec<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion can be held until November, A. D. 1872; therefore,</p>
<p>Sec. 1. Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Governor be, and he is hereby authorized and required to issue his proclamation for a special election to be held in the organ<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ized counties of each Congressional District in this State for Repre<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sentatives to the Forty-second Congress of the United States; said election to commence on the first Tuesday after the first Monday in October, A. D. 1871, to continue four days, and to be conducted in conformity with the law providing for the mode and manner of con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ducting elections in this State.</p>
<p>Sec. 2. That this resolution take effect and be in force from and after its passage.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 2, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XXII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution for the relief of Davis county.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, During the late war all books, laws, etc., belonging to Davis county were lost and destroyed; therefore,</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Secretary of State be and he is hereby authorized and directed to furnish said county with the usual supply of laws, books, etc., for the use of the officers of said county.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Passed <date>May 2, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="addendum">
<p>The foregoing joint resolution, received in the office of Secretary of State May eleven, one thousand eight hundred and seventy-one, having been presented to the Governor of Texas for his approval, and not having been returned by him to the house in which it origi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />nated within the time prescribed by the Constituton, has become a law without his approval.</p>
<closer>
<signed>JAMES P. NEWCOMB, <lb/>Secretary of State.</signed>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1060" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="158" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XXIII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution authorizing the Secretary of State to issue to the Galveston Mercantile Library sets of public documents of the State of Texas.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, The Galveston Mercantile Library, organized under the enlightened liberality of the merchants and citizens of Galves<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ton, on the 13th September, 1870, is the only chartered library in the State; and</p>
<p>Whereas, There has been donated to said library by the citizens of Galveston very nearly two thousand (2000) volumes, compris<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ing, in variety, works in every branch of literature and science, and has also obtained from the Federal Government full bound sets of all public documents since the 4th of March, 1861; therefore</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That de<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sirous of aiding in every feasible way literary institutions of the character mentioned, the Secretary of State be and is hereby au<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />thorized to issue to the Galveston Mercantile Library such com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />plete sets of public documents of Texas as may be donated without injury to the arrangement of the State archives or library.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 12, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XXIV.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution authorizing His Excellency the Governor of the State to dispose of the &#8220;Houston Tap and Brazoria Railroad.&#8221;</salute>
</opener>
<p>Section 1. Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That his Excellency, the Governor of the State, be, and he is hereby authorized to dispose of the &#8220;Houston Tap and Brazoria Railroad,&#8221; now in possession of the State. The disposition of said road to be by public or private sale, upon such terms and to such parties as he may deem best for the security of the school fund of the State; provided, that no sale or transfer shall be made to any parties until thirty days from the passage of this joint resolution, and not for less than the actual value of the iron on the track; and<pb n="1061" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="159" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>provided further, that the Governor may give the citizens residing on said road, or tributary to it, the preference of buying said road, so that the rails of said road may not be removed from the track of said road, as at present located.</p>
<p>Sec. 2. That this resolution take effect and be in force from and after its passage.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 18, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XXV.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution in relation to payment of salaries of District Judges.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, The Comptroller of the State of Texas has expressed doubts as to his authority to audit the claims, and the Treasurer to pay the salaries due the district judges, for any part of the month of July and the whole of the month of August, 1870, and</p>
<p>Whereas, The Legislature has hitherto made no appropriation for the payment of such salaries prior to the first of September, 1870; therefore,</p>
<p>Section 1. Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That the Comptroller of the State is hereby authorized and required to audit the claims, and the Treasurer to pay to the dis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />trict judges of the State, such amounts as may be due them from the date of their qualification as judges of their respective districts up to the first day of September, 1870; the same to be paid out of the appropriation made by the Commanding Officer, Fifth Military District, for the salaries of district judges for the year 1870, or if that be insufficient then out of any moneys in the State Treasury otherwise unappropriated.</p>
<p>Sec. 2. That this resolution take effect from and after its passage.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 18, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1062" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="160" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XXVI.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution proposing an amendment to section six of article ten of the Constitution of the State of Texas.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That section six of article ten of the Constitution of the State of Texas be so amended as hereafter to read and be as follows:</p>
<p>&#8220;Section 6. The Legislature shall not hereafter grant lands, ex<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cept for purposes of internal improvement,to any person or persons, nor shall any certificate for land be sold at the Land Office except to actual settlers upon the same, and in lots not exceeding one hun<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dred and sixty acres; provided, that the Legislature shall not grant out of the public domain more than twenty sections of land for bach mile of completed work in aid of the construction of which land may be granted; and provided further, that nothing in the foregoing proviso shall affect any rights granted or secured by laws passed prior to the final adoption of this amendment.&#8221;</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Passed <date>May 17, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="addendum">
<p>The foregoing joint resolution, receded in the office of Secretary of State May twenty-five, one thousand eight hundred and seventy<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />one, having been presented to the Governor of Texas for his ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />proval, and not having been returned by him to the house in which it originated within the time prescribed by the Constitution, has be<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />come a law without his approval.</p>
<closer>
<signed>JAMES P. NBWCOMB, <lb/>Secretary of State.</signed>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1063" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="161" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XXVII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Senate Joint Resolution instructing our Senators and requesting our Representatives in Congress to use their influence in the passage of such an act by the United States Congress as shall in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />corporate the name of Commodore John G. Tod in the navy of the United States in the same rank held by him in the Texas navy at the date of annexation.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, The Legislature of the State of Texas did, in the year 1857, and also in the year 1860, after full and complete investiga<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion of the premises, commend and indorse the services and labors of Commodore John G. Tod, as entitling him to a continuation of his rank and pay in the navy of the United States, and did request the same as a souvenir of the naval interest of Texas in that great event; and</p>
<p>Whereas, Commodore Tod remains the only survivor of the Texas navy transferred to the United States upon annexation (he having remained some months in the United States service during the &#8220;Mexican war,&#8221; and performed important services and functions in the operations against Mexico) who did not relinquish his claim to rank and pay by receiving any indemnity in lieu thereof from the United States, and whose devotion to the Republic during her days of darkness and danger had obtained for him from the Con<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />gress of the Republic of Texas the plaudit of &#8220;Well done, thou good and faithful servant;&#8221; now, therefore,</p>
<p>Section 1. Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That our Senators in Congress be instructed and our Repre<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sentatives requested to use their influence in the passage of such an act by the United States Congress as shall incorporate the name of Commodore John G. Tod in the navy of the United States, in the same rank held by him in the Texas navy at the date of annexation.</p>
<p>Sec. 2. That the Governor of Texas be requested to cause copies of these resolutions to be forwarded to the President of the United States, and to each of the Senators and Representatives of Texas in the United States Congress.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 24, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1064" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="162" /><fw type="header" place="top">Joint Resolutions.</fw>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">CHAPTER XXVIII.</head>
<opener>
<salute>Joint Resolution authorizing the Governor of the State to invite the Honorable Horace Greeley to visit the capital of the State.</salute>
</opener>
<p>Whereas, The Honorable Horace Greeley of New York, has consented to be present at the State Fair, to be held at the city of Houston; therefore,</p>
<p>Be it resolved by the Legislature of the State of Texas, That his Excellency, the Governor, be and he is hereby requested and empowered to invite Mr. Greeley to visit Austin, the Capital, as the guest of the State. Said invitation to be expressed and conveyed in such terms and manner as the Governor may deem befitting the eminent character and distinguished public services of the honored guest.</p>
<closer>
<dateline>Approved <date>May 24, 1871</date>.</dateline>
</closer>
</div2>
<div2 type="addendum">
<pb n="1065" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="163" />
<p>THE STATE OE TEXAS, <lb/>D<smcap>EPARTMENT OF </smcap>S<smcap>TATE</smcap>.</p>
<p>I, James P. Newcomb, Secretary of State of the State of Texas, certify that the Acts and Joint Resolutions contained in this vol<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ume (except as explained in notes on page one hundred and six: the word &#8220;effect&#8221; left out after &#8220;give&#8221; and before &#8220;to&#8221; in the cap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion to chapter fifty-five, on page sixty; the figures &#8220;1871&#8221; for &#8220;1870&#8221; in caption to chapter forty-three, on page thirty-six; and the certificates appended to Joint Resolutions on pages 147, 157 and 160, which should be omitted,) are true copies taken from the originals in the Department of State, with which they have been carefully compared.</p>
<p>And I farther certify that this session, of the Legislature of said State commenced at the city of Austin on Tuesday, the tenth day of January, in the year of our Lord one thousand eight hundred and seventy-one, and adjourned on Wednesday, the thirty-first day of May, in the year of our Lord one thousand eight hundred and seventy-one.</p>
<p>In testimony whereof I have hereunto signed my name and have caused the seal of the Department of State to <floatingText rend="left"><body><p>[L. S.]</p></body></floatingText>be affixed at the city of Austin, this first day of August, in the year of our Lord one thousand eight hundred and seventy-one.</p>
<closer>
<signed>JAMES P. NEWCOMB, <lb/>Secretary of State.</signed>
</closer>
</div2>
<pb n="1066" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="164" />
<pb n="1067" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="165" />
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">INDEX.</head>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">A.</head>
<p>Page</p>
<p>Acknowledgment or Proof&#8212;</p>
<p>of instruments for record, before what officers to be taken.. 77</p>
<p>Administrators&#8212;(See instates of deceased persons.)</p>
<p>Administrators, Executors, Guardians and Trustees&#8212;</p>
<p>may secure their bonds by pledge of real estate instead of personal security............................ 83</p>
<p>desiring to do so, shall file application with judge...... 86</p>
<p>judge to appoint three commissioners to ascertain and re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />port title and value............................. 83</p>
<p>if judge satisfied from report, prayer granted......... 83</p>
<p>pledge allowed only of unincumbered property at three<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fourths of its value................................ 83</p>
<p>applicant to execute and record mortgage deed........ 83</p>
<p>when done, bond to be approved and former sureties re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />leased........................................83-84</p>
<p>whenever duties fully discharged, judge to issue release of the property............................ 84</p>
<p>where real estate pledged, bond may be for actual (not double) amount............................ 84</p>
<p>Agent, traveling&#8212;</p>
<p>for patent medicines, etc., taxed..................... 46</p>
<p>Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas&#8212;</p>
<p>institution of learning, established under the style of..... 36</p>
<p>Governor to appoint three commissioners to locate....... 37</p>
<p>commissioners haying located, shall proceed to build...... 37</p>
<p>sum of $75,000 appropriated for buildings................ 37</p>
<p>contract for building shall require completion by 23d July, 1871................................................. 37</p>
<p>expenditures to be made under the order of the commission<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ers................................................ 37</p>
<pb n="1068" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="166" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Agricultuaal and Mechanical College of Texas&#8212;</p>
<p>expenditures to be drawn by warrant of commissioners on</p>
<p>State Treasurer..................................... 37 expenditures to be drawn by warrant of commissioners on</p>
<p>Comptroller, who shall draw his warrant on State Treas<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />urer.................................................. 135</p>
<p>rules for management of, as in the act to establish the Uni<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />versity of Texas, passed February 11, 1858............. 37</p>
<p>Alley, Nine or Ten Pin, taxed....................... 45</p>
<p>Appeal&#8212;</p>
<p>and trial by jury secured to persons charged with carrying weapons unlawfully............................... 26</p>
<p>by persons unable to give bond, perfected as to costs, by filing affidavit of such inability....................... 74</p>
<p>Appeal to Supreme Court in criminal cases&#8212;</p>
<p>form of recognizance on............................. 61</p>
<p>when notice of appeal given in criminal case District Court to stay proceedings till notice from clerk of Supreme Court of disallowance of appeal....................... 129</p>
<p>clerk of District Court to make transcript and deliver to convict or attorney.................................... 129</p>
<p>transcript to be presented to Judge of Supreme Court..... 129</p>
<p>if error appear, judge shall allow appeal.......... 129 clerk of Supreme Court to file and docket cause and issue order............................................. 129</p>
<p>if no error appear, judge shall disallow appeal, etc........ 129</p>
<p>clerk of Supreme Court to certify denial to District Court.. 129</p>
<p>if Judge of Supreme Court refuses appeal, transcript may be presented to some other judge, etc................ 129</p>
<p>clerk of District Court shall certify to Supreme Court no<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tice given of appeal, naming party, offense, etc........ 129</p>
<p>receipt of transcript by clerk of Supreme Court by mail to be deemed presentation to a Judge..................... 130</p>
<p>cleric of Supreme Court to keep docket of appeals asked.. 130</p>
<p>Apprentices, law of 1866 relating to, repealed...................... 90</p>
<p>Appropriations&#8212;</p>
<p>for mileage and per diem of members and per diem of offi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cers of Legislature............................... 1</p>
<p>for mileage and per diem of members and per diem of offi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cers of Legislature..................................... 12</p>
<p>for additional clerk for Governor......................... 5</p>
<p>for taking evidence as to estate of J. C. Clark, deceased, etc...................................................... 5</p>
<pb n="1069" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="167" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Appropriations&#8212;</p>
<p>to pay contingent and printing expenses of Twelfth Legisla<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ture..................................................... 7</p>
<p>for clerk for Comptroller in Pension Bureau................... 14</p>
<p>for salaries of clerks to judges of Supreme Court.......... 21</p>
<p>for release of citizens, captives with Indians........... 21</p>
<p>for officers of penitentiary now unpaid, etc................ 24</p>
<p>for preservation of graves in State cemetery........... 35</p>
<p>for buildings for Agricultural and Mechanical College.... 37</p>
<p>for payment of expenses in procuring transcripts of grants from archives in Mexico.................................. 57</p>
<p>for transcribing indexes in General Land Office............ 63</p>
<p>for furnishing Comptroller&#8217;s department.................... 66</p>
<p>to pay bonds heretofore issued by auditorial board......... 68</p>
<p>to pay expenses of auditorial board.................. 69</p>
<p>to pay expenses of receiving from United States moneys due this State............................................ 87</p>
<p>to pay witnesses on impeachment of W. H. Russell......88, 91</p>
<p>to pay for continuing general index to special acts........ 90</p>
<p>for contingent and printing expenses of Twelfth Legislature 97</p>
<p>for support of the State government.................. 98</p>
<p>for support of the Executive Department............... 98</p>
<p>for support of the State Department.................... 99</p>
<p>for support of the Comptroller&#8217;s Department............ 99</p>
<p>for support of the Treasurer&#8217;s Department............. 100</p>
<p>for support of the General Land Office..................... 101</p>
<p>for support of the Attorney General&#8217;s Department.............. 101</p>
<p>for support of the Adiutant General&#8217;s Department.......... 102</p>
<p>for support of the School Department............... 102</p>
<p>for support of the Bureau of Immigration............... 103</p>
<p>for support of the Geological Department............... 103</p>
<p>for support of the Lunatic Asylum............. 104</p>
<p>for support of the Blind Asylum................ 104</p>
<p>for support of the Deaf and Dumb Asylum.................... 104</p>
<p>for support of the Judiciary...................... 104</p>
<p>for support of the State Penitentiary................... 105</p>
<p>for repairs and improvements..................... 105</p>
<p>for miscellaneous.......................... 106</p>
<p>for expense of bonds to supply deficiency in revenue...... 108</p>
<p>for four additional draftsmen in General Land Office...... 110</p>
<p>for purposes of Bureau of Immigration.................. 128</p>
<p>to pay outstanding accounts against Blind Asylum........ 137 Arms&#8212;(See Weapons, Deadly.)</p>
<pb n="1070" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="168" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Arrest of person charged with crime may be made upon warrant transmitted by telegraph................. 39</p>
<p>Attorneys&#8212;</p>
<p>county, act for appointing repealed................. 35</p>
<p>at-law, taxed.................................. 46</p>
<p>Attorney General&#8212;</p>
<p>to be member of and president of auditorial board......... 68, 69</p>
<p>authorized to compromise suits against John S. Hancock and others in Colorado District Court.............. 133</p>
<p>shall certify compromise to district judge........................ 133</p>
<p>auctioneers, occupation tax levied on............ 46</p>
<p>Auditorial Board&#8212;</p>
<p>to be composed of Attorney General, Comptroller of Public Accounts and State Treasurer..........................67, 123</p>
<p>Attorney General to be president.................. 68</p>
<p>to audit all claims against the State reported on by former board and indebtedness for penitentiary...............68, 123</p>
<p>and all other claims against the State...................... 123</p>
<p>to endorse bonds heretofore issued, if valid............... 68, 123</p>
<p>fifty thousand dollars appropriated to pay bonds, etc....68, 124</p>
<p>if bonds not found valid, to be canceled.................... 68, 124</p>
<p>if any part valid, such portion to be paid................... 68, 124</p>
<p>Governor to procure necessary amount of bonds........ 68, 124</p>
<p>bonds to be signed by Governor, countersigned by Treasurer and registered by Comptroller.......................... 68</p>
<p>Governor made agent to sell bonds, may appoint agent.... 68</p>
<p>owners of valid claims may take bonds................ 69</p>
<p>when bonds disposed of, proceeds to be turned into Treasury 69</p>
<p>claims rejected by board, to be reported to Legislature.... 69</p>
<p>annual appropriation to be made to cover interest, etc..... 69</p>
<p>Comptroller to invest in United States bonds or bonds under this act.................................... 69</p>
<p>when sinking fund sufficient, bonds to be paid and destroyed 69</p>
<p>$2500 appropriated to pay expenses......................... 69</p>
<p>President authorized to appoint auditing clerk............. 69</p>
<p>pay of clerk, seven dollars per diem................... 69</p>
<p>if debts for Penitentiary be specie, to value in currency.... 123</p>
<p>all allowances of claims subject to approval of Governor.... 124</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1071" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="169" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">B.</head>
<p>Back Taxes&#8212;</p>
<p>may be sued for and recovered................... 51</p>
<p>how property freed from.................................... 52</p>
<p>Barbers, occupation tax levied on.......................... 46</p>
<p>Billiard, bagatelle and other tables, occupation tax levied on. 44</p>
<p>Blind Asylum&#8212;</p>
<p>Board of authorized to order payment of sundry accounts.. 137</p>
<p>Comptroller authorized to draw warrants on Treasurer.... 137</p>
<p>appropriation to pay them $3496 63...................... 137</p>
<p>Board of Education&#8212;</p>
<p>composed of Superintendent of Public Instruction, Governor and Attorney General............................. 58</p>
<p>shall adopt all necessary rules and regulations, etc........... 58</p>
<p>shall provide for examination and appointment of teachers, etc..................................................... 58</p>
<p>shall define course of study, kind of apparatus and books... 58</p>
<p>shall prescribe duties of board of directors................ 58</p>
<p>shall prescribe no rule preventing separation of students.. 58</p>
<p>shall report to Legislature necessary amendments, etc.... 59</p>
<p>shall prescribe manner of collecting and disbursing taxes for school houses, etc................................ 59</p>
<p>Board of School Directors&#8212;</p>
<p>to be appointed by supervisor of judicial district.......... 58</p>
<p>may separate students as may be for general good........... 58</p>
<p>shall have authority to levy tax for school houses, etc..... 59</p>
<p>shall require attendance of scholastic population at school.. 59</p>
<p>Boarding house, eating house, cook shop, occupation tax levied on......................................................... 45</p>
<p>Bond&#8212;</p>
<p>to be given on appeal where party is charged with carrying weapons unlawfully....................... 26</p>
<p>if forfeited proceeds appropriated to county roads...... 27</p>
<p>Bonds&#8212;</p>
<p>may be issued by counties, cities and towns in aid of rail<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />roads and other internal improvements.................. 30</p>
<p>not till tax is levied to pay interest and sinking fund...... 30</p>
<p>not to be issued except for work done.................... 30</p>
<p>to be registered and endorsed by Comptroller............... 30</p>
<p>to be canceled when paid, by whom and how................... 30</p>
<p>to be given by justices and sheriffs under tax law......... 53</p>
<pb n="1072" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="170" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Bonds&#8212;</p>
<p>to be recorded by district clerk and filed with Comptroller. 53</p>
<p>condition of justices&#8217; and sheriffs&#8217;....................... 53</p>
<p>justices and sheriffs may be required to give new, etc...... 53</p>
<p>sheriffs to give additional, for county moneys.............. 54</p>
<p>to be precured by Governor for liquidation of State debt.. 68</p>
<p>of Brazos county for jail, legalized................... 97</p>
<p>10 per cent. coupon, to be procured by Governor to supply deficiency in revenue............................... 106</p>
<p>principal and interest to be payable in currency........... 107</p>
<p>interest to be payable semi-annually first September and first March........................................... 107</p>
<p>to be redeemable semi-annually after two years............. 107</p>
<p>to be payable in five years from date.................. 107</p>
<p>principal and interest payable in New York or at State Treasury, at option of purchaser..................... 107</p>
<p>to be issued under direction of Governor, and sold by him or his agent............................................ 107</p>
<p>style and denomination to be directed by Governor........ 107</p>
<p>per cent age to agent for sale, not over one per cent....... 107</p>
<p>Governor to turn over proceeds of to State Treasury...... 107</p>
<p>Treasurer yearly to set apart sufficient amount to pay semi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />annual interest and one-third of principal............. 107</p>
<p>if revenue sufficient, to pay more than one-third.......... 107</p>
<p>appropriation for expenses $1500......................... 108</p>
<p>plates to be deposited in Treasury or destroyed under di<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />rection of Governor.................................... 108</p>
<p>act irrepealable till bonds fully paid.......................... 108</p>
<p>of administrators and executors to be payable to and ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />proved by district clerk......................... 125</p>
<p>new, to be given in twenty days when surety applies for re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />lief..................................................... 126</p>
<p>insufficient, approved by district clerk, clerk liable........ 126</p>
<p>Bowie, county of&#8212;</p>
<p>Governor authorized to commission two justices elected in. 96</p>
<p>official acts of those justices validated..................... 96</p>
<p>Brazoria county, Judge of Eighteenth Judicial District to hold special term in.................................. 140</p>
<p>Brazos, county of, bonds issued by County Court of, for jail legalized............................................. 97</p>
<p>Bridge or ferry, keeper of, occupation tax levied on............ 46</p>
<p>Brokers, (three classes of,) occupation tax levied on........... 46</p>
<p>Burlage &#38; Hollingsworth&#8217;s Abstract, Commissioner of General Land Office authorized to purchase 130 copies of.......... 131</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1073" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="171" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">C.</head>
<p>Cameron, county of, boundary of defined....................... 62</p>
<p>Canton, town of, designated as county seat of Van Zandt coun<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ty....................................................... 17</p>
<p>Captives with Indians, to be ransomed......................... 21</p>
<p>Cass, county of, name changed to, from Davis................. 92</p>
<p>Cemetery, State, graves in, to be preserved........................ 35</p>
<p>Certificates&#8212;(See Land Certificates.) Chaplain, to be appointed to State Penitentiary............. 15</p>
<p>Change of Venue&#8212;(See Venue.) Chief of State Police&#8212;(See State Police.) Circus, each performance taxed.............................. 45</p>
<p>Clark, John C., deceased, appropriation for taking evidence in suit for estate of, to be charged to estate................ 5</p>
<p>Clerk or sheriff, if either, party in a suit, district judge may appoint clerk or sheriff pro tern., who shall be sworn and give bond............................................... 89</p>
<p>Clerk of District Court&#8212;</p>
<p>of Lamar county, to make cross indexes to records............. <sub>7</sub>7</p>
<p>expenses to be paid by County Court of Lamar........... 77</p>
<p>Clerks of District Courts&#8212;</p>
<p>in criminal cases, when notice of appeal given, to make transcript and deliver to convict or attorney............... 129</p>
<p>to certify to Supreme Court notice given of appeal, naming party, offense and date of time.................. 129</p>
<p>Clerks of district courts and justices of the peace may issue executions for fees................................ 28</p>
<p>Clerk of Supreme Court&#8212;</p>
<p>when appeal allowed in criminal case, to file and docket cause and issue proper order to district court......... 129</p>
<p>when appeal disallowed, to certify denial to district court.. 129</p>
<p>receipt through mail of transcript by, deemed presentation to a judge of said court.............................. 130</p>
<p>to keep docket of appeals prayed for......................... 130</p>
<p>Clerks to judges of Supreme Court, each judge authorized to employ one............................................. 20</p>
<p>Code, Penal&#8212;</p>
<p>Arts. 412 and 418 amended............................ 84</p>
<p>former amendment of same articles repealed.............84-85</p>
<p>Code of Criminal Procedure, article 263 amended.......... 61</p>
<pb n="1074" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="172" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Coleman, County of&#8212;</p>
<p>attached to Brown county for judicial purposes........... 9</p>
<p>attached to Thirty-fourth Judicial District............ 11</p>
<p>re-attached to Brown county......................... 20</p>
<p>Collector of State Taxes&#8212;</p>
<p>to collect tax levied by counties, cities and towns, in aid of railroads, etc............................................ 31</p>
<p>to give bond for faithful collection and payment.......... 31</p>
<p>College, Agricultural and Mechanical, of Texas&#8212;(See Agricul<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tural and Mechanical College of Texas.) Collier, Edward, Esq., appropriation for taking evidence, etc., in relation to estate of John C. Clark, deceased, to be ex<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />pended by............................................ 6</p>
<p>Comal, county of, boundary lines of the, defined........... 4</p>
<p>Commission merchants, occupation tax levied on................ 46</p>
<p>Commissioners of Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas&#8212;</p>
<p>to be appointed by the Governor............................ 37</p>
<p>to locate the same in thirty days after appointment..... 37</p>
<p>to proceed, to construction of buildings, etc............ 37</p>
<p>shall procure architect................................... 37 Commissioner of General Land Office&#8212;</p>
<p>to issue patent on surveys made on valid land certificates, etc.................................................. 61</p>
<p>(See Land Office, General.) Comptroller of Public Accounts&#8212;</p>
<p>may employ clerk in pension bureau................... 13</p>
<p>to register and endorse bonds issued by counties, etc., in aid of works of internal improvement....................... 30</p>
<p>to approve bond of collector of taxes..................... 31</p>
<p>to cause additional tax to be levied, it necessary.............. 31</p>
<p>authorized to invest principal of perpetual school fund in United States Bonds...................................... 38</p>
<p>the United States bonds to be deposited in the Treasury.... 39</p>
<p>but not to invest interest paid by railroad companies...... 39</p>
<p>delinquent lists to be furnished to............................ 51</p>
<p>to give to persons paying back taxes sealed receipt........ 52</p>
<p>to prescribe form of bond for justices and sheriffs......... 53</p>
<p>bonds of justices and sheriffs to be deposited with....... 53</p>
<p>sheriffs to report to, amounts collected and when........ 54</p>
<p>sheriffs to pay drafts of, or remit to, as required............. 54</p>
<p>to prepare instructions under the tax law.................. 55</p>
<p>appropriation to furnish department of................... 66</p>
<pb n="1075" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="173" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Comptroller of Public Accounts&#8212;</p>
<p>to be a member of the auditorial board.................. 68</p>
<p>to invest sinking fund for payment of claims against the State in United States bonds, or bonds issued under this act.................................................... 69</p>
<p>when sinking fund sufficient, bonds to be paid off........ 69</p>
<p>to issue warrant on requisition of Chief of Police.......... 71</p>
<p>vouchers of Chief of Police to be filed with................. 71</p>
<p>to pay mileage, etc., of police, on vouchers certified by Chief................................................... 71</p>
<p>to draw warrants on State Treasurer upon warrants of Com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />missioners of Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas............................................. 135</p>
<p>to give registered and sealed receipt on payment of back taxes.................................................. 136</p>
<p>to draw warrants for accounts against Blind Asylum....... 137</p>
<p>Concerts&#8212;</p>
<p>unless gratuitous, taxed............................ 45</p>
<p>Concho, county of&#8212;</p>
<p>attached to county of San Saba for judicial jurposes...... 9</p>
<p>Contracts for labor&#8212;</p>
<p>act of 1866 regulating, repealed........................ 91</p>
<p>Courts of justices of the peace&#8212;</p>
<p>in court of what precinct suit may be commenced......... 81</p>
<p>suits for real property in precinct where land lies........ 81</p>
<p>in what county suit may be commenced....................... 82</p>
<p>if no justice in proper precinct, suit may be commenced in any adjoining precinct............................ 82</p>
<p>if none there, in any precinct in the county.................... 82</p>
<p>person having no fixed residence may be sued in any pre<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cinct................................................. 82</p>
<p>residents of incorporated cities, etc., before any justice in the corporation......................................... 82</p>
<p>appeal allowed, on notice given in open court............... 82</p>
<p>bond to be filed in ten days, amount and condition.......... 82</p>
<p>Courts, county&#8212;</p>
<p>thirty-eighth section act of August 13, 1870, concerning appointment of county attorneys, repealed................ 35</p>
<p>to order election for aiding railroads, etc.................... 29</p>
<p>to hold special meeting to ascertain result.................... 30</p>
<p>shall have power to issue bonds, etc..................... 30</p>
<p>may require accounts thereof from Comptroller............ 31</p>
<p>may levy tax equal to half of State tax................... 46</p>
<p>not to tax railroad or telegraph companies incomes........ 46</p>
<pb n="1076" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="174" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Courts, District&#8212;</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Twenty-first Judicial District.. 3</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Thirty-third Judicial District.. 4</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Thirty-firth Judicial District.. 4</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Eighteenth Judicial District.... 6</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Nineteenth Judicial District... 6</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Fourteenth Judicial District... 8</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Twenty-sixth Judicial District.9, 66</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Thirty-second Judicial District.9, 19</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Thirty-fourth Judicial District. 9</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Seventh Judicial District..... 10</p>
<p>to have concurrent jurisdiction under act to regulate keep<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ing and bearing deadly weapons, and judge to give the act specially in charge to grand juries.................. 27</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Eleventh Judicial District..... 32</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Fifteenth Judicial District.... 36</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Kaufman county (Tenth Judi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cial District)....................................... 41</p>
<p>time of holding changed in Thirtieth Judicial District..... 72</p>
<p>proceedings in&#8212;(See Depositions.) to stay proceedings in criminal cases when notice of appeal given, until notice from clerk of Supreme Court of dis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />allowance............................................. 129</p>
<p>of San Jacinto county, causes to be transferred to, from District Court of Polk county........................... 34</p>
<p>Criminal, of Galveston and Harris, jurisdiction of the court defined.................................................... 94</p>
<p>clerks of, to take charge of records and papers of former Criminal Court, transfer causes, etc., etc............... 94</p>
<p>Judge of, may exchange with any other judge in criminal matters............................................... 95</p>
<p>shall have jurisdiction of all appeals from justices of the peace in misdemeanor cases................................ 95</p>
<p>Court, Supreme&#8212;</p>
<p>Judges of, may employ each a private clerk............. 20</p>
<p>salary of clerk not more than $1200....................... 20</p>
<p>to be paid on certificate of judge.......................... 20</p>
<p>building in Capitol grounds, dedicated to use of........... 76</p>
<p>money for use of said building and of library, to be placed by State Treasurer to credit of court, and drawn by war<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />rant of Comptroller upon vouchers of court................ 76</p>
<p>building to be completed and (except Attorney General&#8217;s office) furnished under control of the court........... 76</p>
<pb n="1077" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="175" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Court, Supreme&#8212;</p>
<p>building, library, furniture, records, etc., to be under control of the court or appointee of the court............... 76</p>
<p>terms of, when to commence and how long to continue.... 81</p>
<p>(See Appeals to Supreme Court in criminal cases.) Court, Criminal, of San Antonio&#8212;</p>
<p>act of 1866 establishing, repealed................... 2</p>
<p>causes, papers, etc., therein transferred to District Court of Bexar.................................................... 2</p>
<p>writs, processes, etc., returnable to District Court of Bexar 2</p>
<p>Counties&#8212;</p>
<p>Atascosa, in Twenty-fourth Judicial District........... 33</p>
<p>Austin, District Court when held in................... 3</p>
<p>Bandera, in Twenty-fourth Judicial District................. 33</p>
<p>Bee, in Seventeenth Judicial District.................... 33</p>
<p>Bell, District Court when held in........................... 9</p>
<p>Bell, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District................ 11</p>
<p>Blanco, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District.................11, 33</p>
<p>Blanco, District Court when held in.................. 9, 66</p>
<p>Bosque, in Thirty-fifth Judicial District..................... 2</p>
<p>Bosque, District Court when held in............... 4</p>
<p>Bowie, Governor authorized to commission two justices elect<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ed in.................................. 96</p>
<p>acts of those justices validated......................... 96</p>
<p>Brazoria, District Court when held in.................... 6</p>
<p>Brazoria, Judge of Eighteenth Judicial District to hold special term in........................................ 140</p>
<p>Brazos, (bonds issued by, for jail legalized....................... 97</p>
<p>Brown, District Court, when held in.........................9, 20</p>
<p>Brown, in Thirty-second Judicial District................. 11</p>
<p>Burnet, District Court, when held in.................9, 19</p>
<p>Burnet, in Thirty-second Judicial District.................... 11</p>
<p>Cameron, District Court, when held in........................ 36</p>
<p>Cameron, boundary of, defined........................ 62</p>
<p>Cass, name of Davis county changed to.................... 92</p>
<p>Collin, District Court, when held in.......................... 33</p>
<p>Coleman, attached to Brown county (in Thirty-second Ju<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dicial District)..................................... 9</p>
<p>Coleman, attached to Thirty-fourth Judicial District...... 11</p>
<p>Coleman, re-attached to Brown county........................ 20</p>
<p>Colorado, District Court, when held in.................... 3</p>
<p>Comal, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District..................... 33</p>
<p>Comal, District Court when held in........................... 66</p>
<pb n="1078" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="176" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Comanche, District Court, when held in................. 9</p>
<p>Comanche, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District............ 11</p>
<p>Concho, attached to San Saba, county....................... 9</p>
<p>Concho, attached to Thirty-second Judicial District...... 11</p>
<p>Corvell, District Court when held in................. 9</p>
<p>Corvell, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District.................. 11</p>
<p>Dallas, District Court when held in..................... 8</p>
<p>Dallas, County Court of, authorized to levy tax for court house.................................................. 88</p>
<p>Davis, District Court when held in.......................... 10</p>
<p>Davis, name changed to Cass..................... 92</p>
<p>Delta, boundary of, changed....................... 18</p>
<p>Dimmitt, attached to Twenty-first Judicial District...... 33</p>
<p>Duval, boundary of, defined........................... 62</p>
<p>Edwards, attached to Kerr county....................9, 66</p>
<p>Edwards, attached to Twenty-sixth Judicial District......11,33</p>
<p>Ellis, District Court when held in................ 8</p>
<p>El Paso, boundaries of, defined........................ 70</p>
<p>Encinal, attached to Webb county.................... 36</p>
<p>Encinal, boundary of, defined............................. 62</p>
<p>Erath, District Court when held in....................... 9</p>
<p>Erath, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District............... 11</p>
<p>Falls, in Thirty-third Judicial District..................... 2</p>
<p>Falls, District Court when held in.................. 4</p>
<p>Fannin, District Court when held in..................... 33</p>
<p>Fort Bend, District Court when held in................. 3</p>
<p>Frio, attached to Twenty-fourth Judicial District........ 33</p>
<p>Frio, organized and boundaries defined....................... 73</p>
<p>Galveston, District Court when held in................ 6</p>
<p>Gillespie, District Court when held in............9, 66</p>
<p>Gillespie, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District...............11, 33</p>
<p>Goliad, in Seventeenth Judicial District.................. 33</p>
<p>Grimes, county seat of, to be fixed by election.............. 64</p>
<p>Grimes, District Court when held in............... 72</p>
<p>Hamilton, District Court when held in............... 9</p>
<p>Hamilton, in Thirty-fourth Judicial District.............. 11</p>
<p>Hamilton, county seat of, permanently located.......... 21</p>
<p>Harris, District Court when held in.................... 6</p>
<p>Harris, may issue bonds for county indebtedness.......... 121</p>
<p>Hays, may levy tax for court house................... 13</p>
<p>Hidalgo, District Court when held in................... 36</p>
<p>Hidalgo, boundary of, defined..................... 62</p>
<p>Hill, in Thirty-fifth Judicial District.................. 2</p>
<pb n="1079" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="177" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Counties&#8212;</p>
<p>Hill, District Court, when held in..................... 4</p>
<p>Hopkins, District Court when held in...................... 33</p>
<p>Hunt, District Court when held in................... 33</p>
<p>Johnson, eastern boundary changed................. 17</p>
<p>Karnes, in Seventeenth Judicial District................ 33</p>
<p>Kaufman, District Court when held in................. 41</p>
<p>Kimball, attached to Gillespie county....................9, 66</p>
<p>Kimball, attached to Twenty-sixth Judicial District.....11, 33</p>
<p>Kinney, attached to Twenty-fourth Judicial District...... 33</p>
<p>Kendall, District Court when held in..................9, 66</p>
<p>Kendall, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District................11, 33</p>
<p>Kerr, District Court when held in......................9, 66</p>
<p>Kerr, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District...................11, 33</p>
<p>Kerr. County Court of, may levy tax for jail............ 96</p>
<p>Lampasas, District Court when held in................9, 20</p>
<p>Lampasas, in Thirty-second Judicial District................ 11</p>
<p>Lampasas, County Court of, to have surveyor&#8217;s records tran<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />scribed.............................................. 138</p>
<p>La Salle, attached to Webb county.................. 36</p>
<p>La Salle, made part of Seventeenth Judicial District and at<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tached to Live Oak county.................................. 132</p>
<p>Limestone, in Thirty-third Judicial District................. 2</p>
<p>Limestone, District Court when held in................... 4</p>
<p>Live Oak, in Seventeenth Judicial District................. 33</p>
<p>Llano, District Court when held in.......................9, 20</p>
<p>Llano, in Thirty-second Judicial District...................... 11</p>
<p>Madison, District Court when held in.................. 72</p>
<p>Marion, District Court when held in............... 10</p>
<p>Mason, District Court when held in............................ 9, 66</p>
<p>Mason, in Twenty-sixth Judicial District............. 11</p>
<p>Maverick, in Twenty-fourth Judicial District............... 33</p>
<p>McCulloch, attached to San Saba county................... 9</p>
<p>McCulloch, attached to Thirty-second Judicial District.... 11</p>
<p>McLennan, in Thirty-third Judicial District................ 2</p>
<p>McLennan, District Court when held in................... 4</p>
<p>McMullen, attached to Seventeenth Judicial District...... 33</p>
<p>Medina, in Twenty-fourth Judicial District............. 33</p>
<p>Menard, attached to Mason county.............. 9</p>
<p>Menard, attached to Twenty-sixth Judicial District....... 11</p>
<p>Milam, County Court of may levy tax for court house... 79</p>
<p>Montgomery, District Court when held in............ 6</p>
<p>Navarro, in Thirty-fifth Judicial District................. 2</p>
<pb n="1080" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="178" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Navarro, District Court when held in................... 4</p>
<p>Nueces, boundary of defined.......................... 62</p>
<p>Pecos, organized and boundaries defined.................. 73</p>
<p>Presidio, organized and boundaries defined................. 86</p>
<p>Refugio, county seat removed to Rockport................. 12</p>
<p>Robertson, County Court of may levy tax for court house and jail............................................. 27</p>
<p>Runnels, attached to Brown county...................... 9</p>
<p>Runnels, attached to Thirty-fourth Judicial District........ 11</p>
<p>Runnels, re-attached to Brown county...................... 20</p>
<p>San Jacinto, District Court when held in................ 72</p>
<p>San Jacinto, county tax collected in other counties on per<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sons and property in, to be paid to county treasurer of.. 122</p>
<p>San Saba, District Court when held in....................9, 20</p>
<p>San Saba, in Thirty-second Judicial District.............. 11</p>
<p>Starr, District Court when held in...................... 36</p>
<p>Starr, boundary of defined........................... 62</p>
<p>Tarrant, District Court, when held in.................. 8</p>
<p>Titus, District Court when held in.................... 10</p>
<p>Titus, County Court of may issue bonds for building court house and jail..................................... 22</p>
<p>Uvalde, in Twenty-fourth Judicial District................ 33</p>
<p>Van Zandt, county seat of located at Canton................ 17</p>
<p>Van Zandt, acts of County Court of validated............. 80</p>
<p>Van Zandt, County Court of may levy tax for building court house................................... 130</p>
<p>Walker, District Court when held in..................... 72</p>
<p>Washington, County Court of may levy tax for building jail 11</p>
<p>Webb, District Court when held in.................... 36</p>
<p>Webb, boundary of defined........................... 62</p>
<p>Williamson, District Court when held in.................9, 19</p>
<p>Williamson, in Thirty-second Judicial District.............. 11</p>
<p>Wilson, in Seventeenth Judicial District.................. 33</p>
<p>Zapata, boundary of defined........................ 62</p>
<p>Zavala, attached to Twenty-fourth Judicial District...... 33</p>
<p>Counties, Cities and Towns&#8212;</p>
<p>authorized to aid in construction of railroads, etc....... 29</p>
<p>fifty freeholders to petition for election.................... 29</p>
<p>court to order election between thirty and forty days after the order........................................ 29</p>
<p>order to be entered on minutes, stating time and place, and appointing three managers, of election.................... 29</p>
<pb n="1081" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="179" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>order to be published three weeks......................... 29</p>
<p>any manager failing to attend, those present to appoint.... 29</p>
<p>voting shall be by ballot............................. 29</p>
<p>every elector under the Constitution may vote................ 29</p>
<p>one of the managers to make return to the court............ 30</p>
<p>special meeting to be held by the court to ascertain result.. 30 30</p>
<p>if two-thirds in affirmative, court to make necessary order.. 30</p>
<p>court shall have power to issue bonds, etc............... 30</p>
<p>but not till tax first levied for interest and sinking fund.... 30</p>
<p>bonds not to be issued except for work done............... 30</p>
<p>bonds to be registered and endorsed by State Comptroller.. 30</p>
<p>taxes levied under, to be applied only to purposes of this act 30</p>
<p>taxes to be collected by collector of State taxes............ 31</p>
<p>collecting officer to give bond, etc......................... 31</p>
<p>State Treasurer to receive, pay out, and keep separate ac<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />counts thereof.................................... 31</p>
<p>County Court may require statement from Comptroller.... 31</p>
<p>bonds to be canceled when paid, by whom and how............. 31</p>
<p>if sufficient tax not levied, Comptroller to have it done.... 31</p>
<p>no county to aid any one railroad, etc., beyond ten per cent. on its taxable property and not beyond twenty per cent. for all...................................... 32</p>
<p>any incorporated city or town may aid in like manner.... 32</p>
<p>city and town officers to perform similar duties to those of county officers............................................. 32</p>
<p>all such aid to be appropriated exclusively to internal im<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />provements of this State............................. 75</p>
<p>(See Registration.)</p>
<p>County occupation tax, to be collected by county treasurer.... 48</p>
<p>County roads, fines for bearing arms, etc., etc., appropriated to 26</p>
<p>County Surveyor&#8212;</p>
<p>may be appointed for two or more counties................ 133</p>
<p>shall keep records of each county separate..................... 133</p>
<p>no one to be appointed, unless recommended, etc............ 133</p>
<p>of Lampasas county, records of, to be transcribed........... 138</p>
<p>County tax, collected in other counties, to be paid into the State treasury to the credit of the county where due....... 53</p>
<p>Criminal cases&#8212;(See Appeals to Supreme Court in.)</p>
<pb n="1082" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="180" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">D.</head>
<p>Daguerrean and photographic gallery, occupation tax levied on 46</p>
<p>Dallas county, court of, authorized to levy and collect tax for building court house.................................. 89</p>
<p>Davis county, name of, changed to Cass........................ 92</p>
<p>Delta county, boundary of changed.......................... 18</p>
<p>Dentists, occupation tax levied on........................ 46</p>
<p>Departments, heads of authorized to administer oaths.......... 124</p>
<p>Depositions&#8212;</p>
<p>when witness resides out of State deposition may be taken by either party.......................................... 110</p>
<p>interrogatories to be filed in the court where suit pending.. 110</p>
<p>notice with copy to be served on opposite party, agent or at<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />torney.................................................. 110</p>
<p>after fifth day after service, commission to be issued...... 110</p>
<p>to whom directed and what it requires................... 111</p>
<p>answers to be reduced to writing and signed and sworn to by witness.............................................. 111</p>
<p>officer taking, to certify under hand and seal................. 111</p>
<p>depositions so taken may be returned into court, etc...... 111</p>
<p>depositions taken under former laws, shall be valid........ 111</p>
<p>official character of party taking, outside of the United States, how tested............................... 111</p>
<p>Directors of State Penitentiary, board of three to be appointed 15</p>
<p>Distillery, Brewery, occupation tax levied on............... 45</p>
<p>District clerk&#8212;</p>
<p>all bonds of executors and administrators payable to and to be approved by...................................... 125</p>
<p>approving insufficient bond, liable to party interested.... 126</p>
<p>District Judge&#8212;</p>
<p>may appoint sheriff or clerk pro tem. when sheriff or clerk is party in a suit, etc.......................... 89</p>
<p>of Colorado county to dismiss suits of the State vs. J. S. Hancock et als., upon certificate of Attorney General of compromise................................. 133</p>
<p>Districts, judicial&#8212;</p>
<p>act providing for amended as to Thirty-third District..... 2</p>
<p>act providing for amended as to Thirty-fifth District...... 3</p>
<p>act providing for amended as to Twenty-sixth District..... 11</p>
<pb n="1083" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="181" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>act providing for amended as to Thirty-second District... 11</p>
<p>act providing for amended as to Thirty-fourth District.... 11</p>
<p>act providing for amended as to Seventeenth District...... 33</p>
<p>act providing for amended as to Twenty-fourth District.... 33</p>
<p>act providing for amended as to Twenty-sixth District.... 33</p>
<p>La Salle county made part of the Seventeenth District.... 132</p>
<p>Judge of Eighteenth, to hold special term in Brazoria county 140</p>
<p>Dramatic representations, etc., tax levied on................. 45</p>
<p>Duval, county of, boundary of the defined................. 62</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">E</head>
<p>Education&#8212;(See Public Free Schools.)</p>
<p>Edwards, county of, attached to county of Kerr............... 9</p>
<p>Election, three managers of, to be appointed by County Court on proposition to aid railroads, etc...................... 29</p>
<p>Ellis, county of&#8212;</p>
<p>County Court of, authorized to issue bonds for building court house and jail............................. 65</p>
<p>to collect special tax to pay interest, etc.................... 65</p>
<p>El Paso, county of, boundaries of defined................ 70</p>
<p>Encinal, county of, boundaries of defined.................. 62</p>
<p>Estates of deceased persons&#8212;</p>
<p>where administration shall be commenced.................. 125</p>
<p>appointment of temporary administrator may be made with<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />out notice.................................... 125</p>
<p>appointee shall within five days take oath and give bond to be approved by and payable to the district clerk......... 125</p>
<p>if clerk appointed, bond to be approved by district judge... 125</p>
<p>application ready for trial at the term after notice duly posted...................................... 125</p>
<p>if time complete during term, shall stand for trial at that term...................................125, 126</p>
<p>executor&#8217;s bond to be payable to and approved by district clerk..................................... 125</p>
<p>when not otherwise provided, time for giving bond and tak<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ing oath fixed at twenty days.......................... 126</p>
<p>surety may apply for relief, and, upon notice, administrator or executor shall give new bond in twenty days........ 126</p>
<p>sureties discharged, when whole penalty recovered....... 126</p>
<pb n="1084" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="182" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>all bonds of executors and administrators payable to and to be approved by clerk of District Court................. 126</p>
<p>clerk approving insufficient bond, liable to any person in<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />terested.................................... 126</p>
<p>executor or administrator, failing to pay when ordered, ex<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ecution to issue against his property for amount and ten per cent. per month interest......................... 126</p>
<p>sales of real property of wards governed by rules for sale of real estate by administrators and executors, sections 233 to 250 inclusive (act of 1870)...................... 126</p>
<p>rules as to accounts of executors and administrators applied to accounts of guardians, but no notice required........ 127</p>
<p>Evidence&#8212;</p>
<p>(See Depositions.)</p>
<p>printed statute books of this State shall be............. 111</p>
<p>printed statute books of the United States and of the sev<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />eral States, printed under Government authority, shall also be...................................... 111</p>
<p>certified copy under seal or Secretary of State of acts from such books shall also be.......................... 112</p>
<p>copies of private bill certified by Secretary of State shall be. 112</p>
<p>Execution&#8212;</p>
<p>clerks and justices may issue bills of costs for fees, which shall have the force of............................. 28</p>
<p>laws concerning, to apply to such bills of costs............. 28</p>
<p>may be issued against property of executor or administrator failing to pay when ordered........................ 126</p>
<p>Executors&#8212;</p>
<p>(See Administrators, Executors, Guardians and Trustees.)</p>
<p>(See Estates of Deceased Persons.)</p>
<p>Exclusion of witness&#8212;(See Witness.)</p>
<p>Exemption&#8212;</p>
<p>from service in reserve militia provided for.............. 23</p>
<p>fund arising therefrom to pay State guard, etc............. 23</p>
<p>of certain property from taxation....................... 85</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">F.</head>
<p>Fees or costs due clerks, sheriffs, etc., payable in United States currency................................. 63</p>
<p>Ferry or bridge, keeper of, occupation tax levied on........ 46</p>
<pb n="1085" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="183" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>organized and boundaries defined......................... 122</p>
<p>county seat to be at William Eastwood Rancho until other<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />wise ordered and named Frio....................... 122</p>
<p>commissioners appointer to divide into five precincts and order election of justices of the peace................. 122</p>
<p>twenty days notice of election by posting at three public places........................................ 122</p>
<p>election to be held at county seat.................... 123</p>
<p>commissioners to have powers of judges of election, to Secre<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tary of State in ten days...................... 123</p>
<p>Frontier counties to be designated by Governor, where weap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ons may be carried........................... 26</p>
<p>Funding State debt&#8212;</p>
<p>(See Auditorial Board.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">G.</head>
<p>Galveston and Harris, Criminal Court of&#8212;</p>
<p>(See Court, Criminal District of.)</p>
<p>Gaming Tables&#8212;</p>
<p>keeping and exhibiting of, how punished................. 84</p>
<p>betting at, how punished......................... 84</p>
<p>Gauge, railroads authorized to regulate.................... 7</p>
<p>General muster of militia to be held on fourth of July....... 23</p>
<p>Gift enterprises, tax levied on......................... 45</p>
<p>Governor&#8212;</p>
<p>authorized to employ additional clerk.................. 5</p>
<p>authorized to lease Penitentiary.................. 14</p>
<p>authorized to procure release of captives with Indians........ 21</p>
<p>authorized to advance part or all of the appropriation there<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />for...................................... 38</p>
<p>authorized to control militia fines and exemption fund.... 23</p>
<p>authorized to designate frontier counties in which weapons may be carried on the person........................ 26</p>
<p>required to publish act to regulate keeping and bearing deadly weapons................................ 27</p>
<p>to appoint three commissioners for the Agricultural and Mechanical College.............................. 37</p>
<p>to appoint suitable person to transcribe grants from Mexi<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />can records................................ 56</p>
<p>Superintendent of Public Instruction to report to........ 57</p>
<p>to approve appointments and removals of supervisors by Superintendent.............................. 58</p>
<pb n="1086" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="184" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>with Superintendent and Attorney General to constitute Board of Education............................ 58</p>
<p>to procure bonds sufficient to pay indebtedness ascertained by auditorial board.......................... 68</p>
<p>made agent of the State to sell, and may appoint agent.... 68</p>
<p>shall turn over proceeds into State Treasury.............. 69</p>
<p>shall approve requisitions of Chief of Police................ 71</p>
<p>may remove members of State Police................. 71</p>
<p>may appoint special policemen (not more than twenty in a county).................................... 71</p>
<p>may constitute conductors, etc., special policemen........ 72</p>
<p>to require National Bank Note Co. to cancel plates, etc.... 75</p>
<p>to receive from United States, money due Texas......... 87</p>
<p>to place, when received, in State Treasury............... 87</p>
<p>if in gold, may convert to currency..................... 87</p>
<p>may appoint agent to receive............................. 87</p>
<p>if agent a State officer, he shall be paid only necessary ex<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />penses...................................... 87</p>
<p>to have general index to special acts continued........... 90</p>
<p>authorized to commission two justices in Bowie county.... 96</p>
<p>authorized to procure bonds not over $400,000, to supply deficiency in revenue, etc......................... 106</p>
<p>bonds to be sold by, or by his agent, at discretion......... 107</p>
<p>shall direct style and denomination of bonds............. 107</p>
<p>per centage not over one per cent. allowed to agents....... 107</p>
<p>shall turn over proceeds to State Treasury............. 107</p>
<p>shall see that sufficient revenue set apart to pay principal and interest is so applied......................... 107</p>
<p>shall cause notice not less than thirty days of proposals to redeem principal of bonds...................... 107</p>
<p>to appoint superintendent of immigration.............. 128</p>
<p>to lay before Legislature report of superintendent......... 128</p>
<p>may appoint or accredit agents or lecturers.............. 128</p>
<p>may appoint county surveyors for two or more counties.... 133</p>
<p>Grimes county, election to be held to fix county seat of...... 64</p>
<p>Guardians&#8212;(See Administrators, Executors, Guardians and Trustees, and Estates of Deceased Persons.)</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1087" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="185" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">H.</head>
<p>Hamilton county, county seat of, permanently located...... 21</p>
<p>Hancock, John S. and sureties&#8212;</p>
<p>suit against, in Colorado District Court may be compromised by Attorney General.......................... 133</p>
<p>district judge of Colorado, to dismiss suits on Attorney Gen<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />eral&#8217;s certificate of compromise...................... 133</p>
<p>Harris, county of, County Court of, authorized to issue bonds for county indebtedness.......................... 121</p>
<p>Hays, county of, may levy tax for building court house...... 13</p>
<p>Heads of departments authorized to administer oaths........ 124</p>
<p>Hidalgo, county of, boundary of, defined................ 62</p>
<p>Hides and Animals&#8212;(See Stockraising.)</p>
<p>Homestead&#8212;</p>
<p>any one occupying one hundred and sixty acres or less for three years, entitled to it as a homestead............ 16</p>
<p>original occupant being dead, patent may issue to heirs.... 16</p>
<p>original occupant having sold, patent may issue to his as<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />signee...................................... 17</p>
<p>(See Public Lands.)</p>
<p>Hotels, occupation tax levied on (several classes)............ 45</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">I.</head>
<p>Idiots and insane persons, duties of chief justices in relation to, to be performed by presiding justices................ 41</p>
<p>Immigration&#8212;</p>
<p>Bureau of created............................. 127</p>
<p>Governor, with advice of Senate, to appoint Superintendent, 127</p>
<p>Superintendent to hold office for four years............. 127</p>
<p>salary of Superintendent $2000 per annum................ 127</p>
<p>duties of Superintendent..................... 127</p>
<p>to report to Governor before each session of Legislature.... 128</p>
<p>may appoint four agents, two for the United States, two for Europe........................... 128</p>
<p>agents to act under instruction of superintendent........ 128</p>
<p>their salary not to exceed $3500 per annum.............. 128</p>
<p>(Governor may appoint agents or lecturers, but without com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />pensation............................. 128</p>
<p>$30,000 appropriated for purposes of the Bureau............ 128</p>
<pb n="1088" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="186" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Indians&#8212;</p>
<p>citizens captives with, release to be procured............. 21</p>
<p>$5000 appropriated for that purpose.................... 21</p>
<p>Governor to advance part of or the whole appropriation.... 38</p>
<p>Inspection of hides and animals&#8212;(See Stock Raising.)</p>
<p>Inspector of State Penitentiary&#8212;</p>
<p>to be appointed by the Governor.................... 15</p>
<p>his duties defined................................ 15</p>
<p>Insurance companies, life, fire and marine, tax levied on...... 46</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">J</head>
<p>Johnson, county of, eastern boundary of, changed........... 17</p>
<p>Judge or other magistrate may send warrant or affidavit by telegraph................................... 39</p>
<p>Jurisdiction of district court in probate matters&#8212;(See Es<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tates of Deceased Persons.)</p>
<p>Jury, grand, act concerning bearing deadly weapons to be given specially in charge to...................... 27</p>
<p>Justices and clerks may issue bills for fees, to have force of executions................................... 28</p>
<p>Justices of the Peace&#8212;(As Assessors of Taxes.)</p>
<p>taxes shall be assessed by........................ 48</p>
<p>may assess by deputy, who may be a county officer......... 48</p>
<p>to call on all residents of precinct for lists.................. 48</p>
<p>failing to do so, liable to fine....................... 49</p>
<p>to give bond with three or more good securities............ 53</p>
<p>shall take and subscribe constitutional oath................. 53</p>
<p>may be required to give new bond..................... 53</p>
<p>when so required, shall suspend duties until, etc........... 53</p>
<p>failing to give new bond for thirty days, shall be dismissed, 53</p>
<p>compensation of, for assessing, etc..................... 55</p>
<p>excess over $4000, to be paid into State Treasury........ 55</p>
<p>section 29 of act of 13th, August 1870, authorizing them to appoint deputies repealed......................... 137</p>
<p>Justices of the Peace, Courts of&#8212;(See Courts of Justices of the Peace.)</p>
<p>Judgment of justice for taxes, not to operate to enforce lien.. 50</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1089" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="187" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">K.</head>
<p>Kimball, county of, attached to Gillespie county............ 9</p>
<p>Kerr, county of, County Court of, authorized to levy special tax for jail.................................... 96</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">L.</head>
<p>Lamar, county of&#8212;</p>
<p>clerk of district court of, to make cross indexes to records. 77</p>
<p>county court of, to provide for expense.................... 77</p>
<p>Lampasas, county of&#8212;</p>
<p>County Court of, to have surveyor&#8217;s records transcribed.... 138</p>
<p>transcript, when made, legal and valid................... 138</p>
<p>court may pay fifteen cents per hundred words............ 138</p>
<p>Land agents&#8212;</p>
<p>occupation tax levied on........................ 46</p>
<p>who are and who are not........................... 46</p>
<p>Land certificates&#8212;</p>
<p>rights under genuine, not forfeited by failure to locate, sur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />vey or return, and time extended.................. 61</p>
<p>all surveys properly made under, if returned and filed, and not in conflict, valid and patent to issue............. 61</p>
<p>Land Office, General&#8212;</p>
<p>indexes in, to be transcribed...................... 63</p>
<p>Commissioner to employ four draftsmen................... 110</p>
<p>Commissioner authorized to purchase one hundred and thir<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ty copies of Burlage &#38; Hollingsworth&#8217;s book of valid land titles...................................... 131</p>
<p>Landed property&#8212;</p>
<p>when sold under decree of court, court to specify size, etc., of lots..................................... 79</p>
<p>court may order employment of surveyor................. 79</p>
<p>his fees to constitute part of the costs................ 79</p>
<p>one deed to each purchaser for all the lots he may buy.... 79</p>
<p>fee to sheriff for one deed only to each purchaser......... 79</p>
<p>La Salle, county of&#8212;</p>
<p>made part of Seventeenth Judicial District and attached to Live Oak county.......................... 132</p>
<p>Leaverton, James H., deceased, settlement of estate of, trans<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ferred from district court of Anderson county to that of Houston county............................ 78</p>
<pb n="1090" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="188" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Lee, I. A., acts of, as justice of the peace in Coryell county vali<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dated................................ 138</p>
<p>Lessees of Penitentiary&#8212;</p>
<p>(See Penitentiary, State.)</p>
<p>Live Oak, county of, dividing line between, and Nueces county defined................................... 109</p>
<p>Livery stables, occupation tax levied on (several classes)..... 45</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">M.</head>
<p>Magistrate, judge or other, may send warrant or affidavit by telegraph.................................. 39</p>
<p>McCulloch county attached to county of San Saba............ 9</p>
<p>Managers of election&#8212;</p>
<p>three to be appointed for special election to aid railroads, etc...................................... 29</p>
<p>any of, failing to attend, the others may appoint......... 29</p>
<p>Meeting of stockholders or directors&#8212;</p>
<p>(See Railroad Companies.)</p>
<p>Menagerie, wax works, etc., tax levied on................. 45</p>
<p>Menard, county of, attached to Mason county................ 9</p>
<p>Merchants, wholesale and retail, occupation tax levied on.... 45</p>
<p>Milam county, court of may levy and collect special tax for building court house............................ 79</p>
<p>Militia&#8212;</p>
<p>act of June 24, 1870, amended.................... 23</p>
<p>fines, etc., appropriated to pay State guard, etc........... 23</p>
<p>exemption from militia duty on payment of five dollars.... 23</p>
<p>exemption fund, appropriated as the fines, etc............. 23</p>
<p>Fourth of July to be day of general muster............ 23</p>
<p>muster of reserve militia to be held in the precincts......... 23</p>
<p>not more than four days in a year.................... 23</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">N.</head>
<p>New Braunfels, city council of, may levy tax for bridges..... 42</p>
<p>Nueces county, boundary of, defined.....................62,109</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1091" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="189" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">O</head>
<p>Oaths&#8212;</p>
<p>may be administered by officers and deputies named in tax act...................................... 53</p>
<p>may be administered by heads of departments............ 124</p>
<p>Occupation taxes&#8212;(See Taxes, act to give effect, etc.,) and page.................................. 44</p>
<p>Officers&#8212;</p>
<p>all peace, to arrest parties unlawfully carrying weapons.... 26</p>
<p>refusing or failing to arrest, to be dismissed on conviction in district court.............................. 27</p>
<p>and in addition fined not exceeding $500......................... 27</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">P</head>
<p>Pawn brokers, occupation tax levied on..................... 46</p>
<p>Pecan timber, to protect growth of...................... 42</p>
<p>Pecos county&#8212;</p>
<p>organized and boundaries defined...................... 73</p>
<p>commissioners appointed.......................... 73</p>
<p>shall divide county into five precincts and order necessary elections................................. 73</p>
<p>shall make return of election to Secretary of State, etc..... 73</p>
<p>county seat to be located by electors.......................... 73</p>
<p>Peddlers, occupation tax levied on..................... 45</p>
<p>Penal Code, articles 412 and 418 of, amended............... 84</p>
<p>Penitentiary, State&#8212;</p>
<p>Governor authorized to lease.................... 14</p>
<p>terms and conditions of lease..................... 14</p>
<p>directors of, to be appointed..................... 15</p>
<p>physician and chaplain to be appointed................... 15</p>
<p>salaries of officers to be paid monthly by lessees.......... 16</p>
<p>lessees to give bond in $50,000 to $100,000................... 16</p>
<p>appropriation for salaries of officers of, now unpaid, etc.... 24</p>
<p>Physician to be appointed to State penitentiary................ 15</p>
<p>Physicians, surgeons, dentists, occupation tax levied on...... 46</p>
<p>Pledge of real estate may be given in lieu of personal security by administrators, executors, guardians and trustees....... 83</p>
<p>Police&#8212;(See State Police.)</p>
<pb n="1092" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="190" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Polk county, clerk of District Court of, to transmit to clerk of District Court of San Jacinto county, causes, papers, etc., belonging to jurisdiction of the latter................... 34</p>
<p>Poll or capitation tax&#8212;</p>
<p>assessed on all male persons between twenty-one and sixty.. 43</p>
<p>persons failing to pay, shall not receive money from State or county............................. 50</p>
<p>Poor persons&#8212;(See Appeal.)</p>
<p>Pre-emption&#8212;(See Public Lands.)</p>
<p>Presiding Justices&#8212;</p>
<p>to perform duties as to idiots and lunatics, prescribed by act of February 5, 1858, to chief justices.................. 41</p>
<p>acts by, in relation thereto, validated...................... 41</p>
<p>Presidio county&#8212;</p>
<p>organized and boundary described....................... 86</p>
<p>commissioners appointed to divide into five precincts and hold election............................. 86</p>
<p>commissioners to make return of election to Secretary of State.................................. 86</p>
<p>county seat of, to be selected at same election............. 87</p>
<p>Probate matters&#8212;(See Estates of Deceased Persons.)</p>
<p>Proceedings in Courts&#8212;</p>
<p>no witness to be excluded on account of color, nor (in civil actions) because interested in the issue................. 108</p>
<p>where executor, administrator or guardian is party, neither party to testify as to acts of testator intestate or ward, un<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />less called by opposite party or by court................ 108</p>
<p>Proof or acknowledgment of instruments for record, before what officers................. 77</p>
<p>Property&#8212;</p>
<p>to be rendered for taxation, where, when and how........... 49</p>
<p>value of, how ascertained for taxation.................... 49</p>
<p>how freed from back taxes................. 52</p>
<p>when sold for taxes, how redeemed.................... 52</p>
<p>certain, exempt from taxation...................... 85</p>
<p>Public Lands&#8212;</p>
<p>occupant of 160 acres three years in good faith, entitled to patent......................... 16</p>
<p>pre-emptors compelled to abandon homestead, who return and complete their occupancy, likewise................. 16</p>
<p>original occupant dead, patent to his heirs.................... 16</p>
<p>assignee of original occupant entitled to patent............... 16</p>
<pb n="1093" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="191" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>each head of family having no homestead, entitled to 160 acres, etc.......................................... 93</p>
<p>on condition of three years&#8217; occupancy and paying fees.... 93</p>
<p>any person settling on public domain not appropriated, en<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />titled to purchase at $1 per acre..................... 93</p>
<p>certificate of survey or sufficient proof of occupancy......... 93</p>
<p>holder of any genuine certificate or land claim may locate on any land not appropriated, etc..................... 93</p>
<p>provided survey be returned to General Land Office by January 1, 1875........................... 93</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">R</head>
<p>Railroads and other internal improvements&#8212;(See Counties, Cities and Towns, authorized, etc.)</p>
<p>Railroad Companies&#8212;</p>
<p>authorized to change gauge............................. 7</p>
<p>income of, faxed........................... 47</p>
<p>tax reduced.......................... 60</p>
<p>may hold meetings of stockholders or directors out of State. 134</p>
<p>but twenty days&#8217; notice must be published in the official journal of district where principal office................... 134</p>
<p>proceedings of such meeting to be recorded in principal of<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fice in State in forty days.......................... 134</p>
<p>Recognizance, form of, on appeal to Supreme Court.......... 61</p>
<p>Record of instruments, upon proof or acknowledgment before what officers................................. 77</p>
<p>Registration&#8212;</p>
<p>special, to be made when election ordered for aiding rail<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />roads, ete............................. 139</p>
<p>conducted according to provisions of act of July 11, 1870.. 139</p>
<p>each certificate to be marked &#8220;special registration&#8221;........ 139</p>
<p>boards of appeals, etc., to meet and hear appeals, etc...... 139</p>
<p>none to vote unless holding certificate of special registration 139</p>
<p>Reserve militia&#8212;</p>
<p>musters of, to be held in the precincts..................... 23</p>
<p>times of, to be designated by the Governor.................... 23</p>
<p>not more than four days in a year...................... 23</p>
<p>Retailing liquors, occupation tax levied on........................ 44</p>
<p>Revenue, Governor authorized to procure bonds to supply de<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ficiency in, for current year........................ 106</p>
<pb n="1094" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="192" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Roads and Bridges&#8212;</p>
<p>county tax and poll tax for................. 44</p>
<p>persons liable to poll tax for, may pay in work................. 44</p>
<p>Robertson county, authorized to collect tax for building court house and jail.................. 27</p>
<p>Rockport, county seat of Refugio county removed to....... 12</p>
<p>Runnels county attached to Brown county............... 9</p>
<p>Russell, William H, witnesses on impeachment of, to be paid. 88, 91</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">S.</head>
<p>Sale of landed property&#8212;&#8226;</p>
<p>(See Landed Property.)</p>
<p>San Antonio-&#8212;</p>
<p>criminal court of, discontinued........................ 2</p>
<p>causes, books, records, writs, processes, bonds and recogni<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />zances therein transferred to Bexar District Court........... 2</p>
<p>San Jacinto county&#8212;</p>
<p>district clerk of Polk county to transfer to district court of, all causes, books, papers, etc............. 34</p>
<p>county tax collected in other counties on persons and prop<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />erty in, to be paid to Treasurer.................... 122</p>
<p>School fund&#8212;</p>
<p>perpetual, to be invested.................. 38</p>
<p>School houses&#8212;</p>
<p>tax levied, for district....................... 47</p>
<p>Schools, public free&#8212;</p>
<p>to be under control of Superintendent of Public Instruction 57</p>
<p>one supervisor of education for each judicial district....... 53</p>
<p>supervisors to hold office for four years...................... 58</p>
<p>compensation five dollars per day, not to exceed twelve hun<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dred dollars per annum...................... 58</p>
<p>may be removed by Superintendent, on approval of Grov<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ernor.................................. 58</p>
<p>supervisors to lay off counties into school districts........ 58</p>
<p>supervisors to appoint five school directors in each........ 58</p>
<p>subject to revision of Superintendent...................... 58</p>
<p>supervisors to enforce rules of board of education........ 58</p>
<p>board of education composed of Superintendent of Public Instruction, Governor and Attorney General............. 58</p>
<p>may adopt all necessary rules and regulations............. 58</p>
<pb n="1095" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="193" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>shall make no rule preventing directors from separating students....................... 58</p>
<p>shall report for action of Legislature, amendments, etc.... 59</p>
<p>available school fund for, defined............................. 59</p>
<p>directors of each school district may levy tax for school houses, etc................................ 59</p>
<p>shall require attendance at public schools of all the scholastic population at least four months........................... 59</p>
<p>parent or guardian of child not attending, liable to fine.... 59</p>
<p>but not, if shown to attend private teacher properly certified, or if prevented by ill health or danger from Indians...... 59</p>
<p>and no child under ten required to go more than a mile.... 59</p>
<p>Secretary of State&#8212;</p>
<p>to have tax law published............................. 56</p>
<p>Secretary of Senate&#8212;</p>
<p>to draw warrant on certificate of Sergeant-at-Arms of the Senate, in favor of witnesses on impeachment of W. H. Russell................................................ 88</p>
<p>Sheriff&#8212;</p>
<p>to levy bill of costs of clerk or justice and sell as under exe<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cution......................................... 28</p>
<p>not to charge fee for collecting.......................................... 28</p>
<p>to collect taxes, etc................................... 48</p>
<p>may collect by deputy, who may be a county officer....... 48</p>
<p>may collect in unorganized county attached to his....... 48</p>
<p>to post notice when he will receive taxes........................... 50</p>
<p>to give bond with three or more good securities................. 53</p>
<p>shall take and subscribe constitutional oath......................... 53</p>
<p>may be required to give new bond, etc........................... 53</p>
<p>when so required shall suspend duties until, etc........... 53</p>
<p>failing to do so in thirty days, shall be dismissed........... 53</p>
<p>shall give additional bond for county moneys.................. 54</p>
<p>shall report to Comptroller moneys collected.................... 54</p>
<p>shall pay Comptroller&#8217;s draft, or remit by draft, etc......... 54</p>
<p>shall make final settlement by December 31 in each year.... 54</p>
<p>shall obey orders of county court in regard to county moneys and pay to treasurer as be may be ordered.................... 54</p>
<p>compensation for services under tax law............... 55</p>
<p>excess thereof above $4000 to be paid into State Treasury.. 55</p>
<p>Sheriffs arid other peace officers, to arrest parties bearing weapons unlawfully.................................... 26</p>
<pb n="1096" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="194" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Sheriff or clerk, if party in any suit, district judge may ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />point sheriff or clerk pro tem., who shall be sworn and give bond............................................. 89</p>
<p>Spanish Grants&#8212;</p>
<p>copies to be obtained of, recorded in Reynosa, Camargo, Mier and Guerrero, Mexico......................... 56</p>
<p>Governor to appoint some suitable person to obtain.......... 56</p>
<p>transcripts to be certified by Mexican authorities............ 57</p>
<p>transcripts and translations to be filed in General Land Of<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />fice.......................... 57</p>
<p>fee for transcribing same as in General Land Office.......... 57</p>
<p>mileage to appointee, same as allowed United States jurors. 57</p>
<p>$2500 appropriated to pay expenses............................. 57</p>
<p>Special Acts&#8212;</p>
<p>Governor to have general index to, continued.................... 90</p>
<p>$250 appropriated for that purpose........................ 90</p>
<p>Starr county, boundary of defined...................... 62</p>
<p>State cemetery, graves in to be preserved..................... 35</p>
<p>State Police&#8212;</p>
<p>established in connection with militia................... 71</p>
<p>composed of one chief, six captains, twelve lieutenants, thirty sergeants and two hundred and ten privates................... 71</p>
<p>pay of privates and officers.............................. 71</p>
<p>additional pay for use of horses and arms............................. 71</p>
<p>additional pay for use of horses and arms to chief........ 71</p>
<p>and in lieu of traveling expenses............................. 71</p>
<p>chief, with approval of Governor, may make requisition on Comptroller to pay police........................... 71</p>
<p>Comptroller thereon to issue warrant.................... 71</p>
<p>chief to file vouchers with Comptroller.......................... 71</p>
<p>Governor or chief, with Governor&#8217;s approval, may remove any members of..................................... 71</p>
<p>shall receive in addition to pay sheriff&#8217;s mileage, etc................... 71</p>
<p>such compensation not due, unless prisoner conveyed to another county............................ 71</p>
<p>to be paid out of costs due sheriff........................... 71</p>
<p>any number of special policemen (not exceeding twenty) may be ordered out by Governor...................... 71</p>
<p>their pay, when in service, to be paid by county................. 72</p>
<p>Governor or chief may make conductors, etc., special police<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />men, but to receive no compensation....................... 72</p>
<p>State Treasurer&#8212;(See Treasurer.)</p>
<pb n="1097" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="195" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Steen, I. H.&#8212;</p>
<p>acts of, as justice of the peace in Hamilton county, legalized 131</p>
<p>acts of, as district clerk of Hamilton county, legalized..... 132</p>
<p>Stock Raising&#8212;</p>
<p>each organized county created an inspection district, except, etc................................................. 112</p>
<p>Governor to appoint inspector in each district................... 112</p>
<p>inspectors to hold office four years unless removed................ 112</p>
<p>in case of vacancy, presiding justice to appoint justice to act. 112</p>
<p>inspectors to give bond with two securities................... 112</p>
<p>penalty and condition of bond......................... 112</p>
<p>shall also take and subscribe oath of office....................... 112</p>
<p>bond and oath to be recorded and deposited with district clerk............................................... 112</p>
<p>each inspector to furnish himself with seal........................... 113</p>
<p>design on seal to be specified by Governor......................... 113</p>
<p>all official acts of inspector to be certified therewith................... 113</p>
<p>inspectors may appoint deputies.................. 113</p>
<p>deputies to give bond and take oath........................ 113</p>
<p>appointments and oaths to be recorded by district clerk.... 113</p>
<p>clerk of district court to furnish deputies certificates of ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />pointment.................................................. 113</p>
<p>deputies, each to have seal, same as principals.................. 113</p>
<p>inspector to inspect all hides and animals sold, leaving or going out of county for sale, etc...................... 113</p>
<p>shall record brands and marks, name of seller and buyer, and return certified copy to district clerk at the end of each month........................................ 113</p>
<p>shall not permit unbranded hide or animal to be taken out of county............................................ 114</p>
<p>nor permit to be slaughtered unbranded calf or yearling un<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />less identified.............................................. 114</p>
<p>inspectors to inspect all animals driven or sold for slaughter to packeries, etc., and all hides and animals taken from county for sale or shipment, and keep register of brands and marks, name of seller and buyer, and return certified copy to clerk at the end of each month................. 114</p>
<p>shall prevent sale or shipment of unbranded or freshly branded calves or yearlings, and slaughter of same at pick<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />eries, etc., unless identified.............................. 114</p>
<p>shall prevent the sale of all hides, or animals having no brand or unascertadnable brand, or taking or shipping such from county, unless identified................. 114</p>
<pb n="1098" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="196" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Stock Raising&#8212;</p>
<p>shall have power to seize and sequestrate all unmarked or freshly marked calves or yearlings about to be slaughtered or removed, unless identified, and all animals and hides having no brand or unascertainable brand, unless prop<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />erly accounted for, and sell........................... 114</p>
<p>sale to be at public auction after ten days&#8217; notice................ 114</p>
<p>proceeds, if owner not found, paid to county treasury....... 114</p>
<p>failing to file certified copies of register, liable to fine of twenty-five dollars............................... 114</p>
<p>making false return, or permiting slaughter, sale or ship<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ment contrary to law, liable to fine of one hundred dollars 115</p>
<p>fees of inspector.......................... 115</p>
<p>on payment of fees lie shall issue proper certificate........ 115</p>
<p>persons buying or driving for sale or shipment out of county (except counties excepted) to take bill of sale from seller, showing number, kind, marks and brands of animals.... 115</p>
<p>to be inspected by inspector or deputy......................... 115</p>
<p>bill of sale to be recorded and certified by district clerk.... 115</p>
<p>certificate shall protect from payment of inspection fees in any other district in the State.................... 115</p>
<p>persons failing to comply, fined $25 for each animal, etc... 115</p>
<p>person selling, taking, etc., any horse or other animal with<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />out written consent of owner, liable to fine $25........... 116</p>
<p>purchaser with knowledge, liable to fine $25............... 116</p>
<p>person found in range in possession of hog with ears or head cut off, or dead hog newly marked, fine $25.............. 116</p>
<p>and liable in civil suit to owner for double value........ 116</p>
<p>written consent not valid, unless certified under seal of dis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />trict clerk or notary public............................ 116</p>
<p>but owner may testify to his consent............... 116</p>
<p>stock owner having marks and brands recorded, may fur<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />nish to inspector list certified by the district clerk, and names of his agents attached......................... 116</p>
<p>such list filed, sufficient authority to agent....................... 116</p>
<p>seller making and buyer accepting false bill of sale, liable to fine $25...................................... 117</p>
<p>altering, etc., marks or brands, finable $25 for each animal not his own.................................... 117</p>
<p>buyer may add his brand, not defacing former brand..... 117 any one who shall take, drive, etc., any animal contrary to</p>
<p>sections 3 and 5, liable to fine $25 for each head............. 117</p>
<pb n="1099" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="197" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>taking, driving, or cutting out from mother calf, yearling, etc., not his own, finable $25 for each head............... 117</p>
<p>persons gathering stock to drive to nearest stock pen...... 117</p>
<p>holding more than twenty-four hours, liable to fine $100... 117</p>
<p>from stock range, taking, driving, etc., animal not his own without written consent, finable $25 each head........ 117</p>
<p>failing to have brand recorded, prima facie evidence of no stock........................ 117</p>
<p>skinning dead, animal not his own without written consent, or buying skin knowingly, finable $10 for each hide..117, 118</p>
<p>but owner may testify to consent....................... 118</p>
<p>buying or selling hide with unascertainable brand, or brand<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ed after skinned or taking it out of county, finable $10 for each hide; and inspector may seize and sequestrate such hides................................. 118</p>
<p>Clerk of District Court allowed for recording and certifying same fees as allowed by law for similar services........ 118</p>
<p>upon affidavit that any one holding or driving contrary to law, warrant to be issued, etc., fine double value of each head........................................ 118</p>
<p>animals to be driven or shipped beyond the limits of the State, to go out of the State at certain points............ 118</p>
<p>animals intended for Mexico, or to be shipped from any part of Texas, shall be inspected at the place of shipment, or of crossing the State boundary.......................... 119</p>
<p>inspector&#8217;s fee two and a half cents for each hide or animal.. 119</p>
<p>inspector to keep correct record of each herd................. 119</p>
<p>inspector failing to do so, finable as in section 6................... 119</p>
<p>buyers to drive across the northern or northeastern bound<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ary of the State to put on cattle road mark............... 119</p>
<p>failing to do so, punishable as in section 8................... 119</p>
<p>shipping or driving, or attempting to do so, contrary to the provisions of this act, punishable by fine, etc.........119,120</p>
<p>but hides and animals from Mexico may be shipped from any port in Texas on certificate of United States collecter or inspector, where imported, or of any justice of the county....................................... 120</p>
<p>such officers allowed same fees as in section 22.................. 120</p>
<p>to what counties the whole act applies....................... 120</p>
<p>to what counties that part relating to inspection of live stock (not of hides) applies............................ 120</p>
<pb n="1100" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="198" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>none of the provisions of this act apply to any county not mentioned in sections 24, 25 and 26....................... 120</p>
<p>takes effect forty days after passage............................. 120</p>
<p>Superintendent of Immigration-&#8212;(See Immigration.)</p>
<p>Superintendent of Public Instruction....................... 57</p>
<p>shall have supervisory control of all public free schools.... 57</p>
<p>salary of. $3000 per annum......................... 57</p>
<p>shall keep record of scholastic population of each county... 57</p>
<p>shall apportion school fund to counties accordingly....... 57</p>
<p>shall keep correct account of moneys of school fund, etc., and report annually to the Governor condition of school fund, etc...............................................57, 58</p>
<p>shall prescribe and furnish all necessary forms for teachers and officers........................................... 58</p>
<p>shall direct as to reports by subordinates.......................... 58</p>
<p>shall approve all accounts for compensation and other ex<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />penses.............................................. 58</p>
<p>shall appoint supervisor for each judicial district with ap<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />proval of Governor.......................................... 58</p>
<p>may remove them on approval of the Governor.......................... 58</p>
<p>may control and revise their proceedings.............................. 58</p>
<p>with Governor and Attorney General, form board of educa<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion........................................... 58</p>
<p>Supervisors of Education&#8212;</p>
<p>one for each judicial district................................... 58</p>
<p>to be appointed and removed by superintendent with ap proval of the Governor.............................. 58</p>
<p>to hold office for four years................................ 58</p>
<p>compensation $5 per day, not to exceed $1200 per annum.. 58</p>
<p>to lay oft counties in districts and appoint directors............. 58</p>
<p>Supreme Court&#8212;</p>
<p>form of recognizance on appeal to...................... 61</p>
<p>shall not entertain jurisdiction unless, etc................ 62</p>
<p>except in cases now pending.................. 62</p>
<p>time of commencing term fixed to first Monday in Decem<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ber......................................... 81</p>
<p>(See Clerk of Supreme Court.)</p>
<p>Supplemental tax, levied on property not assessed or not paid on................................................ 48</p>
<p>Sureties&#8212;(See Estates of Deceased Persons.)</p>
<p>Surveyor&#8212;(See County Surveyor.)</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1101" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="199" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">T.</head>
<p>Tax by Counties, Cities and Towns&#8212;</p>
<p>may be levied to pay interest and sinking fund of bonds issued in aid of railroads, etc........................ 30</p>
<p>to be applied to no other purpose....................... 30</p>
<p>to be collected by collector of state taxes, and by him paid into State Treasury...................... 30</p>
<p>to be paid out by State Treasurer on warrant of Comptroller 30</p>
<p>Taxation, certain property exempted from....................... 85</p>
<p>Taxes&#8212;</p>
<p>levied according to provisions of Constitution................... 43</p>
<p>poll or capitation tax for public schools $1.................... 43</p>
<p>direct ad valorem State tax one-half of one per cent....... 44</p>
<p>direct ad valorem county tax one-half of State tax....... 44</p>
<p>may be reduced by county court if deemed too large...... 44</p>
<p>direct ad valorem road and bridge tax one-fourth of one per cent................... 44</p>
<p>poll tax for same purposes not less than $1.................... 44</p>
<p>any person thus taxed may pay in work........................ 44</p>
<p>Occupation Taxes&#8212;</p>
<p>retailing liquors................................... 44</p>
<p>not to include wine or beer made in the State...................... 44</p>
<p>billiard and bagatelle, and other tables................. 44</p>
<p>nine or ten pin alley in city or town.................... 45</p>
<p>nine or ten pin alley mot in city or town or county site.... 45</p>
<p>foot peddler (in each county)...................... 45</p>
<p>peddler with one horse or yoke of oxen (do.)........... 45</p>
<p>peddler with two horses or yokes of oxen (do.)................ 45</p>
<p>venders of fruits, trees and home manufactures excepted... 45</p>
<p>gift enterprises..................... 45</p>
<p>theatre or dramatic representation............................ 45</p>
<p>amateur arid charitable performances excepted............................ 45</p>
<p>circus.............................................. 45</p>
<p>menagerie, wax work, etc., etc.............................. 45</p>
<p>concert (entertainments for charitable purposes excepted.. 45</p>
<p>Hotels, first class, second, class, third class..................... 45</p>
<p>cook shop, eating house, boarding house..................... 45</p>
<p>no house, boarding house, unless four boarders, etc................ 45</p>
<p>and not when annual income is less than $300.................... 45</p>
<p>livery stables, (four classes)............................. 45</p>
<pb n="1102" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="200" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>distillery, brewery.................... 45</p>
<p>merchants, wholesale........................... 45</p>
<p>merchants, first, second, third, fourth class, retail.........45,48</p>
<p>classes explained and merchant explained........................ 46</p>
<p>traveling agent, selling patent rights medicines, etc................... 46</p>
<p>brokers, two classes....................... 46</p>
<p>life, fire and marine insurance companies........................ 46</p>
<p>tax to be paid by company to Comptroller....................... 46</p>
<p>copies of Comptroller&#8217;s receipt under seal to be authority to agents to work in any county.............................. 46</p>
<p>tax to be assessed where principal office.................... 46</p>
<p>if principal office not in State, then where principal State agency..................................................... 46</p>
<p>physician, surgeon, dentist.............................. 46</p>
<p>attorney at law................................... 46</p>
<p>daguerrean or photographic gallery, three classes................. 46</p>
<p>auctioneer..................................... 46</p>
<p>barber....................................... 47</p>
<p>ship, merchandise or cotton broker............................ 47</p>
<p>pawnbroker............................ 47</p>
<p>keeper of ferry or toll bridge..................... 47</p>
<p>commission merchant................................... 47</p>
<p>land agents............................... 47</p>
<p>who are and who are not land agents......................... 47</p>
<p>county courts may levy taxes on occupations equal to one<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />half State tax.................................... 47</p>
<p>traveling agents, physicians, surgeons, dentists, attorneys and land agents, to pay but once a year..................... 47</p>
<p>county courts not authorized to tax incomes of railroad or telegraph companies.................................... 47</p>
<p>pro rata tax may be paid for less than a year, but not for less than three months........................................ 47</p>
<p>tax on railroad and telegraph companies........................... 47, 60</p>
<p>tax for district school houses one-fourth of State tax....... 47</p>
<p>supplemental to tax on property not assessed or paid on.... 48</p>
<p>taxes to be assessed by justices and collected by sheriffs.... 48</p>
<p>county occupation tax to be collected by treasurer....... 48</p>
<p>those officers may act by deputy, who may be any county of<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ficer........................................... 48</p>
<p>court to designate magistrate to assess unorganized county. 48</p>
<p>sheriff to collect therein.................................. 48</p>
<p>property to be rendered for taxation, where........................ 48</p>
<p>justices to call on all residents in their precincts for lists... 48</p>
<pb n="1103" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="201" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>justices failing to do so, liable to fine...................... 49</p>
<p>property to be rendered for taxation, when and how.......... 49</p>
<p>value of property, how ascertained for taxation.................... 49</p>
<p>if unrendered, to be fixed by the assessing officer............. 49</p>
<p>if rendered, and the assessing officer not satisfied with the valuation, he shall assess............................. 49</p>
<p>if owner dissatisfied, arbitration to be had................... 50</p>
<p>assessor or owner may appeal to county court..................... 50</p>
<p>but owner must first pay the taxes he has admitted............ 50</p>
<p>duty of all persons to render property and pay taxes....... 50</p>
<p>taxes assessed on all real property to be a lien thereon..... 50</p>
<p>duty of all persons to pay poll tax......................... 50</p>
<p>failing to do so, shall not receive money from State or county................................... 50</p>
<p>unpaid tax on personal property, or county occupation tax, may be levied on the same, advertisement and sale.......50, 51</p>
<p>sheriff to post notice when he will receive taxes in each precinct......................................... 51</p>
<p>failure to advertise, no excuse for non-payment......................... 51</p>
<p>assessing officers to assess unrendered (real) property, etc... 51.</p>
<p>owner failing to pay, delinquent list to be rendered to the Comptroller of Public Accounts.............................. 51</p>
<p>delinquent lists may be collected as in actions of debt...... 51</p>
<p>if before justice, nor for enforcement of lien......................... 51</p>
<p>if not made on justice&#8217;s judgment, lien to be enforced in the proper district court............................. 51</p>
<p>back taxes may be sued for and recovered.................... 51, 52</p>
<p>property, how freed from back taxes................... 52, 135, 136</p>
<p>Comptroller to give person paying sealed receipt.......... 52</p>
<p>when sold for taxes, how redeemed.......................... 52</p>
<p>county tax collected in other counties to be paid into the Treasury to the credit of the county where due................. 53</p>
<p>officers and deputies named in this act may administer oaths, 53</p>
<p>justices and sheriffs to give bond in form prescribed by Comptroller, three or more good securities, etc................ 53</p>
<p>shall also take and subscribe constitutional oath............. 55</p>
<p>bond to be recorded by district clerk and deposited with Comptroller................................... 53</p>
<p>condition of such bond.................................. 53</p>
<p>justice or sheriff may be required to give new bond, etc........ 53</p>
<p>when so required, shall suspend duties, etc........... 53</p>
<p>on failure to give new bond in thirty days, shall be dis<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />missed................................................ 53</p>
<pb n="1104" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="202" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>sheriff to give additional bond for county moneys............ 54</p>
<p>sheriff to report to Comptroller amounts collected........ 54</p>
<p>sheriff to pay Comptroller&#8217;s drafts, or remit by draft, etc... 54</p>
<p>sheriff to make final settlement by thirty-first December in each year................................................. 54</p>
<p>sheriff to obey orders of county court in regard to county moneys, and pay to Treasurer as he may be ordered....... 54</p>
<p>compensation to justices for assessing...................... 55</p>
<p>compensation to sheriffs for services under tax law.................. 55</p>
<p>fee for every oath administered........................... 55</p>
<p>excess of compensation of justice or sheriff over $4000 to be paid into State treasury.................... 55</p>
<p>Comptroller to prepare instructions, etc................. 55</p>
<p>such instructions to be obeyed by all officers...................... 56</p>
<p>conflicting laws repealed..................... 56</p>
<p>Secretary of State to have act published.......................... 56</p>
<p>Taxes, Back&#8212;</p>
<p>Person rendering property for taxation and paying taxes for 1871 and previous years, discharged from all claim for back taxes, State, county, municipal or special............. 135</p>
<p>Comptroller to give registered and sealed receipt, which, shall be received in all courts as conclusive proof.......... 136</p>
<p>if real estate has been sold, delinquent to pay to buyer amount paid and interest at 25 per cent. till repaid or deposited in the Treasury.............................. 136</p>
<p>purchaser at tax sale invested with lien for purchase money, 136</p>
<p>property cleared of back taxes accruing after 1871, by pay<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ment of all taxes accrued since acceptance of Constitu<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tion (if any) with interest and three times the State tax of the year when paid, and ten per cent. in addition and ten per cent. for each year..................... 136</p>
<p>Telegraph&#8212;</p>
<p>warrant or affidavit may be sent by...................... 39</p>
<p>operator or other person divulging liable to fine or peniten<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />tiary............................................... 40</p>
<p>companies, incomes of, taxed............................. 49</p>
<p>operators exempted from jury and militia duty................... 67</p>
<p>Titus county&#8212;</p>
<p>county court of, may issue bonds for building court house and jail........................................... 22</p>
<p>bonds not to be used or sold at less than par................... 22</p>
<p>may levy tax not more than one-half per cent..................... 22</p>
<pb n="1105" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="203" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>tax to be appropriated to build court house and jail and pay bonds............................................ 22</p>
<p>Towns, counties and cities, authorized to aid in construction of railroads, etc........................... 29</p>
<p>Transcripts and translations of Spanish grants, to be pro<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />cured from Mexico and filed in General Land Office.... 57</p>
<p>Treasurer, State&#8212;</p>
<p>to receive, pay out, and keep separate accounts of taxes levied by counties, etc., in aid of railroads, etc.............. 31</p>
<p>to be member of auditorial board..................... 68</p>
<p>to set apart yearly sufficient to pay semi-annual interest and one-third of principal of bonds for deficiency in revenue... 107</p>
<p>to pay warrants of Comptroller in favor of Commissioners of Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas, out of school fund................................ 135</p>
<p>Treasury, balance in, of appropriations for per diem of mem<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />bers and officers of the Legislature, reappropriated....... 1</p>
<p>Trial by jury, and appeal guaranteed to persons charged with unlawfully bearing weapons.................................. 26</p>
<p>trustees&#8212;(See Administrators, Executors, Guardians and Trustees.)</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">U.</head>
<p>United States&#8212;</p>
<p>authorized to purchase land, etc............................ 18</p>
<p>property so purchased to be held free from taxation....... 19</p>
<p>money due from, to Texas, to be received by the Governor.. 87</p>
<p>to be placed in the Treasury, etc.................. 87</p>
<p>if in gold, may be converted to currency................ 87</p>
<p>Governor authorized to appoint agent..................... 87</p>
<p>agent, if State officer, to be paid expenses only................... 87</p>
<p>one thousand dollars appropriated for expenses............... 87</p>
<p>Unorganized county, county court may designate justice to as<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />sess in...................................... 48</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1106" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="204" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">V.</head>
<p>Value of Property, how ascertained for taxation............... 49</p>
<p>Van Zandt county, county seat of, located at Canton........ 17</p>
<p>acts of county court of, validated.................. 80</p>
<p>county court of, authorized to levy special tax for building court house.......................... 130</p>
<p>Venue changed in case of M. A. Wygal, in the State of Texas, from Fort Bend county to Travis county................ 109</p>
<p>Voting on proposition to aid railroads, etc., to be by ballot.... 29</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">W.</head>
<p>Warrant of Arrest&#8212;</p>
<p>may be transmitted by telegraph.................... 39</p>
<p>unless signed or endorsed by Supreme or district judge, of<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ficer shall procure endorsement of nearest magistrate... 39</p>
<p>affidavit charging crime, may be sent by telegraph........ 39</p>
<p>magistrate receiving, to issue warrant thereon................ 39</p>
<p>original warrant or affidavit to be deposited with manager of telegraph office................. 40</p>
<p>shall be forwarded in preference to other business........... 40</p>
<p>when received, shall be delivered as soon as practicable to the person to whom addressed, certified to by manager as a true copy.................................... 40</p>
<p>not to be forwarded unless properly certified.............. 40</p>
<p>not to be endorsed or warrant issued unless, etc.............. 40</p>
<p>fine for divulging to any but proper party............... 40</p>
<p>or imprisonment in penitentiary................. 40</p>
<p>Washington county, County Court of, authorized to levy tax for jail............ 11</p>
<p>Weapons, Deadly&#8212;</p>
<p>keeping and bearing of, regulated..................... 25</p>
<p>fine for, and weapon forfeited to the county................... 25</p>
<p>who permitted to bear..................... 25</p>
<p>excusable, if done openly, in pressing danger................... 25</p>
<p>but not, if difficulty commenced by accused.............. 25</p>
<p>not to apply to county designated by Governor as a frontier county.................................. 26</p>
<p>fine for bearing arms at certain assemblies and places..... 26</p>
<p>penalty for subsequent offense......................... 26</p>
<pb n="1107" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="205" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>how fines and forfeited weapons appropriated................ 26</p>
<p>sheriffs and other peace officers to arrest violators............ 26</p>
<p>trial by jury and right of appeal guaranteed...................... 26</p>
<p>bond required in case of appeal.................... 26</p>
<p>money collected on forfeited bond appropriated as the fines.. 27</p>
<p>officer refusing or failing to arrest, dismissed from office on conviction before district court............................... 27</p>
<p>in addition fined not over $500.................... 27</p>
<p>district courts have concurrent jurisdiction of this act....... 27</p>
<p>act to be given specially in charge to grand jury......... 27</p>
<p>Governor to publish act throughout State..................... 27</p>
<p>to take effect sixty days after passage............... 27</p>
<p>Webb county, boundary defined.................. 62</p>
<p>Witness&#8212;</p>
<p>not to be excluded on account of color, nor (in civil cases) on account of interest............................ 108</p>
<p>where executor, administrator or guardian, is party, neither party to testify as to acts of testator, intestate or ward, unless called by opposite party or the court......... 108</p>
<p>Witnesses in impeachment of W. H. Russell, to be paid............ 89, 91</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">Z</head>
<p>Zapata county, boundary of, defined................. 62</p>
</div3>
</div2>
<div2 type="act">
<head type="main">JOINT RESOLUTIONS.</head>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">A</head>
<p>Adjutant General, directed to procure suitable building, and remove powder, etc., thereto............................ 141</p>
<p>Appropriations&#8212;</p>
<p>to pay for portrait of Gen. Sam. Houston............. 147</p>
<p>to pay costs in suit of Gray, Receiver, etc., vs. Governor, etc., 148</p>
<p>to pay district judges for July and August, 1870............... 159</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1108" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="206" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">B</head>
<p>Backers, J. R., presented with Winchester carbine for gallan<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />try against Indians.................................. 156</p>
<p>Bills of last session, introducer of bill which passed both houses and failed to become a law, may withdraw enrolled copy from office of Secretary of State............... 147</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">C</head>
<p>Clerks, Engrossing and Enrolling, may occupy State Library Room................................ 148</p>
<p>Comptroller of Public Accounts&#8212;</p>
<p>to re-transfer $35,950 05 from available school fund account to State revenue account......................... 154</p>
<p>to audit claims of district judges for pay for July and Au<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />gust. 1870............................ 159</p>
<p>Constitution, amendment of, section 6, article 10 of, to be sub<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />mitted................... 160</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">D</head>
<p>Daniels, R.&#8212;</p>
<p>presented with Winchester carbine for gallantry against In<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dians......................... 156</p>
<p>Davis county (now Cass)&#8212;</p>
<p>to be furnished with books, laws, etc....................... 157</p>
<p>District Judges&#8212;</p>
<p>claims for pay in July and August, 1870, to be audited and paid.................... 159</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">E</head>
<p>Election&#8212;</p>
<p>(See United States Senator.)</p>
<p>Governor authorized to issue proclamation for special....... 156</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1109" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="207" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">G</head>
<p>Galveston Mercantile Library&#8212;</p>
<p>(secretary or State to issue to, such complete sets of public documents as can be spared................. 158</p>
<p>Gibson, B. M.&#8212;</p>
<p>presented with. Winchester carbine for gallantry against In<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dians.................... 156</p>
<p>Governor&#8212;</p>
<p>authorized to direct appeal to be taken in case of Gray, re<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ceiver for Memphis and El Paso Railroad Company, against the Governor and Commissioner of General Land Office, in Circuit Court of United States for Western District of Texas............... 144</p>
<p>authorized to employ assistant counsel to appear in the Su<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />preme Court of the United States, in case the Attorney General cannot leave his office.................. 144</p>
<p>authorized to suspend sale of Texas and New Orleans Rail<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />road, the company having paid amount due........... 146</p>
<p>authorized to issue proclamation for special election........ 156</p>
<p>authorized to dispose of Houston Tap and Brazoria Railroad, 158</p>
<p>Greeley, Hon. Horace&#8212;</p>
<p>invited to visit Austin as guest of the State.................. 162</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">H</head>
<p>Harrington, J. W.&#8212;</p>
<p>Harrington, D. E.&#8212;</p>
<p>Haynes, W. R.&#8212;</p>
<p>each presented with Winchester carbine for gallantry against Indians........................... 156</p>
<p>Houston Tap and Brazoria Railroad&#8212;</p>
<p>Governor authorized to dispose of..................... 158</p>
<p>Houston, Gen. Sam.&#8212;</p>
<p>appropriation to pay for portrait of...................... 147</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1110" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="208" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">I</head>
<p>Page</p>
<p>Indian Country&#8212;</p>
<p>Congress urged in some way to open the, north of Texas, to settlement, and to establish State of Territorial Gov<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ernments.................................... 154</p>
<p>Indians&#8212;</p>
<p>(See murders and outrages by Indians.)</p>
<p>Representatives in Congress called on to urge the removal of the Comanches and Kiowas to at least one hundred and fifty miles from organized territory............. 153</p>
<p>for gallantry against, Winchester carbines presented to sun<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dry individuals................................. 156</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">M</head>
<p>Mail Facilities&#8212;</p>
<p>resolution asking influence of Representatives in Congress for appointment of special mail agent for Texas, for increas<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ing...................................... 142</p>
<p>Memphis and El Paso Railroad Company&#8212;</p>
<p>in suit by Gray, receiver of, against the Governor and Com<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />missioner of the Land Office, appeal advised from decision of U. S. Circuit Court.......................... 143</p>
<p>Governor authorized to employ additional counsel in Su<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />preme Court of United States, in case the Attorney Gen<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />eral cannot leave his office to appear there for the State.. 144</p>
<p>appropriation to pay costs.......................... 148</p>
<p>desire of State expressed that Supreme Court decide said appeal as soon as practicable....................... 148</p>
<p>Montgomery, Capt. William W.&#8212;</p>
<p>asking Congress to confer pension on widow and heirs of.... 155</p>
<p>Morrison William&#8212;</p>
<p>presented with Winchester carbine for gallantry against In<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dians........................................ 156</p>
<p>Murders and outrages by Indians&#8212;</p>
<p>requesting Congress to send committee to inquire into and report upon................................... 149</p>
</div3>
<pb n="1111" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="209" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">P</head>
<p>Phelan, E.&#8212;</p>
<p>presented with Winchester carbine for gallantry against In<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dians.......................................... 156</p>
<p>Phillips, M.&#8212;</p>
<p>presented with Winchester carbine for gallantry against In<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dians...................................... 156</p>
<p>Postal service&#8212;</p>
<p>Representatives in Congress requested to urge on Postmaster General the necessity of three assistants to the postal agent, 152</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">R</head>
<p>Railroad&#8212;</p>
<p>(See Houston Tap and Brazoria Railroad.)</p>
<p>Railroad to Pacific&#8212;</p>
<p>urging upon Congress the passage of a bill for construction of, from eastern boundary of Texas, on or near thirty<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />second parallel.................................. 145</p>
<p>Reams, J. M.&#8212;</p>
<p>presented with Winchester carbine for gallantry against In<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dians....................................... 156</p>
<p>Rockport&#8212;</p>
<p>favoring establishment of port of entry at.............. 153</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">S</head>
<p>Sabine Pass&#8212;</p>
<p>favoring establishment of port of entry at.............. 143</p>
<p>Secretary of State&#8212;</p>
<p>to deliver to members enrolled copy of any bill which at last session passed both houses and failed to become a law, 147</p>
<p>to present Winchester carbines to several persons for gal<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />lantry against Indians............................ 156</p>
<p>to furnish Galveston Mercantile Library such public docu<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />ments as may be spared............................ 158</p>
<p>Senator&#8212;</p>
<p>(See United States Senator.)</p>
<pb n="1112" ed="gammelslawsoftexas" /><pb ed="unknown" n="210" /><fw type="header" place="top">Index.</fw>
<p>Shelby, E. M.&#8212;</p>
<p>presented with Winchester carbine for gallantry against In<pc force="weak">-</pc><lb break="no" />dians..................................... 156</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">T</head>
<p>Telegraph Facilities&#8212;</p>
<p>Representatives in Congress requested to urge passage of a bill giving increased.............................. 151</p>
<p>Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company&#8212;</p>
<p>Governor authorized to suspend sale of road............. 146</p>
<p>Tod, Commodore John G.&#8212;</p>
<p>Representatives in Congress requested to urge that name of, be incorporated in navy of United States.............. 161</p>
<p>Treasurer, State&#8212;</p>
<p>authorized to pay district judges&#8217; claims for salary for July and August, 1870................................ 159</p>
</div3>
<div3 type="section">
<head type="main">U</head>
<p>United States Senator&#8212;</p>
<p>to be elected for term commencing March 4, 1871.......... 141</p>
<p>election to be held on the twenty-fourth of January 1871... 142</p>
</div3>
</div2>
</div1>
</body>
</text>
